<FTL>
<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					DUSKBRINGER SECTOR 
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->

<!--
		ITEMS!!!
	Events that give stuff
-->
<eventList name="ITEMS_DUSKBRINGER">
	<event load="DUSK_MILITIA_ESCORT"/>
	<event load="DUSK_PROPOGANDA"/>
	<event load="DUSK_SLAVER_TRADE"/>
	<event load="DUSK_IDOL"/>
</eventList>

<event name="DUSK_MILITIA_ESCORT" unique="true">
	<text>Friends of the Federation aren't all that common in these parts, but a Militia Transport protected by an escort is passing through. They must have noticed you, but they don't attempt to make contact.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MILITIA_DUSK_ESCORT" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Approach.</text>
		<event>
			<text>It appears that the transport has sustained some damage, and judging from the nature of the damage it appears to have been Energy Cannons, meaning they were most likely attacked by the Duskbringers.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Offer some scrap to help repair.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The Militiamen are surprised by your offer, but they gratiously accept.</text>
					<item_modify>
						<item type="scrap" min="-15" max="-25"/>
					</item_modify>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event>
							<text>They offer you a gift as thanks for your generous donation.</text>
							<autoReward level="LOW">missiles_only</autoReward>
							<weapon name="RANDOM"/>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>They make easy targets. Attack!</text>
				<event>
					<text>The Escort isn't about to let you get away with your attack. The Transport is unable to fight back and watches the battle in despair.</text>
					<ship hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="MORALITY_UPDATE_GENERAL_FIGHT"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice req="BLUELIST_DRONES_REPAIR_ALL">
				<text>(Repair Drone) Offer to use the drone to fix up their ship.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The Militiamen are surprised by your offer, but they gratiously accept.</text>
					<item_modify>
						<item type="drones" min="-1" max="-1"/>
					</item_modify>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event>
							<text>They offer you a gift as thanks for your generous donation.</text>
							<autoReward level="LOW">missiles_only</autoReward>
							<weapon name="RANDOM"/>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice req="REPAIR_ARM">
				<text>(Repair Arm) Offer to use the arm to fix up their hull.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The Militiamen are surprised by your offer, but they gratiously accept.</text>
					<item_modify>
						<item type="scrap" min="-5" max="-5"/>
					</item_modify>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event>
							<text>They offer you a gift as thanks for your generous donation.</text>
							<autoReward level="LOW">missiles_only</autoReward>
							<weapon name="RANDOM"/>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Ignore them.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The caravan doesn't bother you, and eventually the ships jump away.</text>
					<choice>
						<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
						<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>Do nothing.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore them.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Militiamen don't bother you, and eventually the ships jump away.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="DUSK_MILITIA_ESCORT_SURRENDER"> <!--only 75% chance to occur-->
	<text>The Militia Escort can't escape without leaving the transport unprotected. Instead, they opt to surrender, pleading for you to let them live.</text>
	<choice>
		<text>Let them live.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You decide to pull back from your assault. The Envoy is left almost completely destroyed, and most likely won't be able to repair the transport in time to save both of them before the Duskbringers arrive. Still, they hand over a weapon from the transport's cargo as "thanks" for "sparing" them.</text>
			<weapon name="RANDOM"/>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Keep fighting.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="DUSK_MILITIA_ESCORT_DESTROY">
	<text>The escort is destroyed, leaving the transport unprotected. They have no where to run, and are completely at your mercy.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Destroy the transport and salvage the wreck.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The militiamen aboard the transport plead for you to spare them, but you end transmissions and destroy their ship. It explodes much more violently than expected, the shockwave throwing back your ship and sending debris scattering across the hull. You don't know what the ship was carrying, but it must have been something explosive. You're certain the rest of the cargo is destroyed, but there still remains some wreckage to salvage.</text>
			<autoReward level="MED">scrap_only</autoReward>
			<damage amount="2"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Demand the transport transfer their cargo.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The militiamen hurry to meet your demands. It appears their ship was carrying high grade explosives and ballistic weaponry, of which you now hold ownership over. You leave them to their certain demise.</text>
			<autoReward level="HIGH">missiles_only</autoReward>
			<weapon name="GIFTLIST_EXPLOSIVES"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DUSK_SLAVER_TRADE">
	<text>Not too long after you jump to this beacon a slaver also jumps nearby. They hail you. "Interesting, a Feddy. Ain't a common sight down here. Don't suppose you need some crew?"</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ask to see their slaves.</text>
		<event load="DUSK_SLAVER_TRADE_BUY"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Kill these bastards.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Shame, I was hoping you might be different... Men, arm the guns!"</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_SLAVER_ALL" hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>We don't deal with slavers.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Yes yes, to be expected. Have fun dealing with the Duskys!" They jump away, and a Duskbringer ship jumps in almost immediately after. The slavers must have been followed!</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_DUSK_FIGHT" hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="DUSK_SLAVER_TRADE_BUY">
	<event>
		<text>Before you can express your interest, a Duskbringer hot in pursuit of the slaver ship jumps in and destroys the pirates. They waste no time moving in to destroy you as well!</text>
		<ship load="SHIP_DUSK_FIGHT" hostile="true"/>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
		</choice>
	</event> 
	<event>
		<text>"Now THAT sure is an unexpected sight. Come aboard captain, see if there's anything that... piques your interests."</text>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Come aboard</text>
			<event load="DUSK_SLAVER_TRADE_BUY_2"/>
		</choice>
	</event> 
</eventList>
<event name="DUSK_SLAVER_TRADE_BUY_2">
	<text>The inside of the slaver ship is no pretty sight. All around various aliens are chained to the walls, many of which have sickening bruises or scars all over their bodies. To turn against the slavers now would be a death sentence, so you better buy someone or get out.</text>
	<choice>
		<text>Buy an Engi.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Excellent choice!" The pirates unchain the slave and toss them in your direction. You bring them back to your ship before telling them that they've been liberated. Perhaps the Duskbringers aren't as bad as the pirates afterall...</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="engi"/>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="-45" max="-45"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Buy a Rockman.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Excellent choice!" The pirates unchain the slave and toss them in your direction. You bring them back to your ship before telling them that they've been liberated. Perhaps the Duskbringers aren't as bad as the pirates afterall...</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="rock"/>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="-35" max="-35"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Buy a Vampweed.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Excellent choice!" The pirates unchain the slave and toss them in your direction. You bring them back to your ship before telling them that they've been liberated. Perhaps the Duskbringers aren't as bad as the pirates afterall...</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="orchid_vampweed"/>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="-40" max="-40"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Leave.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Ah what a shame. If you ever need some extra hands, you can always find us again!" You quickly leave before they can consider taking you captive as well.</text>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DUSK_PROPOGANDA">
	<text>A massive machine floats nearby, akin to a station in size but appears to be fully automated and Zoltan made. As soon as lies start flooding in through your radio, it becomes clear that this is some sort of automated propaganda broadcaster. "Federation officers eat BABIES! That's a fact! Think of the children. Join the Duskbringers today and make the monsters pay!"</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Dismantle the machine for scrap.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Duskbringers and their fascist lies can go to hell. You take apart the power source for the machine and strip apart its outer hull.</text>
			<autoReward level="MED">droneparts</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_ENGI">
		<text>(Engi Crew) Reprogram the machine to spread lies about your location.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Rebels and Duskbringers have worked together on occasion but wouldn't normally take advice from propaganda like this. Still - the location of your ship is information they wouldn't want to pass up and they wouldn't expect the Duskbringers to have any reason to lie.</text>
			<modifyPursuit amount="-3"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_ENGINEER">
		<text>(Engineer Crew) Reprogram the machine to spread lies about your location.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Rebels and Duskbringers have worked together on occasion but wouldn't normally take advice from propaganda like this. Still - the location of your ship is information they wouldn't want to pass up and they wouldn't expect the Duskbringers to have any reason to lie.</text>
			<modifyPursuit amount="-3"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="hacking">
		<text>(Hacking) Reprogram the machine to spread lies about your location.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Rebels and Duskbringers have worked together on occasion but wouldn't normally take advice from propaganda like this. Still - the location of your ship is information they wouldn't want to pass up and they wouldn't expect the Duskbringers to have any reason to lie.</text>
			<modifyPursuit amount="-3"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DUSK_IDOL" unique="true">
	<text>You receive a hail from a young Duskbringer soldier. At first you assume he has some sort of threat for you, but instead he seems amazed to be meeting a Multiverse traveler in person. "Woah, you're one of those special timey wimey ships!"</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_DUSK_GENERIC" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Er, yeah.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Wow! Oooh ooh, have you ever been to Earth?! There was this guy... oh here's a picture!" He holds up a small, black and white photograph of a man saluting to a crowd of people. "He's like a hero of mine! I don't know how to say his name in human language, but he was like a famous leader and he almost conquered the world or something! Have you ever met him?"</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Lie and say you have.</text>
				<event load="DUSK_IDOL_LIE"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Tell the truth and say you haven't.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"You haven't? Man... Well, fun chat! Best I kill you now."</text>
					<ship hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_HUMAN">
				<text>(Human Crew) Your human knows who it is.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Your human coughs, and briefly explains that the man in the photo was no hero, and most of the people of Old Earth resented him for years after he died. "O-oh. I assumed he must have been a famous human warrior! I guess in a sense I was right... but not like that. You know so much more than I do! Oh, command will be so mad at me... but I can't pass up this opportunity!"</text>
					<crewMember amount="1" class="zoltan_devotee"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="DUSK_IDOL_LIE">
	<event>
		<text>"Really?! That's amazing! I wish to come with you, I cannot let this opportunity be passed up to meet actual Renegades!"</text>
		<crewMember amount="1" class="zoltan_devotee"/>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>You quickly regret your decision when the Duskbringer asks a series of questions about the man that you have no idea how to answer. Eventually he starts to see through your ruse and orders the ship to attack!</text>
		<ship hostile="true"/>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
		</choice>
	</event>
</eventList>

<!--
		HOSTILE!!!
	Events that always have a fight
-->
<eventList name="HOSTILE_DUSKBRINGER">
	<event load="ENCOUNTER_DUSKBRINGER"/>
	<event load="ENCOUNTER_DUSKBRINGER_STATION"/>
	
	<event load="ENCOUNTER_PIRATE_DUSKBRINGER"/>
	<event load="ENCOUNTER_REBEL_DUSKBRINGER"/>
	
	<event load="DUSK_ROCK_FANATICS"/>
	<event load="DUSK_PIRATE_CAPTURE"/>
</eventList>

<event name="ENCOUNTER_DUSKBRINGER">
	<text load="TEXT_ENCOUNTER_DUSKBRINGER"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_DUSK_FIGHT" hostile="true"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_ENCOUNTER_DUSKBRINGER">
	<text>The Duskbringers are more extreme than the regular Zoltans, if that was even possible. Usually, they prefer to kill on sight, and the ship here attempts to do the same.</text>
	<text>Duskbringers blame the Federation in particular for the Rebellion's uprising. There is already a Duskbringer ship here, and they intend to repay the favor.</text>
	<text>There are many ways to describe the Duskbringers. One such way might be overly agressive space nazis, but you don't have time to fathom more before a ship is attacking!</text>
	<text>A Duskbringer ship is approaching at high speeds. Arm the weapons!</text>
	<text>Duskbringer patrols often scout out the sector to ward off unwanted visitors. One of these patrols has spotted you and moves in to attack.</text>
	<text>"Greedy, corrupt Federation pig! Your presence here violates code protocol-R78-T! Prepare to be erased!" You suspect their fury is due to more than a simple protocol violation, but you have no choice but to fight.</text>
</textList>

<event name="ENCOUNTER_DUSKBRINGER_STATION" unique="true">
	<text load="TEXT_ENCOUNTER_DUSKBRINGER_STATION"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_DUSK_STATION" hostile="true"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_ENCOUNTER_DUSKBRINGER_STATION">
	<text>"Unidentified ship, this system is off-limits for- ah crap, Feds!" The nearby Duskbringer station activates their arsenal, ready to attack.</text>
	<text>The Duskbringers are surprisingly even more cautious of protecting their borders than even the Zoltan. A station built here to ward off ships like yours spots you, and a fight is inevitable.</text>
</textList>

<event name="ENCOUNTER_REBEL_DUSKBRINGER">
	<text load="TEXT_ENCOUNTER_REBEL_DUSKBRINGER"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_REBEL_FIGHT" hostile="true"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_ENCOUNTER_REBEL_DUSKBRINGER">
	<text>A smug Rebel captain hails you. "Do you need further proof that your Federation is corrupt, when your existence doesn't fuel just one, but two Rebellions?"</text>
	<text>The Rebels and Duskbringers have a strange relationship. Though it would be a lie to say they like each other, the two have a weak bond over their hatred of the Federation. The Rebel ship at this beacon wastes no time proving that this hatred has yet to die down.</text>
	<text>Though this is not their territory, Rebel forces are not all too uncommon in Duskbringer sectors. It appears you have encountered one of their ships.</text>
	<text>"Blegh, can't say I'm a fan of these Zoltan idiots either. Buncha' mini space-nazis or something. Anyways, time to die!"</text>
	<text>You're hailed by the Rebel ship at this beacon. "Well, aren't you just so brave, coming here? I wondered if I would see you here, considering how much you love killing your enemies. Funny, because I just happen to love doing the exact same thing!"</text>
</textList>

<event name="ENCOUNTER_PIRATE_DUSKBRINGER">
	<text load="TEXT_ENCOUNTER_PIRATE_DUSKBRINGER"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_PIRATE_ALL" hostile="true"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_ENCOUNTER_PIRATE_DUSKBRINGER">
	<text>A pirate hiding from the Duskbringers already occupies this beacon. They seem confident in taking on your ship, and attack!</text>
	<text>You pick up a frequency between two pirate ships. "Yeah, these damn Zoltan bastards -- no, everything is still going as planned -- ah crap, Federation!" It appears they've noticed you. One of the ships escapes, but the other attacks!</text>
	<text>Despite trying desperately to keep pirate forces at bay, there's a considerable amount of underground black markets and slave trades held in Duskbringer sectors. Why the pirates do this, whether to rub their superiority in the Zoltan's faces or some other alterior motive doesn't matter, because one such ship is barreling down on you!</text>
	<text>"A Fed? In this sector? How curious. You should have stayed away, amigo. You might think the Dusks are the biggest threat here, but you're wrong. We pirates own this sector!"</text>
	<text>"Damn it, Federation too? Why can't we just catch a break!" The pirates at this beacon don't seem pleased at your presence. Prepare for battle.</text>
</textList>

<event name="DUSK_ROCK_FANATICS" unique="true">
    <text>The Rockmen have always had a fascination with Zoltan culture, so it's not too far of a stretch for some to align with Duskbringer views. The Rock ship here clearly takes its devotion to the Duskbringer cause seriously, and is eager to take you down.</text>
    <ship load="SHIP_ROCK_DUSKBRINGER" hostile="true"/>
    <choice hidden="true">
        <text>Continue...</text>
        <event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
    </choice>
</event>
<event name="FANATICS_AUG">
    <event/>
</event>

<event name="DUSK_PIRATE_CAPTURE" unique="true">
	<text>Two ships inhabit this beacon, a Duskbringer and a Pirate. You notice something isn't right, the two aren't attacking. Then you realise that the Duskbringer ship is empty, and the original crew is aboard the pirate ship. You catch their chatter on the comms. "Damn it! - Federation ship, no time to get back - we'll have to fight them from in here!"</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_DUSK_PIRATE_CAPTURE" hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
		BOARDERS!!!
	Events that always have boarders
-->
<eventList name="BOARDERS_DUSKBRINGER">
	<event load="BOARDERS_DUSKBRINGER_CAPTURE"/>
</eventList>

<event name="BOARDERS_DUSKBRINGER_CAPTURE" unique="true">
	<text>Your comms go to static temporarily and your sensors blank out. You barely catch the warning for boarders before your screen goes black!</text>
	<boarders min="2" max="3" class="zoltan"/>
	<status type="limit" target="player" system="sensors" amount="0"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="ANTI_VIRUS">
		<text>(Anti-Virus) Restore your sensors.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Your sensors system is restored to full power.</text>
			<status type="clear" target="player" system="sensors" amount="100"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
		NEUTRAL!!!
	Events that could have a fight
-->
<eventList name="NEUTRAL_DUSKBRINGER">
	<event load="DUSK_TEAMUP"/>
	<event load="DUSK_ZOLTAN_UNSURE"/>
	<event load="DUSK_PIRATES_HIDING"/>
	<event load="DUSK_IDIOT"/>
	<event load="DUSK_MONASTERY"/>
	
	<event load="ZOLTAN_SCIENCE_DOCK"/>
	<event load="SLAVER_BETRAYAL"/>
	<event load="PIRATE_BRIBER"/>
	<event load="ASTEROID_EXPLORE"/>	
</eventList>

<event name="DUSK_TEAMUP" unique="true">
	<text>You hardly have time to recollect yourself after the light speed jump because the area around this beacon is in total chaos. A Duskbringer, Elite Rebel, Rock, and Zoltan ship are in the midsts of a dogfight.</text>
	<choice>
		<text>Fight the Elite Rebel ship.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Shots come in from all sides as you join the chaotic brawl, heading straight for the Rebels.</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_REBEL_TEAMUP" hostile="true"/>
			<environment type="PDS" target="all"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Fight the Duskbringer ship.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Shots come in from all sides as you join the chaotic brawl, heading straight for the Duskbringers.</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_DUSKBRINGER_TEAMUP" hostile="true"/>
			<environment type="PDS" target="all"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Fight the Zoltan ship.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Shots come in from all sides as you join the chaotic brawl, heading straight for the Zoltan.</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_ZOLTAN_TEAMUP" hostile="true"/>
			<environment type="PDS" target="all"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="MORALITY_UPDATE_ZOLTAN_FIGHT"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Fight the Rock ship.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Shots come in from all sides as you join the chaotic brawl, heading straight for the Rockmen.</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_ROCK_TEAMUP" hostile="true"/>
			<environment type="PDS" target="all"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Get the hell out of here.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You jump away as fast as possible. You catch the Rockmen yelling "Cowards!" over your comms, but eventually you're far away enough that they can't reach you.</text>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="DUSK_TEAMUP_REBEL">
	<text>As you stand victorious over the defeated Rebel ship, the other ships cease their attack. The Duskbringer escapes while it still can, but the Zoltan and Rock ships thank you. The Zoltan works to repair your hull while the Rock gifts you some ammunition.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<damage amount="-7"/>
	<item_modify>
		<item type="missiles" min="3" max="5"/>
	</item_modify>
</event>
<event name="DUSK_TEAMUP_DUSK">
	<text>The Dusk ship is destroyed, leaving the Rebel without an ally. Despite being better equipped than any of your ships individually, they are no match against the three of you. They surrender and jump away. The Zoltans and Rockmen thank you for your help, and work together to repair your hull.</text>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
	<damage amount="-5"/>
</event>
<event name="DUSK_TEAMUP_ZOLTAN">
	<text>You have defeated the Zoltan, leaving the Rockmen without an ally. They abandon all hope and take a kamikaze run straight into the Duskbringer ship, destroying both almost instantly. The last survivor, the Rebel ship, hails you. "Alright, now this is interesting. I suppose I should report your locations to my fleet, but truth be told I don't think I woulda made it outta that one without your help. Tell you what, I'm gonna tell the Fleet your location alright, but it won't be very accurate. In fact, it'll probably lead 'em in circles for a few jumps." You're surprised at the Rebel's willingness to help, but gladly accept it.</text>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
	<modifyPursuit amount="-1"/>
</event>
<event name="DUSK_TEAMUP_ROCK">
    <text>The Rock ship explodes, whether it was from the damage caused in the fight or a last ditch suicide attempt. Your ship is unharmed but a portion of the debris is sent flying into the Zoltan, crippling their shields. The Duskbringer quickly dispatches the ship. You're now outnumbered, and suspect the worst, but the other two ships make no move to attack. The Duskbringer jumps away, unninterested in salvaging any of the wrecks. The Rebel hails you. "Alright, now this is interesting. I suppose I should report your locations to my fleet, but truth be told I don't think I woulda made it outta that one without your help. Tell you what, I'm gonna tell the Fleet your location alright, but it won't be very accurate. In fact, it'll probably lead 'em in circles for a few jumps." You're surprised at the Rebel's willingness to help, but gladly accept it.</text>
    <autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
    <modifyPursuit amount="-1"/>
</event>

<event name="DUSK_ZOLTAN_UNSURE" unique="true">
    <text>You are hailed by a Zoltan ship. Their captain speaks in an unsure tone: "Federation... You have caused this war to escalate far further than you ever expected. It no longer affects just you, but the other races of the galaxy as well. We request that you suggest a way to quell the Duskbringer's anger."</text>
    <ship load="SHIP_ZOLTAN_FIGHT" hostile="false"/> 
    <choice>
        <text>Give them your flight plans, knowing it will most likely end up in Rebel hands.</text>
        <event>
            <text>The Duskbringers and Rebels have been known to share information about the Federation with each other, and you suspect this will only speed up the fleet. Still, you hand the information over to the Zoltan ship, who seems satisfied.</text>
            <modifyPursuit amount="1"/>
        </event>
    </choice>
    <choice>
        <text>Donate some scrap to help the Zoltans.</text>
        <event>
            <text>Parting with your precious scrap is not easy, but you know it will help the Zoltans at the very least to a small extent.</text>
            <item_modify>
                <item type="scrap" min="-25" max="-25"/>
            </item_modify>
        </event>
    </choice>
    <choice req="LIST_CREW_ZOLTAN">
        <text>(Zoltan Crew) Preach to the Zoltans and convince them you know the ways of peace.</text>
        <event>
            <text>Your Zoltan launches into a long, incredibly boring lecture about nonviolence and pacifist ideals. Though it almost puts you into a coma from boredom, it appears to have emotionally moved the crew of the other Zoltan ship. Thoroughly convinced you are different from the other militarized Federation ships, they let you pass.</text>
        </event>
    </choice>
   <!-- <choice req="mind">
        <text>(Mind Control) "Convince" the Zoltans to let you pass.</text>
        <event>
            <text>The Mind Control works wonders on the Zoltans, and they believe every word you tell them. They "willingly" let you pass.</text>
        </event>
    </choice> -->
    <choice hidden="true">
        <text>Dealing with the Dusks is not our problem.</text>
        <event>
            <text>"I was suspecting you might say that. I'm afraid we cannot simply let you continue to destroy our ways of life by growing the divide in our government even wider."</text>
            <ship hostile="true"/>
            <choice hidden="true">
                <text>Continue...</text>
                <event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
            </choice>
        </event>
    </choice>
</event>

<event name="DUSK_PIRATES_HIDING" unique="true">
	<text>A group of pirates has taken refuge from the seemingly endless Duskbringer Patrols in the shadow of a small moon. You doubt they can see you.</text>
	<img planet="PLANET_UNPOPULATED_SMALL"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Contact the pirates.</text>
		<event load="DUSK_PIRATES_HIDING_CONTACT"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore them.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The pirates don't move from their hiding place. You figure it's safe to do something else, but keep an eye on them just in case.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="DUSK_PIRATES_HIDING_CONTACT">
	<event>
		<text>The rest of the pirates flee, scattering away in different directions as soon as they spot you, but one particularly irate pirate hails you. "A Fed? Get lost! It's hard enough survivin' out here with them explosive nazi freaks, I don't need to deal with you too!"</text>
		<ship load="SHIP_PIRATE_ALL" hostile="true"/>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
		</choice>
	</event> 
	<event>
		<text>Surpisingly, none of the pirates move as you approach. One hails you, demanding to know your intentions.</text>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Attack!</text>
			<event>
				<text>Most of the pirates flee, not wanting to take on a full sized cruiser. One however stays behind, confident in their ability to destroy you.</text>
				<ship load="SHIP_PIRATE_ALL" hostile="true"/>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
				</choice>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Offer to trade.</text>
			<event>
				<text>The pirates whisper amongst each other. You wait for a while and begin to consider leaving before the one who you assume is their leader speaks up. "Alright, we have thought long and hard about it. A little trade doesn't hurt, but the minute we suspect you of anything shifty, we'll blow you to smitherens." You consider it ironic for this to be coming from pirates, but you agree to their terms.</text>
				<store>STORE_PIRATE</store>
			</event>
		</choice>
	</event> 
</eventList>

<event name="DUSK_IDIOT" unique="true">
	<text>A Duskbringer ship nearby hails you. A scrawny Zoltan appears, though he is facing the wrong way. He realizes his mistake and turns around, but he's already come across as an idiot. "Federation ships are not welcome here! You are violating protocol... uh... well you're violating one of them. You are a Federation ship, right?"</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_DUSK_GENERIC" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Yes.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Great! This is my chance to prove myself after my last mistake! Devorak will be so happy!" He powers up his weapons and attacks.</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>No.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Oh, my bad sir. Have a wonderful day!" He ends comms, and jumps away. You suspect there might be some sort of trick, but nothing happens. What a moron.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DUSK_MONASTERY" unique="true">
	<text>Though Zoltan Monasteries are usually constructed on the surface of planets, some, like the one at this beacon, are built on large space stations. Unfortunately, this makes them prime targets for hostiles. A pirate group has taken the monastery hostage, and a Duskbringer squadron is trying to negotiate their release.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Help the pirates keep control of the station and fight back the Duskbringers.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Your intervention appears to spark chaos, and soon both pirates and Duskbringers are swarming at each other. You take on the nearest ship.</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_DUSK_MONASTERY" hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Help the Duskbringers retake the Monastery from the pirates.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You swoop into the scene, weapons blasting at the nearest pirate ship. The Duskbringers are confused but realize there's no option but to fight, and soon both sides are engulfed in combat.</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_PIRATE_MONASTERY" hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Don't get involved.</text>
		<event>
			<text>No need to get involved in things like this, especially when neither side is your friend. You slip away unnoticed.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="DUSK_MONASTERY_PIRATE_WIN">
	<text>The presumed leader of the pirates hails you. "Hah! That was one hell of a performance. You have my thanks and my respects, captain. So, waddya want?"</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Release the monks.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"What? You gotta be kidding me. How're we gonna make a profit then?" You propose to them that they could sell the holy artifacts on the black market. "Yeah... alright. Shoulda known you'd go with the sissy option. I'll let the freakos go." The pirates release the monks. With nowhere for them to go, you offer to drop them off at the next holy place you encounter. Most agree, but one of the younger monks requests to join your crew.</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="zoltan_monk"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>We want some of the monk's valuables.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Yeah, alright. We're gonna keep them religious freakos hostage anyways, negotiate a real hell ova bounty from their government. Have at the spoils of their treasury."</text>
			<autoReward level="RANDOM">standard</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="DUSK_MONASTERY_DUSK_WIN">
	<text>When no Duskbringers attempt to hail you, you reach out to their leader. "Yes... yes. You've made quite the show of dominance, and I don't suppose it was out of kindness. What do you want?"</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Give the Rebels fake information on our location.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"I'm going to be martyred because of this..." Though he's clearly unhappy with your request, the Duskbringer accepts. You can only hope he will really give lies, and not just rat you out.</text>
			<modifyPursuit amount="-1"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>We want military supplies.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Yes, I suppose you do. Don't we all... I was hoping to kill a Fed with this gun, not gift it to one." He reluctantly passes over one of his weapons and some ammunition.</text>
			<autoReward level="LOW">missiles_only</autoReward>
			<weapon name="RANDOM"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
		DISTRESS!!!
	Events that have distress beacons
-->
<eventList name="DISTRESS_DUSKBRINGER">
	<event load="DISTRESS_DUSK_FEDERATION"/>
	<event load="DISTRESS_DUSK_DAMAGEDFLEET"/>

	<event load="DISTRESS_ESCORT_BEACON"/>
	<event load="DISTRESS_TRAP_BEACON"/>
	<event load="DISTRESS_PIRATE_CIVILIAN_BEACON"/>
	<event load="DISTRESS_REBEL_VS_FEDERATION"/> 
</eventList>

<event name="DISTRESS_DUSK_DAMAGEDFLEET" unique="true">
	<text>The distress beacon here is coming from no ordinary ship. In the distance lies an immense Zoltan fleetship, a Dreadnaught from the looks of it. It has received critical damage and a good portion of the ship is completely depressurized.</text>
	<img back="BACK_EVENT_ZOLTFLEET_DAMAGED" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<distressBeacon/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Dock and try to help.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Zoltan captain urgently welcomes you inside the ship's spacious hangar. "Good, reinforcements have arrived. The Zoltan Minister dispatched a few small fleets to the Duskbringer sectors to make sure they were kept under control. We hadn't realized how strong they had grown, and they destroyed our fleet with alarming efficiency. We're the only ship left, and that won't last long if we don't make repairs. Our medical and life support systems were damaged heavily but not completely destroyed. There's still hope to fix them, but the path to get to them is completely oxygenless and possibly still has hostiles roaming around."</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Send some crew to repair the life support.</text>
				<event load="DISTRESS_DUSK_DAMAGEDFLEET_DISPATCH"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="BLUELIST_CREW_NO2">
				<text>(Anaerobic Crew) Send your crew to repair the life support.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Without a need for oxygen, your crew doesn't struggle at all with repairing the systems. Once the oxygen levels are stable enough, the remaining Zoltan crew seek out any Duskbringers who may be onboard and dispose of them. Once all is clear the Zoltan captain thanks you for your assistance and pays you a large reward.</text>
					<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>We can't help with repairs, but we can take as many crew as possible in our cargo.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"It's a less than optimal option, but it may be our only choice." The Zoltans hurry onboard. Most are dropped off at the nearby station, but the captain stays behind. "You've done us a great service today, and it would be a shame not to repay it. I have failed my duty in this sector, but perhaps I can help you achieve yours."</text>
					<crewMember amount="1" class="zoltan"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore the fleet ship.</text>
		<event>
			<text>A ship of such size doesn't come to hostile territory such as this without being accompanied by at least a small fleet. Reinforcements will likely arrive soon.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="DISTRESS_DUSK_DAMAGEDFLEET_DISPATCH">
	<event>
		<text>Your team returns, happy to report their mission was a success. Once the oxygen levels are stable enough, the remaining Zoltan crew seek out any Duskbringers who may be onboard and dispose of them. Once all is clear the Zoltan captain thanks you for your assistance and pays you a large reward.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">weapon</autoReward>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>Most of your crew return unharmed, but one did not make it. They report that they ran into Duskbringers on the way and were caught in a firefight. You apologize to the Zoltans for your failure, but there's nothing else you can do.</text>
		<removeCrew>
			<clone>true</clone>
			<text>Luckily your crew was able to be cloned.</text>
		</removeCrew>
	</event>
</eventList>

<event name="DISTRESS_DUSK_FEDERATION" unique="true">
	<text>A marooned Federation ship, with a nasty hole in their engines, appears to be the source of the distress beacon. "Oh, thank god someone came. We were afraid help would never arrive before a Duskbringer patrol alerted the fleet of our position. Please, can you do something about the damage, or lend some fuel? We're leaking fuel badly, but if we have just a little bit we might be able to make it to a store."</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_FED_GENERIC" hostile="false"/>
	<distressBeacon/>
	<choice>
		<text>Give them some fuel.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Thank you, captain. Hopefully it won't all leak out before we get there."</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="fuel" min="-2" max="-3"/>
			</item_modify>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Here, have this as thanks. We were going to sell this to buy more fuel anyways."</text>
					<augment name="RANDOM"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice req="BLUELIST_DRONES_REPAIR_ALL">
		<text>(Repair Drone) Use the drone to repair their engines.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The drone works perfectly, sealing up the breach.</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="drones" min="-1" max="-1"/>
			</item_modify>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Here, have this as thanks. We were going to sell this to buy more fuel anyways."</text>
					<augment name="RANDOM"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice req="BLUELIST_BOMB_REPAIR">
		<text>(Repair Bomb) Use the bomb to repair their engines.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The bomb works perfectly, sealing up the breach.</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="missiles" min="-1" max="-1"/>
			</item_modify>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Here, have this as thanks. We were going to sell this to buy more fuel anyways."</text>
					<augment name="RANDOM"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice req="COMBAT_REPAIR">
		<text>(Repair bots) Release the nanobots to repair their engines.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The nanobots make quick work, sealing up the breach. It doesn't take long before you can hardly make out the area of damage.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Here, have this as thanks. We were going to sell this to buy more fuel anyways."</text>
					<augment name="RANDOM"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>We cannot help.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"So, you're just going to leave us here?" The Federation captain calms himself before speaking again. "Ok. I understand. Best of luck with your mission, captain." He ends the transmission.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
		QUESTS!!!
	Events that have quests
-->
<eventList name="QUESTS_DUSKBRINGER">
	<event load="ZOLTAN_TRADE_HUB"/>
	
	<event load="QUEST_FEDERATION_PLANET_SIGNAL"/>
	<event load="QUEST_MANTIS_INVASION_START"/>
	<event load="QUEST_CREWDEAD_START"/>
</eventList>

<!--
		NEBULA!!!
	Events with unique environments
-->
<eventList name="NEBULA_DUSKBRINGER">
	<event load="NEBULA_ENCOUNTER_DUSKBRINGER"/>
	
	<event load="NEBULA_ZOLTAN_ROCK"/>
	<event load="STORM_ZOLTAN_SUPPLY_CHOICE"/>
	
	<event load="NEBULA_FEDERATION_GIFT"/>
	<event load="NEBULA_SIGNAL"/>
	<event load="NEBULA_DUEL"/>
	<event load="NEBULA_MINE_WRECK"/>
	<event load="NEBULA_WHALE"/>
	
	<event load="NEBULA_NOTHING"/>
	<event load="NEBULA_NOTHING"/>
	<event load="NEBULA_ENCOUNTER_REBEL"/>
</eventList>

<event name="NEBULA_ENCOUNTER_DUSKBRINGER">
	<text load="TEXT_ENCOUNTER_DUSKBRINGER"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_DUSK_FIGHT" hostile="true"/> 
	<environment type="nebula"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					DUSKBRINGER SECTOR 
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->

<event name="DUSKCAP_CLONECANNON" unique="true">
	<text>You've seen a lot of strange sights in your journeys as a Multiverse Renegade, but you don't think you've ever seen a gun like the one strapped to the nearby Auto-ship. At the back is what looks to be a... Clone Bay?</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_DUSK_AUTOCLONER" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Approach the ship and attempt to dismount the weapon.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You approach the ship only for it to activate, and the weapon powers on. A Duskbringer, clad in their usual armor, peeks out from the gun before hurtling harmlessly past your ship and exploding into the vacuum of space. A few seconds later, and the same Zoltan pops out of the gun again. Weird...</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>We can't risk it.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Tempting as it is, there's no way you could retrieve anything from the Auto-ship without alerting it. You leave the ship behind.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="DUSKCAP_CLONECANNON_ESCAPING">
	<text>The Auto-ship's engines activate, and the ship flicks into reverse. They're trying to get away!</text>
</event>
<event name="DUSKCAP_CLONECANNON_GOTAWAY">
	<text>The bizarre ship jumps away, leaving you behind at the beacon.</text>
</event>
<event name="DUSKCAP_CLONECANNON_DEFEAT">
	<text>The automated vessel explodes, sending debris scattering for you to collect.</text>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Search the wreckage.</text>
		<event>
			<text>To your surprise, the strange weapon from the wreckage has survived. You bring it aboard only to find the Duskbringer aboard still alive, perpetually cloned by the machine. He remembers little about his life because of the constant cloning, so he identifies himself simply as "projectile". He has nothing left but this gun, and so he asks that, should you keep him around, you continue to use him as his name suggests.</text>
			<weapon name="CLONE_CANNON"/>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="zoltan_devotee">Projectile</crewMember>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
		UNIQUE!!!
	Events that give stuff
-->
<eventList name="UNIQUE_DUSKCAP">
	<event load="DUSKCAP_DNA"/>
	<!--<event load="DUSKCAP_PRISONERS"/>-->
	<event load="DUSKCAP_PISSED"/>
</eventList>

<event name="DUSKCAP_PISSED" unique="true">
	<text>A small fleet of Duskbringer ships has blockaded this beacon. You attempt to sneak past but a squadron of Duskbringer ships fly down to stop you. You assume a fight is imminent, but instead you receive a hail. "A Federation ship? It's unorthodox, but I have a favor to ask of you..."</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>You are greeted into a large meeting room furnished very strangely. Antique maps and weaponry line the walls, and a Duskbringer Martyr sits on a leather armchair sipping from a cup of tea. "Yes, hello. I know our political alignments have made us enemies, but today I think we can reach a mutually beneficial agreement. As you have surely noticed, the Rebels are quite the issue for us since Vance ordered them to betray our pact. Now, my men and I have been assigned to keeping this... filth out of our sector. There is a particularly slippery and obnoxious Rebel commander around these parts who has been giving me trouble. Give me your service and kill him, and I will give you mine in return. Is this a fair deal?"</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Accept.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Most excellent. Here are the co-ordinates of this nitwitted loon. I believe he goes by the title... ahem... 'Commander Kyle 'Kick your Ass'. Ugh, how distastesful..."</text>
					<quest event="DUSKCAP_PISSED_QUEST"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Decline.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"A pity. Alright men, you know how to handle this one." The Duskbringer soldiers grab their weapons and chase you off the ship. An elite vessel is dispatched to destroy you.</text>
					<ship load="SHIP_DUSK_ELITE_FIGHT" hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="DUSKCAP_PISSED_QUEST">
    <text>You've arrived at the destination specified by the Duskbringers. Indeed, a massive Rebel ship is attacking a small Zoltan settlement, of which you aren't even sure belongs to the Duskbringers.</text>
    <ship load="SHIP_KYLE_PICKET" hostile="false"/>
    <choice hidden="true">
        <text>Hail the Rebels.</text>
        <event>
            <text>"NOW WHO MIGHT THIS BE?! A FEDERATION SHIP, AHAH! DO YOU KNOW WHO I AM? I AM KICK YOUR ASS KYLE, AND I BET YOU CAN GUESS WHAT I'M GOING TO DO TO YOU!" He pauses for a moment. "IN CASE YOU'RE STUPID, I'LL EXPLAIN IT. I'M GOING TO KICK-" You mute him while you decide what to do.</text>
            <choice hidden="true">
                <text>Shoot him dead.</text>
                <event>
                    <text>You briefly unmute Kyle, but after a long string of explicit insults you mute him for the remainder of the fight and prepare to attack.</text>
                    <ship hostile="true"/>
                    <choice hidden="true">
                        <text>Continue...</text>
                        <event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
                    </choice>
                </event>
            </choice>
            <choice hidden="true">
                <text>He doesn't deserve our time. Leave him for the Dusks to handle.</text>
                <event>
                    <text>You switch the engines into reverse and fly away from the Rebel ship. Why is it you who always gets the weird jobs?</text>
                </event>
            </choice>
        </event>
    </choice>
</event>
<event name="DUSKCAP_PISSED_DEFEAT">
	<text>The Rebel ship has been neutralized. You scrap the remains of what was once Kyle's ship.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>While scrapping the Rebel ship, you notice a small pod eject from the vessel. Due to being on a different comm system, you have not yet muted it. Kyle appears on the screen, his over-sized melon of a face red and sweaty. "YOU HAVEN'T HEARD THE LAST OF ME, YOU FEDERATION DIPSH-" Kyle doesn't get to finish this last insult before a Duskbringer carrier jumps into the system and annihilates the pod in a single shot.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event>
					<text>You receive a hail from the same Duskbringer as before. "Very good. It is most unfortunate I did not arrive earlier to partake in the fight, but I see you did sufficient work, and now this neanderthal is dead. You upheld your job... for the most part... and so I shall uphold mine."</text>
					<crewMember amount="1" class="zoltan_martyr" all_skills="1">Reginald</crewMember>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DUSKCAP_PRISONERS" unique="true">
	<text>A small moon is orbiting an otherwise uninhabited planet. On it looks to be a large high-security prison for POWs. Knowing the Duskbringers, it likely contains a lot of Federation and Ministry personnel.</text>
	<img planet="PLANET_MOONS"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Attack and break out the prisoners!</text>
		<event load="DUSKCAP_PRISONERS_RISKY"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="teleporter">
		<text>(Teleporter) Beam inside unnoticed.</text>
		<event load="DUSKCAP_PRISONERS_SUCCESS"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="cloaking">
		<text>(Cloaking) Cloak and send the crew inside undetected.</text>
		<event load="DUSKCAP_PRISONERS_SUCCESS"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>We can't risk it.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Tempting as it is, there's no way you could pull something like that off. You leave the prison behind.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="DUSKCAP_PRISONERS_RISKY">
	<event>
		<text>You attempt to break into the prison, but things don't go as planned. A defense system blasts a hole in your ship and soldiers beam aboard before you can pull away!</text>
		<damage amount="3"/>
		<boarders min="2" max="2" class="zoltan_devotee"/>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>It's risky, but you manage to brute force your way past the security and make it inside the building.</text>
		<choice hidden="false">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="DUSKCAP_PRISONERS_SUCCESS"/>
		</choice>
	</event>
</eventList>
<event name="DUSKCAP_PRISONERS_SUCCESS">
	<text>Your attempts inside are successful. As expected, there are several prison cages holding a wide variety of prisoners, including Federation, Rebel, Zoltan, and Engi personnel! You'll only have so long until the guards catch you, so who will you save?</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Save one of the Zoltan.</text>
		<event>
			<text>It turns out the prisoner was a Duskbringer who betrayed the cause and was thrown into prison. You break open the cage and free them, but an alarm sirens and you can hear Duskbringers marching towards your location. There's no time for introductions, you have to get out of here fast!</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="zoltan_devotee"/>
			<choice>
				<text>Leave!</text>
				<event load="DUSKCAP_PRISONERS_LEAVE"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Save one of the Engi.</text>
		<event>
			<text>It turns out the Engi was working aboard a Ministry vessel before it was taken hostage. You break open the cage and free the prisoner inside, but an alarm sirens and you can hear Duskbringers marching towards your location. There's no time for introductions, you have to get out of here fast!</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="engi"/>
			<choice>
				<text>Leave!</text>
				<event load="DUSKCAP_PRISONERS_LEAVE"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Save one of the Medics.</text>
		<event>
			<text>It turns out the Medic was staff on a Federation support ship that was captured by the Duskbringers. You break open the cage and free the prisoner inside, but an alarm sirens and you can hear Duskbringers marching towards your location. There's no time for introductions, you have to get out of here fast!</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="human_medic"/>
			<choice>
				<text>Leave!</text>
				<event load="DUSKCAP_PRISONERS_LEAVE"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Save one of the Engineers.</text>
		<event>
			<text>It turns out the Engineer was a Rebel deserter who ended up in Duskbringer space and was captured. You break open the cage and free the prisoner inside, but an alarm sirens and you can hear Duskbringers marching towards your location. There's no time for introductions, you have to get out of here fast!</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="human_engineer"/>
			<choice>
				<text>Leave!</text>
				<event load="DUSKCAP_PRISONERS_LEAVE"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="DUSKCAP_PRISONERS_LEAVE" unique="true">
	<text>As you're leaving the prison behind, a Dusk ship swoops in. It's an elite Jailer, and they aren't pleased. Prepare for combat!</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_DUSK_ELITE_JAILER" hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DUSKCAP_DNA" unique="true">
	<text>On the distant but visibly populated planet you can make out some kind of massive Duskbringer structure, heavily fortified and partially concealed by a forest. Scans show large amounts of power being drawn into the facility.</text>
	<img planet="PLANET_POPULATED"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Land and investigate.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You pilot down to the surface, making sure you aren't spotted, and hide in a thick patch of trees. Your crew continue on foot until they reach the entrance of the structure, protected by 2 heavily armed Duskbringer soldiers.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Shoot your way through!</text>
				<event load="DUSKCAP_DNA_BREAKIN"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Too risky, pull back.</text>
				<event load="DUSKCAP_DNA_RETREAT"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="slug_saboteur">
				<text>(Slug Saboteur) Sneak your way inside.</text>
				<event load="DUSKCAP_DNA_INSIDE"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="zoltan_monk">
				<text>(Monk Crew) Have your monk stun the guards.</text>
				<event load="DUSKCAP_DNA_INSIDE"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_DUSK">
				<text>(Duskbringer Crew) Talk your way past the guards.</text>
				<event load="DUSKCAP_DNA_INSIDE"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore the facility.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You're on no suicide mission, and dropping by a Duskbringer megastructure isn't on your to-do list. You fly past the planet.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="DUSKCAP_DNA_BREAKIN">
	<event>
		<text>You underestimate the Duskbringer guards, thinking you can quickly take them out. However, they're quick to the draw and one of your crew falls to the ground, injured. Fortunately, you're able to silently subdue them before anyone else can get hurt.</text>
		<removeCrew>
			<clone>true</clone>
			<text>Fortunately, your crew is revived back at the ship and hurries back to meet up with you.</text>
		</removeCrew>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="DUSKCAP_DNA_INSIDE"/>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>Your crew manage to subdue the Duskbringer soldiers silently. You proceed into the building...</text>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="DUSKCAP_DNA_INSIDE"/>
		</choice>
	</event>
</eventList>
<eventList name="DUSKCAP_DNA_RETREAT">
	<event>
		<text>This may go down as the quickest reconsideration in Federation history, but it's better safe than sorry.</text>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>You order the crew back to the ship, only to find a Duskbringer patrol ship surveying it! Looks like you'll have to take care of these guys before you can leave.</text>
		<ship load="SHIP_DUSK_FIGHT" hostile="true"/>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
		</choice>
	</event>
</eventList>
<event name="DUSKCAP_DNA_INSIDE">
	<text>You proceed into the facility, and are surprised to find rows and rows of what appear to be... test tubes? Each has a small digital label on it denoting them to different serial numbers.</text>
	<choice>
		<text>Continue.</text>
		<event>
			<text>It takes some time looking through the machinery to realize this must be some sort of massive DNA bank! You could likely dismantle some of this tech and bring it back with you, or quickly try to clone one of the Duskbringer soldiers and convince them to work for you.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Grab the Cloning tech. [Backup DNA and 1 free cloning upgrade, if you have the system]</text>
				<event>
					<text>You dismantle some of the cloning tech and bring it back to the ship.</text>
					<augment name="EX_BACKUP_DNA"/>
					<upgrade amount="1" system="clonebay"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="DUSKCAP_DNA_FIGHT"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Clone a Duskbringer Martyr.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You quickly grab a random vial for a Duskbringer Martyr and make sure to wipe all personal memories but not skills or training. Once your new crew is birthed from the machine, utterly confused on their whereabouts, you inform them about the Federation that they now serve and prepare to leave.</text>
					<crewMember amount="1" class="zoltan_martyr"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="DUSKCAP_DNA_FIGHT"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="DUSKCAP_DNA_FIGHT">
	<text>As you leave the facility, an elite Duskbringer vessel approaches you, and an alarm sounds. Looks like you weren't as unnoticed as you thought!</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_DUSK_ELITE_FIGHT" hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
		ITEMS!!!
	Events that give stuff
-->
<eventList name="ITEMS_DUSKCAP">
	<event load="DUSK_MILITIA_ESCORT"/>
	<event load="DUSK_PROPOGANDA"/>
	<event load="DUSK_SLAVER_TRADE"/>
	<event load="DUSK_IDOL"/>
</eventList>

<!--
		HOSTILE!!!
	Events that always have a fight
-->
<eventList name="HOSTILE_DUSKCAP">
	<event load="ENCOUNTER_DUSKBRINGER"/>
	<event load="ENCOUNTER_DUSKBRINGER_STATION"/>
	<event load="ENCOUNTER_DUSKBRINGER_ELITE"/>
	
	<event load="ENCOUNTER_REBEL_DUSKBRINGER_CAPITOL"/>
	<event load="ENCOUNTER_PIRATE_DUSKBRINGER"/>
	<event load="DUSK_ROCK_FANATICS"/>
	<event load="DUSK_PIRATE_CAPTURE"/>
</eventList>

<event name="ENCOUNTER_DUSKBRINGER_ELITE" unique="true">
	<text>The Duskbringer Extremists are only the most devoted members of the Duskbringer organization. Nothing will stop them from bringing down the Federation, not even death. An extremist ship swoops in, guns blazing and ready to destroy you. Looks like you'll have to do the same.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_DUSK_ELITE_FIGHT" hostile="true"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="ENCOUNTER_REBEL_DUSKBRINGER_CAPITOL">
	<text load="TEXT_ENCOUNTER_REBEL_DUSKBRINGER_CAPITOL"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_REBEL_FIGHT" hostile="true"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_ENCOUNTER_REBEL_DUSKBRINGER_CAPITOL">
	<text>The Rebel invasion of this sector is bad news for not just the Duskbringers, but you as well. A Rebel forward scout locks onto your location and attacks.</text>
	<text>"Well, ain't this a nice turn of events. I expected to be stuck fighting Zoltans this entire invasion, but now a Fed shows up? My lucky day!"</text>
	<text>A Rebel thirsting for blood is a threat you'd like to avoid, but unfortunately this encounter hasn't given you an option. A hostile Rebel ship approaches!</text>
	
	<!--below are ones from the normal Dusk rebel encounter-->
	<text>A smug Rebel captain hails you. "Do you need further proof that your Federation is corrupt, when your existence doesn't fuel just one, but two Rebellions?"</text>
	<text>"Blegh, can't say I'm a fan of these Zoltan idiots either. Buncha' mini space-nazis or something. Anyways, time to die!"</text>
	<text>You're hailed by the Rebel ship at this beacon. "Well, aren't you just so brave, coming here? I wondered if I would see you here, considering how much you love killing your enemies. Funny, because I just happen to love doing the exact same thing!"</text>
</textList>

<!--
		NEUTRAL!!!
	Events that could have a fight
-->
<eventList name="NEUTRAL_DUSKCAP">
	<event load="DUSK_TEAMUP"/>
	<event load="DUSK_ZOLTAN_UNSURE"/>
	<event load="DUSK_PIRATES_HIDING"/>
	<event load="DUSK_IDIOT"/>
	<event load="DUSK_MONASTERY"/>
	
	<event load="CAPITAL_DEBATE"/>
	<event load="DUSK_JAILER_CHOICE"/>
</eventList>

<event name="DUSK_JAILER_CHOICE" unique="true">
	<text>The Duskbringers are no fans of intruders in their territory, and so it is not uncommon to see Jailer vessels patrolling the area to transport prisoners. One such ship has made a quick pit-stop here and is re-calibrating their sensors.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_DUSK_JAILER" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Attack while they're distracted!</text>
		<event>
			<text>You move in to destroy the Jailer, knowing that you'll have to kill their crew if you want the prisoners to live.</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="FIREARMS_AND_TELEPORT">
		<text>(Armories + Teleporter) Storm the Jailer.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Your crew, armed to the teeth, board the Jailer and quickly take down the Duskbringer crew staffing it. With the jailers turned prisoners, you free everyone locked up who you don't think will kill you immediately.</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="LIST_CREW_FEDERATION"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Avoid the Jailer.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Jailer doesn't seem to notice as you slip away.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="DUSK_JAILER_KILL">
	<text>You've destroyed the Jailer, but unfortunately none of the captives survived the explosion. You scrap the remains and try to avoid the drifting corpses.</text> 
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<event name="DUSK_JAILER_CAPTURE">
	<text>The Jailer's crew is dead but most of the captives survived the fight. Most of them request to be dropped off as soon as you're out of the Capitol, but one volunteers to stay behind and work aboard your ship.</text> 
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
	<crewMember amount="1"/>
</event>

<eventList name="DISTRESS_DUSKBRINGER">
	<event load="DISTRESS_DUSK_FEDERATION"/>
	<event load="DISTRESS_DUSK_DAMAGEDFLEET"/>

	<event load="DISTRESS_ESCORT_BEACON"/>
	<event load="DISTRESS_TRAP_BEACON"/>
	<event load="DISTRESS_PIRATE_CIVILIAN_BEACON"/>
	<event load="DISTRESS_REBEL_VS_FEDERATION"/> 
</eventList>

<!--
		SPECIAL QUEST!!!!!
		SPECIAL QUEST!!!!!
		SPECIAL QUEST!!!!!
-->
<event name="DUSKCAP_CAPITOLRAID" unique="true">
	<preventQuest/>
	<text>You knew the Rebel invasion in this sector was bad, but you didn't expect it to be this extreme. A squadron of MFK Aces are firing on the Duskbringer Capitol, but not without opposition.</text>
	<img back="BACK_EVENT_DUSKCAP" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<customFleet right="false" firing="true" autoDarkening="false">CUSTOM_FLEET_REBEL</customFleet>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Get involved - Help the Duskbringers.</text>
		<event load="DUSKCAP_CAPITOLRAID_DUSK"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Get involved - Help the Rebels.</text>
		<event load="DUSKCAP_CAPITOLRAID_REBEL"/>
	</choice>
	<choice>	
		<text>Too risky, stay away from the fighting.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Neither the Duskbringers nor the Rebels are your allies. You have no reason to get involved.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DUSKCAP_CAPITOLRAID_DUSK" unique="true">
	<text>You pilot toward a platform where several Duskbringer soldiers are under fire from an armored Rebel ground vehicle. However, when the Rebels see your massive cruiser landing, they quickly retreat.</text>
	<choice>	
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>In command of the Dusk battalion is a specially clothed Duskbringer Martyr. Your Federation database detects his identity almost automatically, informing you that he is a famous Zoltan war hero known as Devorak the Deathless. He has been cloned so many times that they say he can no longer feel pain. The Duskbringers are skeptical of your approach and raise their weapons.</text>
			<choice>	
				<text>Explain to them that you wish to help.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Devorak speaks up, stepping forward from the others. "Help? Doubtful, but I'm in no position to argue. That filthy traitorous Vance turned on us and had his men attack the Capitol when we least expected it. If you want to be less than useless, you could take out that cruiser attacking the command tower." He points out a large MFK Ace ship. "Once they are dealt with, we should be able to storm the tower and re-activate the shields and defense systems."</text>
					<ship load="SHIP_DUSKRAID_REBELBOSS" hostile="false"/>
					<choice hidden="true">	
						<text>Accept and take on the cruiser.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"Don't make me regret this." You power up the weapons and attack the cruiser. The Rebels spot you and engage.</text>
							<ship hostile="true"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">	
						<text>Decline.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Devorak laughs in your face. "As expected. Run along then, you cowardly Fed scum."</text>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="DUSKCAP_CAPITOLRAID_DUSK_WIN" unique="true">
	<text>The MFK Cruiser stood no chance against you. The ship crashes into the base of the tower, scattering debris for you to collect.</text>
	<variable name="ach_boss_mfkcruiser" op="set" val="1"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">	
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Though the Rebel ship has been destroyed, the fleet does not surrender. Devorak and his men attempt to infiltrate it, only for nearly half of the squadron to get massacred by a hacked defense turret.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">	
				<text>Swoop in to assist.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You made a promise to help Devorak and that's a promise you intend to keep. You land the ship down next to him and dismount, firing your blaster at the turret. As you should have expected, it does practically nothing, but you manage to save Devorak and bring him back aboard your ship.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">	
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event>
							<text>In the distance the battle rages on, but Devorak will live. "You... you've saved me. Though this failure does not bode well for the survival of my cause, you have proven your dedication. It is only fair that I accompany you now. But first, stop by that spot." Devorak points roughly to an area on the ground nearby. "There is a secret augment cache here. It should help on your- our mission."</text>
							<unlockCustomShip silent="false">PLAYER_SHIP_DUSKBRINGER</unlockCustomShip>
							<variable name="ach_crew_devorak" op="set" val="1"/>
							<crewMember amount="1" class="unique_devorak" all_skills="2">Devorak</crewMember>
							<augment name="RANDOM"/>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">	
				<text>We've done enough. Retreat now.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You did what you could, but you owe nothing more to the Duskbringers. You abandon Devorak and collect some extra scrap from the wreckage before leaving.</text>
					<autoReward level="HIGH">scrap_only</autoReward>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DUSKCAP_CAPITOLRAID_REBEL" unique="true">
	<text>You navigate towards a small patch of Rebel vessels who are treating injured soldiers and planning out their next move. You nearly get shot out of the air, but you broadcast a surrender signal and are allowed to land.</text>
	<choice>	
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>In the center of the group is General Alban of the Rebel fleet, a slender but well built man with an imposing glare and long face. "You have come to surrender? Make it quick, I am very busy."</text>
			<choice>	
				<text>Explain to them that you wish to help.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Alban laughs for a straight minute, until he realizes you aren't joking. "You're serious? How incredibly stupid! Though... we could use help. We've managed to secure control of the Dusk's command tower and by extension the shield generator for this place, but we haven't been able to do considerable damage yet. Our fleet has been stopped so far by a single Duskbringer cruiser. Take it out for us, and I might be grateful enough to reward you."</text>
					<ship load="SHIP_DUSKRAID_DUSKBOSS" hostile="false"/>
					<choice hidden="true">	
						<text>Accept and take on the cruiser.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Alban merely grunts and waves you on, then goes back to discussing with his fellow Rebels. You head back to the ship and prepare to attack the Duskbringer cruiser.</text>
							<ship hostile="true"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">	
						<text>Decline.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"You Feds are so predictable. Be glad I do not have enough time to arrest you, and leave with haste."</text>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="DUSKCAP_CAPITOLRAID_REBEL_WIN" unique="true">
	<text>The Duskbringer Cruiser stood no chance against you. The ship plummets out of the sky, crashing into the ground. You quickly swoop in to salvage what you can.</text>
	<variable name="ach_boss_duskcruiser" op="set" val="1"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">	
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Without the cruiser to stop them, a swarm of ships enter the system and eradicate the remaining Duskbringer forces. It's terribly lucky you chose to side with the Rebels - otherwise you'd no doubt have been killed as well.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">	
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event>
					<text>You look for Alban again and land. He frowns, "Oh yes, you. You have upheld your word, and to show the Rebels are no cowards I will do the same. I will ensure the fleet does not bother you for a while. You may also help yourself to our left over ammunition and weapon supplies.</text>
					<modifyPursuit amount="-3"/>
					<weapon name="RANDOM"/>
					<autoReward level="MED">missiles</autoReward>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
</FTL>