<FTL>
<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					KNIGHT SECTOR
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					CLEARING EVENTS ()
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<eventList name="CLEARING_KNIGHT">
	<event load="KNIGHT_CALL_CENTER"/>
	<event load="KNIGHT_ORCHID_LOVER"/>
	<event load="KNIGHT_HEKTAR"/>
	<event load="KNIGHT_AMPERE_HOPEFUL"/>
</eventList>

<event name="KNIGHT_CALL_CENTER" unique="true">
    <text>There's a Slug station at this beacon, and a fairly active one at that; you pick up tons of transmissions coming from it. It doesn't seem like they've noticed you yet. You tap into one of the many signals, and luckily, it seems they're all unencrypted.
        
"...yesss ma'am, our ssssoftware will keep your sssstuff safe. You're welcome, ma'am. Now, for payment, we actually only take Tony'ssss giftcardssss - it'ssss much more ssssecure than normal transsssactionsss..."
You swap to another transmission. "...long losssst relative of a prince of a remote ssssysssstem..." a Slug says in what sounds like an attempt at mimicking a Mantis, "and many goodiessss await you! Jusssst need identi-" You've heard enough to get a decent idea of what's going on here.</text>
    <ship load="SHIP_SLUG_CALL" hostile="false"/>
    <choice>
        <text>Blow them up!</text>
        <event>
            <text>You power up your weapons and charge towards the station before they can react.</text>
            <ship hostile="true"/>
            <choice>
                <text>Continue...</text>
                <event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
            </choice>
        </event>
    </choice>
    <choice>
        <text>Approach the station.</text>
        <event>
            <text>You carefully fly closer to the station. It takes little time for them to notice you, and very quickly all the transmissions go quiet. A hail follows after. "Hi, uh, Renegade. We're not up to anything at all. Nope. Not even a little. And even if we hypothetically were, you're not that attached to the Fedssss, right? Not that we are, but you'd let ussss go if we were. Hypothetically. In theory."</text>
            <choice>
                <text>No, we definitely are. Pretty sure scamming is a crime.</text>
                <event>
                    <text>"Aw, ssssshit. Well, in that case..." The station begins charging its weapons. No other option but to engage!</text>
                    <ship hostile="true"/>
                    <choice>
                        <text>Continue...</text>
                        <event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
                    </choice>
                </event>
            </choice>
            <choice>
                <text>Eh, whatever. Sure.</text>
                <event>
                    <text>"Thank god. In an absssstract, theoretical way. Becausssse we're not doing anyth-" These guys aren't fooling anyone, but they aren't your problem to deal with. You cut the comm and prepare to jump away.</text>
                </event>
            </choice>
        </event>
    </choice>
    <choice>
        <text>Who cares about some scammers? Leave.</text>
        <event>
            <text>You prepare to jump away.</text>
            <choice>
                <text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
                <event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
            </choice>
            <choice>
                <text>Do nothing.</text>
                <event/>
            </choice>
        </event>
    </choice>
    <choice req="LIST_CREW_SLUG" hidden="true">
        <text>(Slug Crew) "I have an idea..."</text>
        <event>
            <text>Your Slug directs you to hail the station. The second they connect, they immediately start babbling in a croaky, frail voice. "Issss thissss the technology ssssupport center? My grandsssson found thissss sssship and it keepssss not working..."
			
Another Slug onboard the station responds with poorly concealed glee, apparently not caring that they're scamming one of their own. "Yessss, yesss, it issss. We can help, you jussst need to let ussss interface with your sssship."
			
Your Slug grins at you. "Oh, okay. What'ssss 'interface'?"

Your Slug spends the next while being as dense and obstructive as possible, talking in complete circles and generally being annoying. The scammer lasts for a surprisingly long time, but eventually, after your Slug asks what an engine is for the fifth time, he cracks. There's a banging noise over the comm punctuated by a scream of rage. "Sssstupid little- how isss it posssssible to be too dumb to sssscam? How can you even pilot that thing? AGHHH."</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
                <text>Continue...</text>
				<event>
                    <text>The comm cuts off and your Slug starts howling with laughter. Knowing you've done an incredible service - a.k.a. waste someone's time - you prepare to jump away. Right before you're about to, though, you watch as one of the airlocks on the station opens and a computer comes sailing out, with a schematic saved in it! It's not much, but it's honest work.</text>
					<item_modify>
						<item type="drones" min="1" max="1"/>
					</item_modify>
					<drone name="RANDOM"/>
                </event>
            </choice>
        </event>
    </choice>
</event>

<event name="KNIGHT_ORCHID_LOVER" unique="true">
    <text>There's a Knight ship hanging outside the nebula. Rather than making any motions to attack, the ship seems to ignore you. A private communication comes from within the ship. "You... you are an outssssider. Have you ever heard of the Gathering? I have lived my whole life in thissss nebula, but I have grown tired of thissss place. The latesssst hunt for the crown hassss ssssettled it. I long to go to an arboreal world of lusssh foresstsss and friendly cussstomsss. Get away from thissss sssstresssful life. But... with my reputation assss a Knight of the Crown, I don't think a life outsssside of thissss nebula would ever accept me."</text>
    <ship load="SHIP_KNIGHT" hostile="false"/>
    <choice req="unique_mayeb" hidden="true">
		<text>(Mayeb) Talk about the Gathering.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Mayeb speaks up. "...hello. I am Mayeb, Caretaker of the Gathering. ...It is true that you won't fit in. They will judge you for your past, and for being different. But that does not mean you can't make a life for yourself. If you are not fit for your current position, maybe a life of tending to the plants can be very fulfilling. It is the life I will return to once I am released from my duties. Perhaps we can teach you. Would you like to accompany me?"
			
The Knight's voice is filled with joy. "I will come with you!" Moments later, the Knight appears on your ship.</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="slug_knight">Quan</crewMember>
			<choice>
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event>
					<text>The ship arms weapons and hails you. "Quan?? You are defecting to thissss Renegade'ssss sssship?! Dissssloyal knightssss musssst be sssslain!"</text>
					<ship hostile="true"/>
					<choice>
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
    </choice>
    <choice req="unique_ivar" hidden="true">
		<text>(Ivar) Tell the Knight about the Gathering.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Aye lad! The Gathering is lovely, I support you on your pilgrimage. Though if you ask me, they're a bit too restrained for my tastes. They need to lighten up! I'm always telling them this in my dinner parties."

"Ivar? The Premier of the Oro'Bache?"

Ivar laughs. "That's what the nameplate on my desk says!"

The Knight seems invested. "The rumorssss sssay you are a quarter Ctl'Yae. Issss that true?"

"I got a bit of diversity in my sap, that's true. How about this, next time I have a dinner party, I'll invite you and some of my Floral buddies and we can all have a good time. I'm sure I can turn the ear of your government. Sounds good?"

"Yessss! That ssssoundssss lovely. Thank you. My name is Quan. Pleasssse remember it." Quan presents you with a nice gift of scrap and a weapon.</text>
			<autoReward level="HIGH">scrap_only</autoReward>
			<weapon name="GIFTLIST_KNIGHT"/>
		</event>
    </choice>
    <choice req="unique_tyerel" hidden="true">
		<text>(Ty E'Rel) "I will support your emigration."</text>
		<event>
			<text>"So, you want to move to the Gathering? This is doable. The Gathering would be willing to support an expatriated Knight if you can take a carnivorous pledge and a citizen exam."

The Knight nods fervently. "I've been a carnivore for yearssss. I've alwayssss wanted to be a Ctl'Yae."

Ty nods. "Got it. You would, of course, be subjected to more scrutiny than an Oro'bache might. If you want to pursue that path, I'm certain it would look good if you would join the guard of the Gardenworlds."

The Knight pauses. "If I leave the nebula, there issss no coming back."

Ty E'Rel nods. "If you come with us, I will do everything I can for you." Moments later, the Knight appears on your ship.</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="slug_knight">Quan</crewMember>
			<choice>
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event>
					<text>The ship arms weapons and hails you. "Quan?? You are defecting to thissss Renegade'ssss sssship?! Dissssloyal knightssss musssst be sssslain!"</text>
					<ship hostile="true"/>
					<choice>
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
    </choice>
    <choice req="orchid_praetor" hidden="true">
		<text>(Praetor Crew) Talk about Rt'lak Et.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Your Praetor talks about their time protecting the homelands and about the beautiful gardens that the Caretakers maintain.
			
"Meeting a Praetor issss going to be the highlight of my year. Thank you for your time." The Knight sends you a stockpile of scrap for your time.</text>
			<autoReward level="HIGH">scrap_only</autoReward>
		</event>
    </choice>
    <choice req="orchid_caretaker" hidden="true">
		<text>(Caretaker Crew) Tell the knight about the Gardens.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Your Caretaker begins to talk about their experiences in the gardens caring for the flora of the Gardenworlds. They pore through their personal picture collection and send images to the curious Knight.
			
"Meeting a Caretaker thissss deep in Kleptocracy sssspace... I'm very fortunate. Thank you, I will ussse thesssse picturessss when I am feeling down." The Knight sends a weapon in return.</text>
			<weapon name="GIFTLIST_KNIGHT"/>
		</event>
    </choice>
    <choice req="orchid" hidden="true">
		<text>(Floral Crew) Talk about the Gathering.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Your Orchid is happy to talk about how nice their homeland is, going on about the lush gardens and their friends and family. The Knight seems happy to hear about your Orchid's life. You're rewarded with a modest pile of scrap.</text>
			<autoReward level="MED">scrap_only</autoReward>
		</event>
    </choice>
    <choice req="LIST_CREW_VAMPWEED" hidden="true">
		<text>(Vampweed Crew) Have your Vampweed talk about their experiences.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Your Vampweed begins to talk about their experiences with their floral cousins. The Knight is attentive, but seems vaguely unsatisfied. Nevertheless, you are paid for your time.</text>
			<autoReward level="LOW">scrap_only</autoReward>
		</event>
    </choice>
    <choice req="KERNEL_1">
		<text>Offer the knight a Kernel Burst 1.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"I have alwayssss wanted a Kernel weapon. Maybe when I usssse thissss, I will feel at easssse."</text>
			<remove name="KERNEL_1"/>
			<choice>
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="KNIGHT_KERNEL_PAYMENT_OR_TRADE"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
    </choice>
    <choice req="KERNEL_2">
		<text>Offer the knight a Kernel Burst 2.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"I have alwayssss wanted a Kernel weapon. Maybe when I usssse thissss, I will feel at easssse."</text>
			<remove name="KERNEL_2"/>
			<choice>
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="KNIGHT_KERNEL_PAYMENT_OR_TRADE"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
    </choice>
    <choice req="KERNEL_HEAVY">
		<text>Offer the knight a Heavy Kernel.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"I have alwayssss wanted a Kernel weapon. Maybe when I usssse thissss, I will feel at easssse."</text>
			<remove name="KERNEL_HEAVY"/>
			<choice>
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="KNIGHT_KERNEL_PAYMENT_OR_TRADE"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
    </choice>
    <choice req="KERNEL_FIRE">
		<text>Offer the knight a Fire Kernel.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"I have alwayssss wanted a Kernel weapon. Maybe when I usssse thissss, I will feel at easssse."</text>
			<remove name="KERNEL_FIRE"/>
			<choice>
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="KNIGHT_KERNEL_PAYMENT_OR_TRADE"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
    </choice>
    <choice req="KERNEL_CHAIN">
		<text>Offer the knight a Chain Kernel.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"I have alwayssss wanted a Kernel weapon. Maybe when I usssse thissss, I will feel at easssse."</text>
			<remove name="KERNEL_CHAIN"/>
			<choice>
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="KNIGHT_KERNEL_PAYMENT_OR_TRADE"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
    </choice>
    <choice req="KERNEL_CHARGE">
		<text>Offer the knight a Charge Kernel.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"I have alwayssss wanted a Kernel weapon. Maybe when I usssse thissss, I will feel at easssse."</text>
			<remove name="KERNEL_CHARGE"/>
			<choice>
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="KNIGHT_KERNEL_PAYMENT_OR_TRADE"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
    </choice>
    <choice req="MINELAUNCHER_KERNEL">
		<text>Offer the knight a Kernel Mine Launcher.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"I have alwayssss wanted a Kernel weapon. I've never even heard of a Kernel Mine Launcher! Maybe when I usssse thissss, I will feel at easssse."</text>
			<remove name="MINELAUNCHER_KERNEL"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="KNIGHT_KERNEL_DOUBLE_PAYMENT"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
    </choice>
    <choice req="KERNEL_1_ELITE">
		<text>Offer the knight an elite Kernel Burst 1.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"I have alwayssss wanted a Kernel weapon. An elite Kernel isss even better! Maybe when I usssse thissss, I will feel at easssse."</text>
			<remove name="KERNEL_1_ELITE"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="KNIGHT_KERNEL_DOUBLE_PAYMENT"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
    </choice>
    <choice req="KERNEL_2_ELITE">
		<text>Offer the knight an elite Kernel Burst 2.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"I have alwayssss wanted a Kernel weapon. An elite Kernel isss even better! Maybe when I usssse thissss, I will feel at easssse."</text>
			<remove name="KERNEL_2_ELITE"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="KNIGHT_KERNEL_DOUBLE_PAYMENT"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
    </choice>
    <choice req="KERNEL_HEAVY_ELITE">
		<text>Offer the knight an elite Heavy Kernel.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"I have alwayssss wanted a Kernel weapon. An elite Kernel isss even better! Maybe when I usssse thissss, I will feel at easssse."</text>
			<remove name="KERNEL_HEAVY_ELITE"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="KNIGHT_KERNEL_DOUBLE_PAYMENT"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
    </choice>
    <choice req="KERNEL_FIRE_ELITE">
		<text>Offer the knight an elite Fire Kernel.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"I have alwayssss wanted a Kernel weapon. An elite Kernel isss even better! Maybe when I usssse thissss, I will feel at easssse."</text>
			<remove name="KERNEL_FIRE_ELITE"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="KNIGHT_KERNEL_DOUBLE_PAYMENT"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
    </choice>
    <choice req="KERNEL_CHAIN_ELITE">
		<text>Offer the knight an elite Chain Kernel.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"I have alwayssss wanted a Kernel weapon. An elite Kernel isss even better! Maybe when I usssse thissss, I will feel at easssse."</text>
			<remove name="KERNEL_CHAIN_ELITE"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="KNIGHT_KERNEL_DOUBLE_PAYMENT"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
    </choice>
    <choice req="KERNEL_CHARGE_ELITE">
		<text>Offer the knight an elite Charge Kernel.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"I have alwayssss wanted a Kernel weapon. An elite Kernel isss even better! Maybe when I usssse thissss, I will feel at easssse."</text>
			<remove name="KERNEL_CHARGE_ELITE"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="KNIGHT_KERNEL_DOUBLE_PAYMENT"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
    </choice>
	<choice req="STRAWBERRY">
  	  <text>Offer the knight a Strawberry Gun.</text>
  	  <event>
  		  <text>"What'ssss thisss? Thisss lookssss extremely rare, issss thissss a Renegade weapon? Maybe I sssshould become a Renegade too. Thank you."</text>
  		  <remove name="STRAWBERRY"/>
  		  <choice hidden="true">
  			  <text>Continue...</text>
  			  <event load="KNIGHT_STRAWBERRY_REWARD"/>
  		  </choice>
  	  </event>
	</choice>
	<choice req="STRAWBERRY_CHAOS">
        <text>Offer the knight a Chaotic Strawberry Gun.</text>
        <event>
            <text>"Thissss... issss the mosssst bizarre weapon I've ever sssseen. What have you given me...?"</text>
            <remove name="STRAWBERRY_CHAOS"/>
            <choice>
                <text>Continue..?</text>
                <event>
                    <win ach="slug" creditsText="credit_victory_slug_orchid" text="The galaxy is completely unrecognizable now." creditsBackground="VICTORY_SLUG"/>
             </event>
            </choice>
        </event>
    </choice>
    <choice>
		<text>Attack the Knight's ship.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The private communication is cut. The Knight ship immediately responds to your assault!</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice>
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
    </choice>
    <choice>
		<text>Ignore the strange Knight.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The knight makes no moves to interfere with you.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
    </choice>
</event>
<event name="KNIGHT_KERNEL_PAYMENT_OR_TRADE">
    <text>"I'll let you pick. Would you prefer payment, or a weapon?"</text>
    <choice>
		<text>Payment.</text>
		<event>
			<autoReward level="MED">scrap_only</autoReward>
		</event>
    </choice>
    <choice>
		<text>Trade.</text>
		<event>
			<weapon name="GIFTLIST_KNIGHT"/>
		</event>
    </choice>
</event>
<event name="KNIGHT_KERNEL_DOUBLE_PAYMENT">
	<text>As a repayment for your generous gift, the Knight gives you one of his own weapons, plus a modest amount of scrap to accompany it.</text>
    <weapon name="GIFTLIST_KNIGHT"/>
    <autoReward level="MED">scrap_only</autoReward>
</event>
<event name="KNIGHT_STRAWBERRY_REWARD">
    <text>"You've been too generoussss... I wissssh that I could come with you, but leaving the Kleptocracy would leave me homelessss, and after the excitement fadessss I'd like ssssomewhere to live. What I can do for you, in addition to one of my own weaponssss, isss offer you a tune-up on your weaponssss and reactor. I hope it will ssssuffice."</text>
    <upgrade amount="1" system="reactor"/>  
    <upgrade amount="1" system="weapons"/>  
	<weapon name="GIFTLIST_KNIGHT"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">scrap_only</autoReward>
</event>

<event name="KNIGHT_HEKTAR" unique="true">
    <text>The ship here clearly has a different affiliation to the rest. "Welcome to the Royal Nebula, outssssidersss. We've come here on behalf of Hektar to try and capitalize on thisss hissstoric moment. Would you like to buy a memento of the crown hunt? A limited edition crown, a perfect sssouvenir!"</text>
    <ship load="SHIP_HEKTAR_ALL" hostile="false"/>
    <choice req="LIST_VARIANT_BILLY" hidden="true">
		<text>(Billy) "Are you wassssting company money on thissss?"</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Slug does a double take. "CEO Billy!!! Um... Lisssten, I can explain!" Billy narrows his eyes. "You'd better, your job dependssss upon it." The Hektar employee begins to sputter. He spouts out a number of excuses, before sheepishly shutting up and giving Billy a bribe.</text>
			<autoReward level="HIGH">scrap_only</autoReward>
			<weapon name="GIFTLIST_MODULES"/>
			<store>STORE_HEKTAR_DEFAULT</store>
			<choice>
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event>
					<text>Before you shop, you still have some time to do something else aboard the ship.</text>
					<choice>
						<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
						<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>Do nothing.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
    </choice>
    <choice req="unique_metyunt" hidden="true">
		<text>(Metyunt) This isn't up to regulation.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Metyunt starts to quote the Hektar employee handbook. As he does, the Slug on the other side has a moment of comprehension. "Oh. Pleasssse, don't report me... If it would have worked, I might have been rewarded!" Metyunt sighs. "Well, the very least you can do is give us a look at your store. With credit." The Slug nods.</text>
			<autoReward level="LOW">scrap_only</autoReward>
			<store>STORE_HEKTAR_DEFAULT</store>   		 
			<choice>
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event>
					<text>You have the opportunity to do something on your ship after you shop.</text>
					<choice>
						<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
						<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>Do nothing.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
    </choice>
    <choice req="LIST_VARIANT_HEKTAR">
   	 <text>(Hektar Employee) Ask them if they really expect this to work.</text>
   	 <event>
   		 <text>"A fellow Hektar employee...? Well, I did but... sssshowssss what I know." Your Employee tells them they might as well recoup some of the cost by letting you use their store. "...Fine."</text>
   		 <store>STORE_HEKTAR_DEFAULT</store>
   		 <choice>
   			 <text>Continue...</text>
   			 <event>
   				 <text>You have the opportunity to do something on your ship after you shop.</text>
   				 <choice>
   					 <text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
   					 <event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
   				 </choice>
   				 <choice>
   					 <text>Do nothing.</text>
   					 <event/>
   				 </choice>
   			 </event>
   		 </choice>
   	 </event>
    </choice>
    <choice>
		<text>Buy a phony crown.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Ah, good tasssste, loyal customer. Come, ssssee what elsssse we have in sssstore!" The speaker leans away from the microphone, and you can faintly hear him say to someone else: "Wow, finally ssssold one... I wassss worried my bossss would yell at me for thissss boneheaded idea."</text>
			<store>STORE_HEKTAR_DEFAULT</store>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="-30" max="-10"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
    </choice>
    <choice>
		<text>Attack the wayward Hektar.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The salesman quickly shuts off the display and activates their weapons.</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
    </choice>
    <choice>
		<text>Don't waste your money on this weirdo.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Renegade, you have no tasssste!"</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
    </choice>
</event>

<event name="KNIGHT_AMPERE_HOPEFUL" unique="true">
    <text>Strangely, a Republic ship has made its way into this region of space. "Hey, hi, how ya doin'? Since you're not affiliated with these Slugs, I just wanted to ask for your opinion on this disguise. It'll be great, I'm going to find the crown and become ruler of the Slugs." The Ampere's dressed up in a full Slug suit. It's not terrible.</text>
    <ship load="SHIP_LEECH_ELITE_ALL" hostile="false"/> <!--add an actual slug with leech stats with an augment-->
    <choice hidden="true">
		<text>Tell him it's nice and wish him good luck.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Damn right! I'm gonna win this thing. And... uh, here's a little something for keeping quiet about this."</text>
			<autoReward level="LOW">standard</autoReward>
		</event>
    </choice>
    <choice hidden="true">
		<text>Aren't Slugs... you know... telepathic?</text>
		<event>
			<text>"I got it all figured out!" He opens up his costume and shows you that the head of the costume is insulated with tin-foil. "...you'll see! It'll all work out." You shake your head. "Ah whatever. Take this and get outta here." He gives you some fuel.</text>
			<autoReward level="MED">fuel_only</autoReward>
		</event>
    </choice>
    <choice hidden="true">
		<text>You're going to need a Slug ship if you're going to pass.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"...Oops! Can't believe I forgot about that. Uhhh... I guess I'll just have my guys drop me off somewhere and I'll hitchhike or something. Thanks for the tip." He graciously gives you a decent amount of scrap.</text>
			<autoReward level="MED">scrap_only</autoReward>
		</event>
    </choice>
    <choice>
		<text>Attack this idiot.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You roll your eyes and power up your weapons. The Leeches are quick to respond.</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
    </choice>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					ITEM EVENTS ()
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<eventList name="NEBULA_ITEMS_KNIGHT">
	<event load="NEBULA_KNIGHT_QUIZ"/>
	<event load="NEBULA_KNIGHT_TRAP"/>
	<event load="NEBULA_KNIGHT_SMUGGLER"/>
	<event load="NEBULA_KNIGHT_DUEL"/>
</eventList>

<event name="NEBULA_KNIGHT_QUIZ" unique="true"> <!--basically free stuff with extra flavor unless you're stupid-->
	<text>It's not too common to see Clairvoyant ships about, but you've seen far less than expected here in this Slug-filled nebula. It seems you've finally run into one though, and they aren't firing on you just yet. Instead, it looks like they want to communicate.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_SLUG_ELITE_FIGHT" hostile="false"/> 
	<environment type="nebula"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Respond.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"If our data issss correct, might it be true that you are the ssship everyone iss talking about? The one that hasss brought back to usss Ssslocknog, our great king?"</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Yes.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Fasssscinating. Now I am wondering, do you think Sssslocknog is the bessst king for the Kleptocracy? Or do you prefer Nightsss and hisss... more radical way of leading usss?"</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Slocknog is the true king.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"Interesssting. And what makesss you sssay that?"</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>He keeps things traditional. No need to change what works.</text>
								<event>
									<text>"Yesss, if it ain't broke, don't fix it... Well then, I cannot thank you enough for sssaving our king. Accept thisss asss humble payment."</text>
									<autoReward level="MED">stuff</autoReward>
								</event>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>His name has a lot of S's in it.</text>
								<event>
									<text>"I don't think you underssstand what definesss a good trait in a king. Maybe you are not the bessst perssson to be getting involved in our politicsss..." You assume that's the end of it, but suddenly the Clairvoyant ship attacks! The Slugs must really not appreciate your intervention...</text>
									<ship hostile="true"/>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Continue...</text>
										<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>He has yellow skin. That's pretty cool.</text>
								<event>
									<text>"I don't think you underssstand what definesss a good trait in a king. Maybe you are not the bessst perssson to be getting involved in our politicsss..." You assume that's the end of it, but suddenly the Clairvoyant ship attacks! The Slugs must really not appreciate your intervention...</text>
									<ship hostile="true"/>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Continue...</text>
										<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Nights is the true king.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"Interesssting. Ssso you would think that a drug addicted ssscumlord with three wivesss isss the chosssen king for the Ssslug people? Really ssshows how ignorant the Federation is..." You assume that's the end of it, but suddenly the Clairvoyant ship attacks! The Slugs must really not appreciate your intervention...</text>
							<ship hostile="true"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>I'm indifferent.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"Hmmm, yesss bessst not for foreignerssss to get involved in we Sssslugsss more peculiar formssss of government. All isss well then, take thisss ass a gift for sssaving Sssslocknog."</text>
							<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>No.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Oh... how unfortunate." The ship jumps away, leaving you with nothing to do.</text>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="unique_slocknog">
				<text>(Slocknog) "Yesss, it isss indeed that ssship."</text>
				<event>
					<text>"My liege! I ssswear to follow you wherever you ssshall tread." The Clairvoyants offer supplies and one of them even join your crew.</text>
					<autoReward level="MED">stuff</autoReward>
					<crewMember amount="1" all_skills="1" class="slug_saboteur"/>
				</event>		
			</choice>	
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Respond with violence!</text>
		<event>
			<text>The irredeemable bastard you are, you've decided to assault the ship without even giving them a chance.</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="NEBULA_KNIGHT_TRAP" unique="true">
	<text>A Slug vessel nearby is approaching a planet without any signs of civilization. You can't imagine what they'd be doing, unless they're hiding from something, or know something you don't.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_SLUG_KNIGHT_TRAP" hostile="false"/> 
	<img back="BACK_EVENT_LIGHTNEBULA" planet="PLANET_UNPOPULATED_TERRA"/>
	<status type="loss" target="player" system="sensors" amount="1"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Question them.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Huh? Oh, we're here to partake in the Crown Theft Fesssstival! We were told by some lovely fellowssss in a black and red sssship that thissss isss the place the contesst is being held."</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>There's no one on that planet.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Huh? What ever do you mean? That... Oh. I ssssee. It appearsss we have been played for foolssss. Thank you for sssaving us."</text>
					<autoReward level="LOW">standard</autoReward>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Don't tell them the truth, but kill them and go investigate yourself.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Wait, what are you doing?!" You cut off the Slugs and attack.</text>
					<ship hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">	
		<text>Ignore the Slugs.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You watch as the Slugs fly past you with mild curiosity.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="KNIGHT_TRAP_PLANET">
	<text>You move closer to the planet. You can't see anything visibly of interest, but it's hard to say from a distance.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Land.</text>
		<event load="KNIGHT_TRAP_PLANET_LAND"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="sensors" lvl="2">
		<text>(Upg. Sensors) Scan the surface from a distance.</text>
		<event load="KNIGHT_TRAP_PLANET_SCAN"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="ADV_SCANNERS" lvl="1">
		<text>(Long-Ranged Scanners) Scan the surface from a distance.</text>
		<event load="KNIGHT_TRAP_PLANET_SCAN"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Avoid the planet.</text>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="KNIGHT_TRAP_PLANET_LAND">
	<event>
		<text>As you pilot closer to the planet, an automated message blasts through your ship, "GOTTEM!", followed by a massive explosion that knocks your ship backwards and leaves a humongous crater.</text>
		<damage amount="5"/>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>You land on the planet's surface, and find a massive explosive trap. Scans show it should have already detonated on your approach, but whatever idiot wired it did a horrible job. Without anything to protect it, you scrap as much as you can.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">missiles</autoReward>
	</event>
</eventList>
<eventList name="KNIGHT_TRAP_PLANET_SCAN">
	<event>
		<text>Though the first sweep reveals little, a second and much more in-depth one reveals a massive explosive trap on the surface, wired to explode as soon as you get too close. It's too risky to approach.</text>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>Scans show a massive explosive trap meant to explode as soon as you approach, but whoever must have wired it did a terrible job. It should have already detonated on your approach, but without anything to protect it, you scrap as much as you can.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">missiles</autoReward>
	</event>
</eventList>

<event name="NEBULA_KNIGHT_SMUGGLER" unique="true">
	<text>Though Slugs have few qualms with transporting illicit contraband themselves, sometimes they'll pay the Smuggler clan to do their business. A Smuggler ship is attempting to avoid being seen by passing traffic, but fails to hide from you.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_KNIGHT_SMUGGLER" hostile="false"/> 
	<environment type="nebula"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Hail them, maybe we can buy some contraband off of them.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The smuggler captain appears on the screen. Though he tries to put on a menacing appearance, you can tell from his eager smug grin he's pleased by the prospect of another client. "If you're looking for guns or explosives, can't help you there Feddy boy. I'm on an express trip to Nights himself to deliver some brain melting power. These narcotics sell for premium price among the Slugs here, though not much in any other place."</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Buy the narcotics, they could be a valuable bargaining chip among Nights' men.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"An excellent purchase! Just don't ask what they're made of." You hear the pirate mumble something about Orchid children and Equinoid droppings, then hangs up.</text>
					<augment name="SLUG_NARCOTICS"/>
					<item_modify>
						<item type="scrap" min="-30" max="-30"/>
					</item_modify>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Fight them for the drugs!</text>
				<event load="KNIGHT_SMUGGLER_ATTACK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="COMBAT_ENGINE_JAMMER">
				<text>(Engine Disabler) Cripple their engines and demand they hand over the narcotics!</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Alright, alright! God damn, why are you so aggressive. You're the one who wanted to trade anyways..."</text>
					<augment name="SLUG_NARCOTICS"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="FTL_JAMMER">
				<text>(FTL Jammer) Cripple their engines and demand they hand over the narcotics!</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Alright, alright! God damn, why are you so aggressive. You're the one who wanted to trade anyways..."</text>
					<augment name="SLUG_NARCOTICS"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="hacking" lvl="2">
				<text>(Upg. Hacking) Cripple their engines and demand they hand over the narcotics!</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Alright, alright! God damn, why are you so aggressive. You're the one who wanted to trade anyways..."</text>
					<augment name="SLUG_NARCOTICS"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Decline.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">	
		<text>Ignore the Smugglers.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The smugglers slip away into the nebula not much longer.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="KNIGHT_SMUGGLER_ATTACK">
	<event>
		<text>You arm the weapons and attack the smugglers!</text>
		<ship hostile="true"/>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>You arm the weapons and attack the smugglers!</text>
		<ship hostile="true"/>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>You move in to attack, but the Smugglers hail you again. "Ok, maybe the price was too high! Let's not be hasty. Is this a more favorable deal?"</text>
		<choice>
			<text>Buy the new deal.</text>
			<event>
				<text>"An excellent purchase! Just don't ask what they're made of." You hear the pirate mumble something about Orchid children and Equinoid droppings, then hangs up.</text>
				<augment name="SLUG_NARCOTICS"/>
				<item_modify>
					<item type="scrap" min="-20" max="-20"/>
				</item_modify>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>No, we're still going to kill you.</text>
			<event>
				<text>You arm the weapons and attack the smugglers!</text>
				<ship hostile="true"/>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
				</choice>
			</event>
		</choice>
	</event>
</eventList>
<event name="SLUG_NARCOTICS">
	<text>It appears the Slugs are intrigued by your offer. They gladly accept the narcotics in turn for not fighting you, and even offer some scrap in return.</text>
	<remove name="SLUG_NARCOTICS"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">scrap_only</autoReward>
	<ship hostile="false"/> 
</event>

<event name="NEBULA_KNIGHT_DUEL" unique="true">
	<text>Out of nowhere, a Slug beams aboard your ship, brandishing a long sword. "On guard ye! I challenge you to a duel. Non-fatal, of coursssse. Defeat me and I will give you all the sssscrap my sssship carriessss. Lossse, and I take all of your fuel. Decline, and I shall leave without another word."</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_KNIGHT" hostile="false"/>
	<environment type="nebula"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Accept.</text>
		<event load="KNIGHT_DUEL_DUEL"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_MANTIS">
		<text>(Mantis Crew) Have your Mantis duel.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You send out your Mantis to duel. They give their all, and manage to disarm the Slug! "Alright, a deal isss a deal... Though I don't like the way you played, here'sssss my ssscrap."</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="35" max="45"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="unique_dessius"> <!-- because he literally has a sword -->
		<text>(Dessius) Have Dessius take the duel.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Being a perfect match for such opportunity, Dessius accepts the challenge and unsheaths his own blade. Both fighters give their all, and this chivalrous clash results in the Slug getting disarmed! "Alright, a deal isss a deal. Your companion's prowesss and ssstyle is remarkable, and you do dessserve thisss ssscrap."</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="75" max="85"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>		
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="unique_devorak"> <!-- because he literally has a sword -->
		<text>(Devorak) Have Devorak take the duel.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Being a perfect match for such opportunity, Devorak accepts the challenge and unsheaths his own blade. Both fighters give their all, and this chivalrous clash results in the Slug getting disarmed! "Alright, a deal isss a deal. Your companion's prowesss and ssstyle is remarkable, and you do dessserve thisss ssscrap."</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="75" max="85"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>		
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="slug_knight">
		<text>(Knight Crew) Have your Knight duel.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"I wasssn't expecting to sssee one of my brothersss aboard your vesssel, and even lesss that I'd be going againsst them, but I ssstill look forward to it." Both Slugs fiercely fight, and after a long clash, your own Knight prevails! "Alright, a deal isss a deal. I greatly enjoyed thisss valiant ssskirmisssh, and you do dessserve thisss ssscrap."</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="75" max="85"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>		
	</choice>	
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Decline.</text>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="KNIGHT_DUEL_DUEL">
	<event>
		<text>You pick a crew at random, and send them out to duel. They make a valiant effort, but unfortunately it's not enough. They fail, and the Slug disarms them. "Haha! You losssst. Now, hand over your fuel... And no funny busssinessss!"</text>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>A deal is a deal.</text>
			<event>
				<text>"A good ssssport! Honorable indeed." The Slug beams off with all of your fuel, leaving you stranded.</text>
				<item_modify steal="true">
					<item type="fuel" min="-999" max="-999"/>
				</item_modify>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Refuse.</text>
			<event>
				<text>"What? What a poor ssssport. We made a deal!" The Slug beams back to his ship, and a second later it activates, weapons online. Even worse, it appears they're using a combat augment to jam your shields!</text>
				<status type="loss" target="player" system="shields" amount="2"/>
				<ship hostile="true"/>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
				</choice>
				<choice hidden="true" req="ANTI_VIRUS">
					<text>(Anti-Virus) Unjam your shields.</text>
					<event>
						<text>You re-enable your shields, and prepare to fight the Slugs.</text>
						<status type="clear" target="player" system="shields" amount="100"/>
						<choice hidden="true">
							<text>Continue...</text>
							<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
						</choice>
					</event>
				</choice>
			</event>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>You pick a crew at random, and send them out to duel. They give their all, and somehow they manage to disarm the Slug! "Alright, a deal isss a deal... Heres'ssss my ssscrap."</text>
		<item_modify>
			<item type="scrap" min="75" max="85"/>
		</item_modify>
	</event>
</eventList>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					NEUTRAL EVENTS ()
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<eventList name="NEBULA_NEUTRAL_KNIGHT">
	<event load="NEBULA_KNIGHT_COALITION"/>
	<event load="NEBULA_KNIGHT_CHOICE"/>
	<event load="NEBULA_KNIGHT_PROTESTERS"/>
	<event load="NEBULA_KNIGHT_SHAKESPEARE"/>
	<event load="NEBULA_KNIGHT_JAILER"/>
</eventList>

<event name="NEBULA_KNIGHT_COALITION" unique="true">
	<text>You knew the Coalition consisted of Slugs among other races, but it's not terribly often you see their ships so deep in Slug space.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_COALITION_KNIGHT" hostile="false"/> 
	<environment type="nebula"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Attack the Coalition!</text>
		<event>
			<text>You power up your weapons and engage the Coalition vessel.</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice req="SLUG_NARCOTICS" hidden="true">
		<text>Bribe the Coalition with the Narcotics.</text>
		<event load="KNIGHT_COALITION_BRIBE"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">	
		<text>Ignore the Coalition.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You aren't willing to risk getting involved with another galactic super power today. For another reality, maybe.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="KNIGHT_COALITION_BRIBE">
	<event>
		<text>"What? Drugs? Why would we need these? Get lost, Federation!"</text>
		<ship hostile="true"/> 
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>"I- are these Slug narcotics?" A Rock Crusader looks down at the drugs, but they're quickly scoop up by a Saboteur on the ship. "Yessss, we'll take them!"</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">weapon</autoReward>
		<remove name="SLUG_NARCOTICS"/>
	</event>
</eventList>
<eventList name="KNIGHT_COALITION_SUZERAIN">
	<event>
		<text>The Suzerain beams aboard, but only to immediately detonate a fire bomb that damages the ship! It was a trick!</text>
		<damage amount="3" system="random" effect="fire"/>
		<boarders min="1" max="1" class="mantis_suzerain"/>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>True to his word, the Suzerain beams aboard your ship, ready to turn on his old crew-mates.</text>
		<crewMember amount="1" combat="1" class="mantis_suzerain"/>
	</event>
</eventList>

<event name="NEBULA_KNIGHT_CHOICE" unique="true">
	<text>Short range scans show two Slug vessels are in a dogfight at this beacon: one belong to the Knights, and the other to the Clairvoyants.</text>
	<img back="BACK_EVENT_LIGHTNEBULA"/>
	<status type="loss" target="player" system="sensors" amount="1"/>
	<choice hidden="true">	
		<text>Get involved.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You make your presence known, flying towards the ships. But who will you attack?</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>The Knights!</text>
				<event>
					<text>You arm the weapons and attack the Knight vessel.</text>
					<ship load="SHIP_KNIGHT_CHOICE_KNIGHT" hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SLUG_NARCOTICS">
				<text>(Slug Narcotics) Bribe the Knights to stop fighting.</text>
				<event>
					<text>It appears the Knights are willing to swallow their pride and surrender if it means they get free hard drugs.</text>
					<remove name="SLUG_NARCOTICS"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event>
							<text>The Clairvoyant ship thanks you and offers a weapon.</text>
							<weapon name="RANDOM"/>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>The Clairvoyants!</text>
				<event>
					<text>You arm the weapons and attack the Clairvoyant vessel.</text>
					<ship load="SHIP_KNIGHT_CHOICE_CLAIRVOYANT" hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">	
		<text>Don't get involved.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Slugs have never been known to be reliable allies, so you don't bother helping any side.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="NEBULA_KNIGHT_PROTESTERS" unique="true">
	<text>You jump when a disembodied voice suddenly speaks to you. From behind, a Saboteur uncloaks, wearing a pin of the Knight logo. "You're... an outsssider, right? The one Sssslocknog sssent. Normally I'd kill you on the ssspot, but I think we can work together here. There'ssss sssome pesssky reformisssstss nearby who are trying to overhaul our government. We want them dead. Kill them, I pay you. Deal?"</text>
	<environment type="nebula"/>
	<choice hidden="true">	
		<text>Accept.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Saboteur leads you to a small moon with a Slug colony where several Slugs are protesting, led by a rogue Clairvoyant vessel. Take out their leader, and the rest will likely shut up.</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_CLAIRVOYANT_PROTESTER" hostile="false"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Attack!</text>
				<event>
					<text>You raise the weapons and engage the ship.</text>
					<ship hostile="true"/> 
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="SLUG_NARCOTICS">
				<text>(Slug Narcotics) Bribe the Clairvoyant to turn on its own people.</text>
				<event>
					<text>It seems drugs outweigh any moral quandaries in Slug society. The Clairvoyants take hold of the drugs, then turn their weapons upon the colonists, forcing them to surrender. Behind you, the Knight is so humored by your 'creative' problem solving he offers an even larger reward.</text>
					<remove name="SLUG_NARCOTICS"/>
					<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">	
		<text>Refuse.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Saboteur frowns and beams away to whatever ship is hiding nearby in the nebula watching you.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="KNIGHT_PROTESTERS_WIN" unique="true">
	<text>The rest of the colony is terrified. "Pleasssse, all we want isss peacce! The Kleptocracy isss sssso needlesssly cruel, regardlesss of the king! We want to progressss Sslug sssociety into sssomething the ressst of the galaxy can look at with more than dissstasste!"</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore them and force the colony to surrender.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You ignore the colonists, raising your weapons and firing a warning shot. This sends them running for cover, and inevitably surrendering. The Saboteur returns and thanks you for your help, and rewards you as promised.</text>
			<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Kill the Saboteur and free the colony.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You draw your blaster, and quickly spin around to blast the Saboteur. They're faster at first, but quickly get lost in the unfamiliar corridors of your ship and are dispatched with relative ease. Though a future Knight vessel will likely return to prey on the colony, they're free for now, and reward you in a somewhat unconventional way.</text>
			<damage amount="-7"/>
			<upgrade amount="1" system="shields"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="BLUELIST_FIRE_ALL">
		<text>(Fire Weapon) Make an example, torch the colony.</text>
		<event>
			<text>In a short period of time, the colony is ablaze and about half of its population dead. It's a gruesome display that will undoubtedly be used as propaganda in the future, but it's had quite the impression on the Saboteur. So amazed at your dedication to the task, he even offers to join your crew!</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="slug_saboteur"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="NEBULA_KNIGHT_SHAKESPEARE" unique="true">
	<text>"Hail th're did Feed'ration. Though mine own w'rds might beest rough, I asketh thee to holdeth with me. I may give you nay harmeth, lest thee stow thine weapons 'r brandish dram m're than the bravado one might beest accustom'd to. Aye? Art these reasonable t'rms 'r might we beest needing a duel?"</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_KNIGHT" hostile="false"/>
	<environment type="nebula"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Slug captain looks at you expectantly, though you don't understand a word he said.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Try to speak back in whatever language that was.</text>
				<event load="KNIGHT_SHAKESPEARE_GUESS"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="unique_haynes">
				<text>(Haynes) Haynes recognizes the language.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Haynes explains that the Slugs are speaking in old Earth English. After a quick translation, you learn the Slugs are offering a truce, which you accept and bring back a weapon from their ship as a sign of goodwill!</text>
					<weapon name="RANDOM"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_SLUG">
				<text>(Slug Crew) Have your Slug speak with them.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Your Slug bickers back and forth with the knights for a while, then reports back to you. "They sssspeak fine, they're jusssst ssstubborn and refussse to talk to ussss normally. They sssseem to want to make friendssss though, and are offering fuel."</text>
					<autoReward level="MED">fuel_only</autoReward>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_ENGI">
				<text>(Engi Crew) Analyze their speech patterns to translate.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Language detected: old Earth English. Updating databases..." Your Engi explains the Slugs don't wish to fight, but actually wish to give you some fuel out of good will.</text>
					<autoReward level="MED">fuel_only</autoReward>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="KNIGHT_SHAKESPEARE_GUESS">
	<event>
		<text>You fumble out some meaningless garble in hopeless imitation of the Slug. They obviously don't fall for it, and attack you out of outrage for your pathetic attempt.</text>
		<ship hostile="true"/>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
		</choice>
		<choice req="SLUG_NARCOTICS">
			<text>Bribe them with the narcotics.</text>
			<event load="SLUG_NARCOTICS"/>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>Though your attempt at replicating the Slug's speech is pathetic, they don't seem particularly offended. Laughing tremendously at you, they invite you on-board their ship, and surprisingly offer some repairs and supplies.</text>
		<autoReward level="MED">stuff</autoReward>
		<damage amount="-7"/>
	</event>
</eventList>

<event name="NEBULA_KNIGHT_JAILER" unique="true">
	<text>A Knighted Jailer flies past, only to briefly sling an insult at you. "Pissss off Federation, don't get involved lesssst you want a hole in your ssskull!"</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_KNIGHT_JAILER" hostile="false"/> 
	<environment type="nebula"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Attack the Jailer.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You power up your weapons and engage the Slug vessel.</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="FIREARMS_AND_TELEPORT">
		<text>(Armories + Teleporter) Storm the Jailer.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Your crew, armed to the teeth, board the Jailer and quickly take down the Slug crew staffing it. With the jailers turned prisoners, you free everyone locked up who you don't think will kill you immediately.</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="LIST_CREW_FEDERATION"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice req="SLUG_NARCOTICS" hidden="true">
		<text>Bribe them with the narcotics to let the prisoners go.</text>
		<event load="KNIGHT_JAILER_BRIBE"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">	
		<text>Ignore the Jailer.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You aren't in the mood to hold a jailbreak today. You distance yourself from the Jailer.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="SURRENDER_KNIGHT_JAILER"> 
	<text>"Crap, you're better armed than predicted. Uh, will you let usss go if you take thissss prisssoner?"</text>
	<environment type="nebula"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept a prisoner.</text>
		<event>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="slug"/>
			<ship hostile="false"/> 
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Refuse and keep fighting.</text>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="KNIGHT_JAILER_DESTROY">
	<text>The Jailer has been destroyed. While an excess of scrap remains, it's very unlikely any prisoners survived.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<event name="KNIGHT_JAILER_KILL">
	<text>The crew of the Jailer has been emptied. You scrap the externals of the ship.</text>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Check the prisoners.</text>
		<event>
			<text>It appears most of the prisoners are dissenters from Nights' reign. A Saboteur loyal to Slocknog, recognizing you as the Federation ship sent by his hero, offers to work for you.</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="slug_saboteur"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="KNIGHT_JAILER_BRIBE">
	<text>The Jailer seems more than willing to betray their nation in turn for some hard drugs.</text>
	<remove name="SLUG_NARCOTICS"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Check the prisoners.</text>
		<event>
			<text>It appears most of the prisoners are dissenters from Nights' reign. A Saboteur loyal to Slocknog, recognizing you as the Federation ship sent by his hero, offers to work for you.</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="slug_saboteur"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					DISTRESS EVENTS ()
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->
<eventList name="NEBULA_DISTRESS_KNIGHT">
	<event load="NEBULA_DISTRESS_KNIGHT_TAXES"/>
	<event load="NEBULA_DISTRESS_KNIGHT_SHELLSPY"/>
</eventList>

<event name="NEBULA_DISTRESS_KNIGHT_TAXES" unique="true">
	<distressBeacon/>
	<text>The distress beacon here originates from a small Slug colony, which is being oppressed by a Knighted vessel. You catch a small excerpt from their conversation on the radio. "Thisss iss OUTRAGEOUSSSSS. We haven't been paying taxesss for yearsss! No one doesss. They're merely a concept, not sssomething you enforce! Don't tell me that coward Nightsss finally got ssso greedy he'sss going to sssteal hissss own citizensss' money too?"</text> 
	<environment type="nebula"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Help the colony.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You intend to liberate the Slug colony, and attack the Knighted vessel.</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_KNIGHT_TAXES" hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Help the Knights.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You fire upon the colony, but in response they send a Clairvoyant ship to deal with you!</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_KNIGHT_TAXES_COLONY" hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">	
		<text>Don't get involved.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You have better things to do than help Slugs commit tax evasion.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="KNIGHT_TAXES_COLONYHELP">
	<text>The colony is grateful for your help. "Thankssss. Under Sssslocknog, there were no taxesss, we all got along jussst fine and the government got itsss money from extorting other nationsss. Like it sssshould be! Nightsss doesssn't even want the money to run the Kleptocracy, he just wantsss to ssspend it all on liquor and a mate." The colony brings out a weapon they've been keeping for defensive purposes but no longer need thanks to you.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">weapon</autoReward>
</event>
<event name="KNIGHT_TAXES_KNIGHTHELP">
	<text>Without their ship, the colony surrenders to the Knights. After their taxes have been collected and a few fugitives rounded up, the Knights contact you next. "The hell wasss that? You're probably looking for a reward. Uh... here, have one of the criminalssss. We'll just tell Nightsss they died of some obssscure disssseasse that rapidly decaysss the body or sssomething."</text>
	<crewMember amount="1" weapons="1" class="slug"/>
</event>

<event name="NEBULA_DISTRESS_KNIGHT_SHELLSPY" unique="true">
	<distressBeacon/>
	<text>Surprisingly, it seems a Shell Radiant ship has found their way into the nebula here. They hail you, requesting aid.</text>
	<environment type="nebula"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Receive their request.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Oh good Federation captain, please help! We're here on a mission for thhhhhe Geniocracy to observe the Slug operations, but our commander was taken hostage! Could you track down the shhhip that took thhhhhem and bring thhhem back?"</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Agree.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You plunge further into the nebula until you find the ship they were talking about, but they're already prepared for an attack and lock onto you immediately!</text>
					<ship load="SHIP_KNIGHT_SHELLSPY" hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
					<choice req="SLUG_NARCOTICS" hidden="true">
						<text>Bribe them with the narcotics to let the Shells go.</text>
						<event load="KNIGHT_SHELLSPY_BRIBE"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Decline.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Screw helping people, let's murder!</text>
		<event>
			<text>Once again your sadistic tendencies have taken control, and you've abandoned all decency. But no matter, man the weapons!</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_SHELL_ELITE_GENERIC" hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="MORALITY_UPDATE_SHELL_FIGHT"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore the Shells.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You aren't here to participate in random side quests.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="KNIGHT_SHELLSPY_BRIBE">
	<text>The Knights seems more than willing to betray their nation in turn for some hard drugs.</text>
	<remove name="SLUG_NARCOTICS"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Check on the spy.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Once free, you offer to bring the Radiant back, but he refuses. "Can't, our mission has been compromised. I'll order my men back, but I can't return to thhhe Geniocracy. Thhhhey have little tolerance for failure from Radiants like me. I will come withhh you instead, if thhhat is alright with you."</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="shell_radiant">Bond</crewMember>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					QUEST EVENTS ()
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->


<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					HOSTILE EVENTS ()
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->
<eventList name="NEBULA_HOSTILE_KNIGHT">
	<event load="NEBULA_ENCOUNTER_KNIGHT"/>
	<event load="NEBULA_ENCOUNTER_KNIGHT_CLAIRVOYANT"/>
	<event load="NEBULA_ENCOUNTER_SLUG"/>
	
	<event load="NEBULA_KNIGHT_ENGINES"/>
</eventList>

<event name="NEBULA_ENCOUNTER_KNIGHT">
	<loadEventList first="false" generate="true">
		<event name="NEBULA_ENCOUNTER_KNIGHT_REGULAR"/>
		<event name="NEBULA_ENCOUNTER_KNIGHT_STORM"/>
	</loadEventList>
</event>
<event name="NEBULA_ENCOUNTER_KNIGHT_REGULAR">
	<text load="NEBULA_KNIGHT_FIGHT"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_KNIGHT" hostile="true"/>
	<environment type="nebula"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
	<choice req="SLUG_NARCOTICS">
		<text>Bribe them with the narcotics.</text>
		<event load="SLUG_NARCOTICS"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="NEBULA_KNIGHT_FIGHT">
	<text>"Thessse nebulasss aren't for the Federation to be sssnooping around in! Get lossssst."</text>
	<text>The Knights of Nights sure are determined not to let anyone interfere with the festival. Despite you not even being able to participate, the mere suggestion you might be working with Slocknog is enough to drive the ship nearby to murder.</text>
	<text>A Knight ship jumps in, weapons blazing. It's not usual for Slugs to attack in such a blunt manner, but judging from the strange flight patterns of the ship, they're likely drunk. Let's hope that plays in your favor.</text>
	<text>It appears a Knight vessel is waiting for you here. "I made a bet that I would be the one to kill you! Now ssssit ssstill and let me blow you up."</text>
	<text>A Knight vessel appears to just have finished salvaging the remains of a small Slug interceptor, but as soon as you enter they decide to pick you off next!</text>
	<text>The Knights of Nights have proven to be far more aggressive than regular Slug vessels, and aren't afraid to attack you straight on!</text>
</textList>
<event name="NEBULA_ENCOUNTER_KNIGHT_STORM" unique="true">
	<text>It appears this beacon is home to not only an ion storm, but a Knight vessel as well!</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_KNIGHT" hostile="true"/>
	<environment type="storm"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
	<choice req="SLUG_NARCOTICS">
		<text>Bribe them with the narcotics.</text>
		<event load="SLUG_NARCOTICS"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="NEBULA_ENCOUNTER_KNIGHT_CLAIRVOYANT">
	<text load="NEBULA_KNIGHT_CLAIRVOYANT_FIGHT"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_SLUG_ELITE_FIGHT" hostile="true"/>
	<environment type="nebula"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
	<choice req="SLUG_NARCOTICS">
		<text>Bribe them with the narcotics.</text>
		<event load="SLUG_NARCOTICS"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="NEBULA_KNIGHT_CLAIRVOYANT_FIGHT">
	<text>The Clairvoyants are primarily in favor of Slocknog, but despite this it seems the ship here has chosen protecting their homeland over letting a foreign Federation ship rumored to be supporting their king running about.</text>
	<text>Though you haven't encountered as many Clairvoyant ships as you might have expected in a dense Slug nebula like this, it appears your luck has run out.</text>
	<text>A Clairvoyant ship has chosen to do their job and protect their sector, and is moving in to attack.</text>
	<text>"Renegade, you aren't ssssuppossssed to be here! Thissss isss a private sssector!" A Clairvoyant ship moves in to attack.</text>
</textList>

<event name="NEBULA_KNIGHT_ENGINES" unique="true">
	<text>Immediately after jumping into the beacon, your engines sputter and malfunction. Something is jamming them, and not longer after it's revealed who. A Knight vessel slips out of the nebula, offering to "fix" your engines for a bit of scrap.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_KNIGHT" hostile="false"/>
	<environment type="nebula"/>
	<status type="divide" target="player" system="engines" amount="2"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Refuse.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You aren't paying any fee for your 'broken' engines. Outraged at your refusal, the Knight vessel attacks!</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="ANTI_VIRUS">
		<text>(Anti-Virus) Correct the issue yourself.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You undo the damage they have done. Unsurprisingly, this does not deter them from assaulting you regardless.</text>
			<status type="clear" target="player" system="engines" amount="100"/>
			<ship hostile="true"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice req="SLUG_NARCOTICS">
		<text>Bribe them with the narcotics.</text>
		<event load="SLUG_NARCOTICS"/>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Pay.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Knight captain can't help but snicker as they board and pretend to work on your engines, scoop up some scrap, and leave.</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="-30" max="-25"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					UNIQUE EVENTS
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->
<event name="KNIGHT_CLAN" unique="true">
	<preventQuest/>
	<text>A Clan vessel has taken a rest nearby. You aren't sure why they're here so far outside of the nebulas where ships are hunting for the crown.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_CLAN_KING" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Hail them.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Ah, didn't think there wasss anyone elsse here who wassssn't busssy getting their asss handed to them by Nightsss'ss men. Idiotsss don't even know the Palace isssn't in a nebula, and that there'ssss no way Nightsss would dare leave the comfort of hisss hidey-hole."</text>
			<variable name="loc_speak_clancrown" op="set" val="1"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Why are you here?</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Ah, we've come here for the greatessst hunt known to the galaxy. Three headed beetle creaturesss, mutated Ssslug and Mantisss hybridss, and the mythical Sssalt Man are nothing compared to the prize we're after. The CROWN. Issss there anything better you could imagine?"</text>
					<choice>
						<text>Offer to buy any map data they have.</text>
						<event>
							<text>The Clansmen are more than willing to offer the data, knowing you're no threat to the title they're after.</text>
							<item_modify>
								<item type="scrap" min="-35" max="-20"/>
							</item_modify>
							<reveal_map/>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice blue="false" req="shields" lvl="2">
						<text>Offer to take them with you.</text>
						<event>
							<text>You explain that you're heading to the Palace yourself, and can take them there if they want. Shockingly, the Clansman is more than willing, but he wishes to test you. "I will not work aboard any ssship who is not as ssskilled at the hunt as I am. Let usss duel, and I ssshall only sssurrender sssshould you injure me to the point that I cannot proceed without medical aid!" Sounds easy enough, except the Clansman has used a combat augment to jam your Shields!</text>
							<status type="loss" target="player" system="shields" amount="2"/>
							<ship hostile="true"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true" req="ANTI_VIRUS">
								<text>(Anti-Virus) Restore your shields.</text>
								<event>
									<text>Your shields are restored. The Ranger will have to rely on conventional tactics rather than low blows.</text>
									<status type="clear" target="player" system="shields" amount="100"/>
									<ship hostile="true"/>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Continue...</text>
										<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice blue="false" req="shields" lvl="0" max_lvl="1">
						<text>Offer to take them with you.</text>
						<event>
							<text>You explain that you're heading to the Palace yourself, and can take them there if they want. Shockingly, the Clansman is more than willing, but he wishes to test you. "I will not work aboard any ssship who is not as ssskilled at the hunt as I am. Let usss duel, and I ssshall only sssurrender sssshould you injure me to the point that I cannot proceed without medical aid!"</text>
							<ship hostile="true"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Attack!</text>
		<event>
			<text>You take this chance to attack the Clansmen while they're distracted.</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">	
		<text>Ignore the Clansmen.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Messing with the Clansmen might not be the best idea. Better to take this chance to rest.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="KNIGHT_CLAN_OFFER">
	<text>You find the Ranger you spoke with earlier, injured, but surprisingly still alive. "You are truly an excellent fighter! I could think of no one better to work for. Here'ssss to hoping we get that crown, friend!"</text>
	<crewMember amount="1" class="slug_ranger"/>
	<variable name="loc_got_clancrown" op="set" val="1"/>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					SPECIAL EVENTS
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->
<event name="KNIGHT_PALACE" unique="true">
	<preventQuest/>
	<preventFleet/>
	<beaconType id="map_icon_palace2" global="true">
		<color r="220" g="210" b="60" a="1"/>
	</beaconType>
	<text>You've arrived at the royal palace at last. Slug infrastructure isn't always the most stunning, but you must admit the view in front of you is magnificent. It is no wonder Nights is so reluctant to give up his crown.</text>
	<img back="BACK_EVENT_SLUG_PALACE" planet="NONE"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>As you approach the massive overhang, you can see signs of struggle. It appears Slocknog has already made his move on the palace, along with a fleet of loyal Clairvoyant vessels.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Stick around and watch.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Slocknog has begun speaking to the crowd, which consists of both eager supporters protesting against Nights, and the well armed Knights holding them back. "Give it up Nightsssss. Come out of that palace and take part in the sssame fesstival every other king before you has eagerly participated in! You ssstole that crown, by cheating might I remind you, but if you're truly the brave fighter you claim to be then ssssurely you can protect your throne."</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event>
							<text>Slocknog urges Nights to come out several more times, then gives up and waits. There's a moment of silence, finally followed by Night's raspy voice over the intercom. "Fine, you sssshriveled pisss colored sssmelly sssson-of-a-bitch! I'll come out alright!" A few minutes later, Nights' signature ship, the Black Raven, comes bursting out of one of the hangars firing directly at Slocknog's much larger cruiser. Immediately, chaos breaks out.</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event>
									<text>The battle around you seems to have consumed the landscape for as far as you can see. Both sides seem to be equal in size. You could easily get involved and influence the outcome of this brawl, but who is the right choice?</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Aid Slocknog - he seems reasonable enough, and might be able to bring the Slugs to a glory age.</text>
										<event>
											<text>With Slocknog in charge, the Kleptocracy might finally be able to progress past this stage of barbaric thievery. The Federation aims for a better galaxy, and you'll be damned if you don't do something to see it through.</text>
											<ship load="SHIP_BLACK_RAVEN" hostile="true"/> 
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Continue...</text>
												<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Aid Nights - he seems like the king the Slugs you know would want.</text>
										<event>
											<text>Nights might seem bad on the surface, but to raise this much of a following surely the guy must have some redeeming qualities in the eyes of the Slugs. If you're going to be involved, you might as well pick someone the Slugs want.</text>
											<ship load="SHIP_SLOCKNOG" hostile="true"/> 
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Continue...</text>
												<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Who are we to partake in these matters?</text>
										<event/>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Things might get hectic, let's leave while we can.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Better not to risk it. You pull away from the planet.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
						<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Do nothing.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="KNIGHT_PALACE_RESOLUTION_SLOCKNOG">
	<text>As the Black Raven crashes into the lake, the fighting suddenly seems to come to a halt. You land your ship next to the Clairvoyant Cruiser, where Slocknog smiles and shakes your hand. "I of coursssse could have done it on my own, but... thank you, captain. Thisss isss twice now you have gone out of your way to help me. May the ssstarssss ssshine brightesst between usss, eh friend?"</text>
	<variable name="ach_boss_nights" op="set" val="1"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="KNIGHT_PALACE_RESOLUTION_SLOCKNOG_REAL"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="loc_got_clancrown">
		<text>Go after the crown yourself.</text>
		<event>
			<text>While you watch the ship be fished out of the lake, you remember the Clansmen from earlier, and get the urge to retrieve the crown for yourself, though it won't be easy. Assuming they're still with you, that is.</text>
			<choice hidden="true" req="slug_ranger">
				<text>Your Clansman is alive, let's go for it.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The Slugs have just found the Black Raven's wreck, and have dropped it onto the bank. You'll need stealth to get over there undetected.</text>
					<choice hidden="true" req="cloaking" lvl="2">
						<text>(Upg. Cloaking) Cloak and approach.</text>
						<event>
							<text>You cloak the ship and pilot closer to the wreckage. Now, you'll need to be able to teleport your crew onto the Raven without being seen.</text>
							<choice hidden="true" req="teleporter">
								<text>(Teleporter) Beam the crew aboard.</text>
								<event name="KNIGHT_PALACE_RESOLUTION_SLOCKNOG_BOARD">
									<text>Now that your crew are aboard, the stakes are a lot higher. Unfortunately, it's not easy to see in the dark corridors.</text>
									<choice hidden="true" req="sensors" lvl="2">
										<text>(Upg. Sensors) Guide them.</text>
										<event load="KNIGHT_PALACE_THEFT"/>
									</choice>
									<choice hidden="true" req="ADV_SCANNERS">
										<text>(Long-Ranged Scanners) Guide them.</text>
										<event load="KNIGHT_PALACE_THEFT"/>
									</choice>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Proceed in the darkness.</text>
										<event>
											<text>Oblivious to their surroundings, your crew end up caught by one of the salvage team, and are shot! You have no choice but to pull away, but it's too late. The guards are now on high alert, and your ship takes heavy damage.</text>
											<damage amount="7"/>
											<removeCrew>
												<clone>true</clone>
												<text>Fortunately, your crew is able to be cloned, but that won't reverse the damage you've taken.</text>
											</removeCrew>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true" req="LOCKED_GLOBAL_TELEPORT">
								<text>(Central Teleport) Beam the crew aboard.</text>
								<event load="KNIGHT_PALACE_RESOLUTION_SLOCKNOG_BOARD"/>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Nevermind.</text>
								<event load="KNIGHT_PALACE_RESOLUTION_SLOCKNOG_REAL"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Nevermind.</text>
						<event load="KNIGHT_PALACE_RESOLUTION_SLOCKNOG_REAL"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="beans">
				<text>Bean Sylvan is alive, let's go for it.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The Slugs have just found the Black Raven's wreck, and have dropped it onto the bank. You'll need stealth to get over there undetected.</text>
					<choice hidden="true" req="cloaking" lvl="2">
						<text>(Upg. Cloaking) Cloak and approach.</text>
						<event>
							<text>You cloak the ship and pilot closer to the wreckage. Now, you'll need to be able to teleport your crew onto the Raven without being seen.</text>
							<choice hidden="true" req="teleporter">
								<text>(Teleporter) Beam the crew aboard.</text>
								<event name="KNIGHT_PALACE_RESOLUTION_SLOCKNOG_BEANS_BOARD">
									<text>Now that your crew are aboard, the stakes are a lot higher. Unfortunately, it's not easy to see in the dark corridors.</text>
									<choice hidden="true" req="sensors" lvl="2">
										<text>(Upg. Sensors) Guide them.</text>
										<event load="KNIGHT_BEANS_THEFT"/>
									</choice>
									<choice hidden="true" req="ADV_SCANNERS">
										<text>(Long-Ranged Scanners) Guide them.</text>
										<event load="KNIGHT_BEANS_THEFT"/>
									</choice>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Proceed in the darkness.</text>
										<event>
											<text>Oblivious to their surroundings, your crew end up caught by one of the salvage team, and are shot! You have no choice but to pull away, but it's too late. The guards are now on high alert, and your ship takes heavy damage.</text>
											<damage amount="7"/>
											<removeCrew>
												<clone>true</clone>
												<text>Fortunately, your crew is able to be cloned, but that won't reverse the damage you've taken.</text>
											</removeCrew>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true" req="LOCKED_GLOBAL_TELEPORT">
								<text>(Central Teleport) Beam the crew aboard.</text>
								<event load="KNIGHT_PALACE_RESOLUTION_SLOCKNOG_BEANS_BOARD"/>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Nevermind.</text>
								<event load="KNIGHT_PALACE_RESOLUTION_SLOCKNOG_REAL"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Nevermind.</text>
						<event load="KNIGHT_PALACE_RESOLUTION_SLOCKNOG_REAL"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Nevermind.</text>
				<event load="KNIGHT_PALACE_RESOLUTION_SLOCKNOG_REAL"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="KNIGHT_PALACE_THEFT">
	<text>Your Clansman grabs the crown, holding it up to admire. However, a band of Saboteurs burst in and see your crew, and draw their lasers to shoot. Your team is almost killed before the Clansman shouts for them to stop, declaring themselves the new king by rule of the Crown Theft Contest. The Slugs are dumbfounded, but no one protests.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Your crew waltz out of the wreck, crown on-top his head for all to see. You're amazed to see as the Slugs all around, Slocknog included, bow down, willing to accept this change of events...</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>We've done it.</text>
				<event>
					<win ach="slug" creditsText="credit_victory_slug" text="The galaxy is now a slightly worse place thanks to you." creditsBackground="VICTORY_SLUG"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="KNIGHT_BEANS_THEFT">
	<text>You grab the crown and hold it up to admire it. However, a band of Saboteurs burst in and see your crew, and draw their lasers to shoot. Your team is almost killed before Bean Sylvan shouts for them to stop, declaring themselves the new king by rule of the Crown Theft Contest. The Slugs are dumbfounded, but you raise the can of beans into the air and no one protests.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Your crew waltz out of the wreck, the crown ill-fittingly placed around the can of beans who drags it around him. You're amazed to see as the Slugs all around, Slocknog included, bow down, willing to accept this change of events... Like seriously, why are they so fine with this?</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>We've done it.</text>
				<event>
					<win ach="slug" creditsText="credit_victory_slug_beans" text="The galaxy is now a slightly worse place thanks to you." creditsBackground="VICTORY_SLUG"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="KNIGHT_PALACE_RESOLUTION_SLOCKNOG_REAL">
	<text>Once Nights' corpse has been recovered, he is moved to a hearse ship for later. The crown too is recovered, broken but miraculously not obliterated. The Slugs gather together to discuss what to do next.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Slocknog appears surprised that he isn't included with the crowd. As he attempts to speak to them, an angry member of the crowd speaks up. "You have no right to be here! Alwayssss ssspinning that ssstory about Nightsss cheating or whatever, but in the end you ssstill losssst. Ssssure you were a better king than Nightsss, but you ssstill just cost usss the livessss of DOZENSSSSS of our fellow Sssslugssss jusssst for your little coup!"</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event>
					<text>These words seem to resonate with nearly everyone present, and soon a mob has formed, marching towards Slocknog, demanding he be punished. The only reason no one suggests executing him is because no one has any clue who to elect in his stead.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>These people need further influence - use a show of force to put Slocknog back in power.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Considering you've become so heavily involved in Slug politics already, you might as well go the extra mile. You head back to your ship and approach, firing a warning shot upon the crowd. Once you have everyone's attention, you demand Slocknog be in charge once again. The crowd is reluctant, but the Clairvoyants remain loyal to their king and move to support him.</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event>
									<text>"Well my friend, thisss isss now the THIRD time. Heheh, I'm forever in your debt I ssssuppossse. Perhapsss thisss isss a good ssstart to repaying you."</text>
									<unlockCustomShip silent="false">PLAYER_SHIP_KNIGHT</unlockCustomShip>
									<weapon name="RANDOM"/>
									<augment name="EX_AUTO_COOLDOWN"/>
									<autoReward level="HIGH">scrap_only</autoReward>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Suggest that the Slugs hold an election the proper way - through a vote.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Surprisingly, this revolutionary idea is not immediately rejected. Persuaded by recent events, the Slugs seem to genuinely consider settling their differences and staging a government reform for the better good. However, one member of the crowd inquires, "Then what ssshall happen to Sssslocknog?"</text>
							<variable name="loc_slugdemocracy" op="set" val="1"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>We'll take him with us.</text>
								<event>
									<text>"Well, if it isss a choice between death or working aboard the sssship who hasss worked sso valiantly to assssissst me, I think I ssshall prefer not dying. Farewell to all of you, I hope you rot without me." Slocknog sharply turns and slithers onto your ship.</text>
									<variable name="ach_crew_slocknog" op="set" val="1"/>
									<crewMember amount="1" class="unique_slocknog">Slocknog</crewMember>
								</event>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Execute him.</text>
								<event>
									<text>"I- what? You have ssspent ssso much effort to help me, and yet now you ssssentence me to death?" Slocknog attempts to run, but is quickly caught by some other Slugs and dragged away. You are thanked and rewarded by the Slugs citizens who you have helped so greatly.</text>
									<upgrade amount="1" system="reactor"/>
									<autoReward level="HIGH">scrap_only</autoReward>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="KNIGHT_PALACE_RESOLUTION_NIGHTS">
	<text>As Slocknog's cruiser crashes into the lake, the fighting suddenly seems to come to a halt. You land your ship next to the Black Raven, where Nights is chuckling. "HAH! That'll ssshow that idiot what happenssss when you messs with Nightsss, baby!" Nights pumps his tentacle into the air triumphantly, and you don't bother mentioning you did all of the work.</text>
	<variable name="ach_boss_slocknog" op="set" val="1"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>You watch as the Slugs get together a team to fish the cruiser out of the lake. Once Slocknog's corpse has been recovered, he is moved to a hearse ship for later. The Slugs gather around, trying to decide how to proceed with the festival.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event>
					<text>Furious, Nights storms up to them demanding they hand back to the crown to him, but the crowd refuses. "You basssstard, you don't dessserve ssshit! Had you jussst done your duty asss a king and handled thisss asss ssomething other than an overgrown man-child, we wouldn't have the corpsssess of dozensss sssmoldering in front of the Royal palace!" Shouts someone from the crowd, shockingly appearing to be straight from Nights' inner circle.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event>
							<text>These words seem to resonate with nearly everyone present, and soon a mob has formed, marching towards Nights, demanding he be punished. The only reason no one suggests executing him is because no one has any clue who to elect in his stead.</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>These people need further influence - use a show of force to put Nights back in power.</text>
								<event>
									<text>Considering you've become so heavily involved in Slug politics already, you might as well go the extra mile. You head back to your ship and approach, firing a warning shot upon the crowd. Once you have everyone's attention, you demand Nights be in charge once again. The crowd is reluctant, but faith seems to magically return to his followers, and the Knights of Nights move to support their king. This works, and soon enough Nights is re-elected king.</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Continue...</text>
										<event>
											<text>Nights might be an egregious and irredeemable asshole in many ways, but he apparently has enough of a conscience to thank you personally. Extending the greatest show of goodwill that he can, likely to gain favor from you in case of future issues, he dispatches two guards of his inner circle to assist your mission, followed by heaps of scrap.</text>
											<crewMember amount="1" class="slug_knight"/>
											<autoReward level="HIGH">scrap_only</autoReward>
											<unlockCustomShip silent="false">PLAYER_SHIP_KNIGHT</unlockCustomShip>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Continue...</text>
												<event>
													<crewMember amount="1" class="slug_knight"/>
												</event>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Suggest that the Slugs hold an election the proper way - through a vote.</text>
								<event>
									<text>Surprisingly, this revolutionary idea is not immediately rejected. Persuaded by recent events, the Slugs seem to genuinely consider settling their differences and staging a government reform for the better good. However, one member of the crowd inquires, "Then what ssshall happen to Nightsss?"</text>
									<variable name="loc_slugdemocracy" op="set" val="1"/>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>He can work for us to pay off his debt to the galaxy.</text>
										<event>
											<text>Nights isn't eager about the idea, but the Slugs seem to find great humor in banishing him to work aboard a Federation vessel. Greatly preferring paid labor aboard a ship over public execution by disintegration ray, Nights accepts, and soon after you've got a new crew member aboard.</text>
											<variable name="ach_crew_nights" op="set" val="1"/>
											<crewMember amount="1" class="unique_nights">Nights</crewMember>
										</event>
									</choice>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Execute him.</text>
										<event>
											<text>Nights suddenly drops any show of bravery and cries out in terror, but it's too late. The crowd can't be convinced otherwise, now that the idea has been reinforced by your word. As Nights is dragged off to some underground prison, you are thanked and rewarded by the Slugs citizens who you have helped so greatly.</text>
											<upgrade amount="1" system="reactor"/>
											<autoReward level="HIGH">scrap_only</autoReward>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
</FTL>