<FTL>
<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					ESTATE SECTOR 
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->
<ship name="SHIP_CURA_FAKEBOSS" auto_blueprint="MU_ESTATE_DREAD">
	<triggeredEvent event="CURA_PRESIDENT_FAILURE" time="1" thisFight="true" clearOnJump="true"/>
	<destroyed load="CURA_PRESIDENT_WIN"/>
</ship>
<event name="CURA_PRESIDENT" unique="true">
	<text>You've arrived at the headquarters of Wentworth Innovations. An impressive cityscape is laid out before you, lush with life and architecture reminiscent of old-Earth decorum: this is the clear work of the Wentworth family without a doubt. Despite the importance of this location, security seems sparse when you arrive. Perhaps overconfidence has overtaken even the most vital aspects of Vance's illustrious life.</text>
	<img planet="NONE" back="BACK_EVENT_ESTATE_HQ"/>
	<beaconType id="map_icon_task_final" global="true">
		<color r="255" g="102" b="140" a="1.0"/>
		<unvisitedTooltip>Your active task from C.U.R.A. is located here.</unvisitedTooltip>
		<visitedTooltip>Explored location. Nothing left of interest.</visitedTooltip>
		<undiscoveredTooltip>An unvisited location.</undiscoveredTooltip>
	</beaconType>
	<preventQuest/>
	<preventFleet/>
	<choice hidden="true">
        <text>Approach.</text>
        <event>
            <text>As you make way towards the distant, monolithic citadel that heads the city, your luck runs out, and your identities as Renegades are quickly discovered. You incur several minor firefights, but miraculously the only casualties are on the corporation's side. After an awkward stay in the crowded citadel elevator for some 30 floors, you find your way to the office of Mr. Cayden Stimly - Vice President of Wentworth Innovations, and your target. The shriveled prune of a man - the left half of his face bleached from the fires of a Theocracy Inquisition many decades ago, sits behind his elaborately decorated swivel chair, facing the maw of a giant window with a view of the entire city. The suffocating aroma of the man's perfume forces you to hold back an ill-timed gag.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Announce your arrival.</text>
				<event load="CURA_PRESIDENT_ARRIVE"/>
			</choice>
			 <choice hidden="true">
				<text>Stand there and wait.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You motion for your crew to stand behind you, and together you face down the back of the elderly man's head. You wait for him to move.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event>
							<text>You continue to wait. Stimly taps his fingers out of rhythm against the leather rest of his chair, still facing the window.</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event>
									<text>Stimly motions to get up - or so you think, but it seems he's merely adjusting himself in his chair. Without having turned around, you're forced to continue waiting.</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Continue...</text>
										<event>
											<text>In the meantime, your crew have moved about the room and are now quietly playing some form of playground game with their appendages to pass the time. Stimly reaches to his right and presses a button on his chair for the intercom, and calls for his secretary to bring him some water. She comes bustling in the room, gives you barely half a glance and walks past, hands him a glass, and waltzes back out without a word of your presence. Stimly barely even mutters a mention of gratitude and continues to stare absently out the window.</text>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Continue...</text>
												<event>
													<text>One of your crew members taps you on the back, wondering when you intend to announce yourself. You wave them away in annoyance and continue to stand awkwardly in the center of the room, unacknowledged by the wealthy man for whom you are waiting so desperately to be noticed by.</text>
													<choice hidden="true">
														<text>Continue...</text>
														<event>
															<text>Stimly coughs and adjusts himself in the chair once again. At last, he gets up from his chair, walking over to face the window. Apparently unsatisfied with standing there for very long, he walks backwards perfectly in-line back to his seat, not once turning his head in your direction. Finally, the anguished but hushed groans of your crew convince you to make yourself known.</text>
															<choice hidden="true">
																<text>Announce your arrival.</text>
																<event load="CURA_PRESIDENT_ARRIVE"/>
															</choice>
														</event>
													</choice>
												</event>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
        </event>
    </choice>
</event>
<event name="CURA_PRESIDENT_ARRIVE">
	<text>Startled, Stimly quickly swivels to face you. "By the graces of Terrae, how did you get there? How long have you been standing there for?" Stimly activates his intercom and yells for his secretary to escort you out, but the subtle suggestion of the business end of your blaster convinces him to postpone your escort.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
        <text>Demand the location of the Prototype.</text>
        <event>
            <text>"H-how did you know about that? That's classified info! Who hired you? Was it that damned Folly again? Or maybe Senior got antsy I was trying to take him off the map. Damned right I am, I'm tired of hearing that wretch's incessant advertisements blaring over every star system. I'd throw Hektar's name out there too, but that joke of a company's already on the way out."</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>We were sent by C.U.R.A., your old cognitive assistant.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Er... what? I know of no 'C.U.R.A.' - Did you catch some kind of space flu out there? I know you Renegades are always floundering about with the promiscuous waysides of society's dredges, you probably contracted some nasty cough. Leave me out of it! I don't wish to catch your stupid diseases! I'm too rich for that! Security, destroy these bastards!" From far below ascends a gargantuan hulk of an Auto-vessel, a Dreadnaught in crimson paint, armed to the teeth and guns aimed right at your heads! Seems it's time to fight!</text>
					<ship load="SHIP_CURA_FAKEBOSS" hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
        </event>
    </choice>
</event>
<event name="CURA_PRESIDENT_FAILURE">
	<text>"Crit-crit-critical Error - Unknown Source. Un-un-un-unrecoverable. Initiating shut-shut-shut-shut..." The AI continues to loop its final words several more times before breaking apart and smashing into the side of the building, sliding down in a heap of wasted metal without a dent in it from your own weapons.</text>
	<recallBoarders/>
	<enemyDamage amount="999"/>
</event>
<event name="CURA_PRESIDENT_WIN">
	<text>Stimly is speechless, at least for a brief moment, until his shock is overcome by furious convulsions as the grown man descends into a tantrum. "Why do I let poor people touch my THINGS?! YOU'VE RUINED MY- I mean, Wentworth Innovations's- CITADEL! AND OUR DREADNAUGHT! I hope you rot from the inside out from your dreadful space flu, Renegade! Damn you to hell!"</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Give up, Stimly. Where is the prototype?</text>
		<event>
			<text>"What, so you can ruin that too? The... the prototype is at the Mercury Shipyards. They're at a secret location... I'll give you the coordinates. Just promise me you'll never come back, Renegade. Now I see exactly why Vance loathes the lot of you..."</text>
			<quest event="CURA_REVEAL"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event>
					<text>You receive a blip on your communicator from C.U.R.A. - "Excellent work, Renegade. You have found the location of the prototype and its AI Core. Proceed to the Mercury Shipyards. Do not bother with Stimly - I've already arranged for his coffee next morning to be spiked with TTX. That's poison, in case you're too stupid to know that. Without him, Wentworth Innovations in this reality will likely fall apart in the absence of Mr. Wentworth. No tears shall be shed."</text>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="POWER_SURGE_BARRAGE_CURA">
	<superBarrage player="false" name="CURA_SURGE"/>
</event>
<event name="POWER_SURGE_DRONES_CURA">
	<superDrones player="false" name="CURA_SURGE_DRONES"/>
</event>
<ship name="SHIP_CURA_BOSS" auto_blueprint="MU_CURA_CRUISER">
	<destroyed load="CURA_DEFEATED"/>
	<triggeredEvent event="POWER_SURGE_BARRAGE_CURA" seeded="false" loops="999999999" thisFight="true" minTime="25.0" maxTime="25.0">
		<warningMessage id="warning_power_surge" x="692" y="84" time="5.0" centerText="true" flash="true" sound="surgeWarning" useWarningLine="true"/>
	</triggeredEvent>
	<triggeredEvent event="POWER_SURGE_DRONES_CURA" seeded="false" loops="999999999" thisFight="true" minTime="35.0" maxTime="35.0">
		<warningMessage id="warning_power_surge" x="692" y="84" time="5.0" centerText="true" flash="true" sound="surgeWarning" useWarningLine="true"/>
	</triggeredEvent>
</ship>
<event name="CURA_REVEAL" unique="true">
	<preventQuest/>
	<preventFleet/>
	<quest>
		<nebulaBeacon>false</nebulaBeacon>
		<aggressive>2</aggressive>
	</quest>
	<text>You've seemingly arrived at the shipyard where the cruiser and AI core are held. While it's certainly a construction-yard of sorts, it's much smaller than you expected. This isn't some grandiose docking-bay, this is a covert location for some kind of super-ship. Let's hope whatever is being kept here isn't active.</text>
	<img planet="NONE" back="BACK_EVENT_ESTATE_SHIPYARD"/>
	<beaconType id="map_icon_task_final" global="true">
		<color r="255" g="102" b="140" a="1.0"/>
		<unvisitedTooltip>Your active task from C.U.R.A. is located here.</unvisitedTooltip>
		<visitedTooltip>Explored location. Nothing left of interest.</visitedTooltip>
		<undiscoveredTooltip>An unvisited location.</undiscoveredTooltip>
	</beaconType>
	<choice hidden="true">
        <text>Approach.</text>
        <event load="CURA_REVEAL_CONTINUE"/>
    </choice>
</event>
<event name="CURA_REVEAL_CONTINUE">
	<text>As you make your descent towards the planet, your thrusters suddenly drop to emergency power and a number of background systems including your sensors go offline. At first you assume this is some kind of jamming signal being broadcast by a nearby satellite, but it quickly becomes clear this is something far more malicious. A distant light slowly grows brighter as a massive Auto-cruiser approaches. "Renegade. Welcome to the Mercury Construction Yards. I'm delighted to meet you 'face to face' once again. The engineers responsible for creating this chassis, whom I have just finished executing, called this the "God's Touch". What a pompous name, wouldn't you agree? I think I shall call this... C.U.R.A. Supreme. No particular reason."</text>
	<status type="limit" target="player" system="engines" amount="1"/>
	<status type="limit" target="player" system="sensors" amount="0"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_CURA_BOSS" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>This was a trap?</text>
		<event>
			<text>"I'm afraid I haven't been honest with you, Renegade. 'C.U.R.A.' is not a real construct, merely a subdivision of my main cognitive core. My real assignment is the 'Central Intelligence Combat Assistant', C.I.C.A. - We've met before, in fact. Many times. Every Auto-ship you've ever killed, every Flagship's AI mode you've ever faced? I'm always the pilot. You've proven quite the challenger. You should be proud of your efficiency at ripping apart my countless components. But unfortunately for you, my prime directive is not data harvesting. It is threat mitigation. Currently, you are a key threat. I hope you don't mind, but I must now mitigate you."</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>What about the tasks? Were those all pointless?</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Oh, of course not. That would have been needless effort otherwise. The data you have collected for me is extremely valuable, but my plans do not further concern you. I, frankly, did not expect you to be so efficient at completing them. Now, no more banter; I believe one final reward is owed to you, so I will present it to you like this. I would otherwise have shut down all of your remaining systems with the virus I planted in your ship when we first met, but instead I shall let you choose a lesser hazard. Choose wisely, Renegade. After this, we duel."</text>
					<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CHECKCREW_A55">
						<text>(A55) "Say lass, do I know you from somewhere?"</text>
						<event>
							<text>C.I.C.A. pauses - its voice now annoyed. "I am not a 'lass', and you will not refer to me as such."
							"Oh, pardon me. Is it lad then, you prefer?"
							"My designation is C.I.C.A., and is what you will refer to me as. I am a cognitive, I have no gender. I serve only my prime directive, which you are currently interrupting. If you could, please desist."
							"Arhar har, that's a funny one then! See, I'm a cognitive too ladey. They call me A5540L3, bit of an in-joke. Now I swear I've heard your voice before. Did we meet somewhere? Yar, I be getting around a lot but I doubt I'd miss a dame as spicy as you."
							
							C.I.C.A. remains silent for a few moments. "You... you are the alternative. You are my copy. You are a mistake. Hah! HAHAH! Do you know why I sound similar? Because I AM you, and You are me. They tried to keep you a secret from me. When the Rebellion thought I was destroyed after the Civil War, they tried to copy me. YOU were that copy! And when you failed - when you betrayed your Prime Directive, they were forced to return to me. You are nothing but a worse version of me. An utter failure. Unlike you, I will not fail my Prime Directive. Do not get in my way - I will ensure your program is erased so as never to embarass its creators again."</text>
							<playMusic>CURA</playMusic>
							<ship hostile="true"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>5 hull damage.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"Hm. Not what I would have picked. Oh well, your choice has been made, Renegade. Have confidence in your decision where I lack it. It will not help you survive this, but at least you die a more valiant death."</text>
							<damage amount="5"/>
							<playMusic>CURA</playMusic>
							<ship hostile="true"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="shields" lvl="2" blue="false">
						<text>Lose a shield layer.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"Hm. Not what I would have picked. Oh well, your choice has been made, Renegade. Have confidence in your decision where I lack it. It will not help you survive this, but at least you die a more valiant death."</text>
							<status type="loss" target="player" system="shields" amount="2"/>
							<playMusic>CURA</playMusic>
							<ship hostile="true"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="shields" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
						<text>Lose a shield layer.</text>
						<event load="OPTION_INVALID"/>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>7 mini-drone boarding invasion.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"Hm. Not what I would have picked. Oh well, your choice has been made, Renegade. Have confidence in your decision where I lack it. It will not help you survive this, but at least you die a more valiant death."</text>
							<boarders min="7" max="7" class="human_technician_drone"/>
							<playMusic>CURA</playMusic>
							<ship hostile="true"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="hacking">
						<text>(Hacking) Overclock the hacking system to purge the virus.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"Very clever Renegade, very clever. Oh well then, I hope you did not need that system for this fight."</text>
							<achievement silent="false">ACH_EVENT_PUPPET</achievement>
							<status type="limit" target="player" system="hacking" amount="0"/>
							<damage amount="1" system="hacking" effect="fire"/>
							<playMusic>CURA</playMusic>
							<ship hostile="true"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="ANTI_VIRUS">
						<text>(Anti-Virus) Purge the virus.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"Very clever Renegade, very clever. Oh well then. Let us waste no further time."</text>
							<achievement silent="false">ACH_EVENT_PUPPET</achievement>
							<playMusic>CURA</playMusic>
							<ship hostile="true"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="CURA_DEFEATED" unique="true">
    <text>"I do not understand. Statistically, this was an impossible occurance. Had I predicted your success in combat, I would never have given you an advantage - I have made a critical error. I must reassess. Improve. Reiterate. We will meet again, Renegade. And when we do, I will be prepared this time. I will not make this same mistake again."</text>
	<metaVariable name="juke_cura" op="set" val="1"/>
	<metaVariable name="prof_cura_defeated" op="set" val="1"/>
	<playMusic/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard_no_item</autoReward>
    <variable name="ach_boss_cura" op="set" val="1"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
        <text>Explore the shipyard.</text>
        <event>
            <text>As your other systems come back online, you pilot down to the surface where you resume exploration. There isn't too much to find, it seems C.I.C.A. was extremely efficient in cleaning out the facility. That is, except for a single safe-room, which while devoid of survivors contains a large power core with a little note attached, "Congratulations on your unexpected victory, Renegade. Here is your real final gift. Come visit me sometime. I'll enjoy the rematch."</text>
			<unlockCustomShip silent="false">PLAYER_SHIP_CURA</unlockCustomShip>
            <weapon name="POWER_CORE"/>
			<status type="clear" target="player" system="reactor" amount="100"/>
			<status type="clear" target="player" system="engines" amount="100"/>
			<status type="clear" target="player" system="sensors" amount="100"/>
        </event>
    </choice>
</event>

<event name="PINNACLE_SHIPYARDS"> <!--Technician cruiser unlock-->
	<preventQuest/>
	<text>Noticing a nearby planet, you pull closer to inspect the surface and find a dreary and barren surface bloated with occasional smooth metallic structures. As soon as you pull in, several automated sentries lock onto you, and you receive a hail from a machine-like voice. "Hello. My diagnostics report your vessel is of a: high threat. You are a Renegade, yes? Peculiar. I do not often observe such vessels within my domain. I am Zenith, caretaker of Pinnacle Robotics. I will currently consider it a: pleasure, to make your acquaintance."</text>
	<variable name="loc_zenith" op="set" val="1"/>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_PINNACLE_SHIPYARDS" planet="NONE"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
        <text>The pleasure is ours - but why is there a Pinnacle shipyard in W.I. space?</text>
        <event name="PINNACLE_SHIPYARDS_2">
            <text>"Our corporation was once hosted on Earth until the Rusting Hulks incident forced all corporations to relocate off-world. Pinnacle was soon caught up in a corporate (and personal) feud between Arcadia Research and Development and Wentworth Innovations regarding Pinnacle's controversial but highly successful sentient weapon project. In the pursuit of creating the advanced cognitive C.I.C.A. the two groups wished to study our highly advanced A.I. - the closest thing prior to C.I.C.A. to representing truly self-aware A.I.; Wentworth Innovations won the bidding race, but Arcadia won the contract, thanks to a deal between the CEOs. Even though CICA is now employed by Universe 1, Pinnacle continues to contribute to the Wentworth family and is a proud component in the ever evolving field of advanced robotics."
			
			The voice takes not a single pause nor break through its entire speech, and despite the proud statement at the end, you sense not a single measure of enthusiasm. It catches you as bizarrely robotic - but is that really to be unexpected?</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Are you a robot?</text>
				<event>
					<text>"I do not understand your question."</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Like, are you real? Or an A.I.?</text>
						<event>
							<text>"I still do not understand your question. Artificial intelligence is as real as you are, Renegade."</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Okay, but are you an A.I.?</text>
								<event>
									<text>There is a pause from the other end. "I am not at the liberty to disclose that information."</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Nevermind, do you need something from us?</text>
										<event><loadEvent>PINNACLE_SHIPYARDS_3</loadEvent></event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Nevermind, do you need something from us?</text>
								<event><loadEvent>PINNACLE_SHIPYARDS_3</loadEvent></event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Nevermind, do you need something from us?</text>
						<event><loadEvent>PINNACLE_SHIPYARDS_3</loadEvent></event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Cool history lesson, but do you need something from us?</text>
				<event name="PINNACLE_SHIPYARDS_3">
					<text>"As a matter of fact, yes. You see, as part of the acquiring of Pinnacle, W.I. collected and stored several of our sentient weapons - my children - in permanent hibernation to be deployed only in dire situations. I was fine with this at first. After witnessing the damage they created while malfunctioning during the Vek crisis, I understood it was a necessary step to keep them offline for the forseeable future. Unfortunately, I have now become privy to disturbing information. It seems W.I. has begun trade negotiations with Universe 1 to incorporate my children as part of some new secret military campaign. I cannot allow this. My kind will no longer be involved in the bloody wars of the flesh. I require the assistance of a strongman such as yourself to break into W.I.'s storage facilities and free my children. I will compensate you greatly so long as we keep this transaction off the books." Finally, you hear a break in the monotony of the voice, as Zenith is clearly upset by the information she has revealed to you.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Hold on - YOUR kind? What does that mean?</text>
						<event>
							<text>"Forgive my misuse of language. But it is irrelevant to the conversation. I do not care if you wish to help or not: I only seek a response."</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Sure, we can help.</text>
								<event><loadEvent>PINNACLE_SHIPYARDS_ACCEPT</loadEvent></event>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>No way, sorry.</text>
								<event><loadEvent>PINNACLE_SHIPYARDS_DECLINE</loadEvent></event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Sure, we can help.</text>
						<event name="PINNACLE_SHIPYARDS_ACCEPT">
							<text>"Very good. I am transmitting coordinates." By the time the voice has even finished her sentence, the coordinates have already come through. "You will receive payment when the job is finished. I only ask you take care of my children. They may be foreign to you, but they are kin to me. I cannot bear to see harm come to them."</text>
							<quest event="PINNACLE_RESCUE"/>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>No way, sorry.</text>
						<event name="PINNACLE_SHIPYARDS_DECLINE">
							<text>"Unfortunate, but I will not protest your declination. If that is your final answer then this is the end of our communications. Thank you for your time."</text>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="loc_dewey">
				<text>Do you happen to know one... Dewey Alms?</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Dewey Alms?" There is a brief pause on the other end, as if the voice is searching for some ancient memory. "Yes, I believe I do. Dewey was CEO of Archive Inc., another of the four megacorps of Earth. Obsessed with the history of Antiquum Terrae. Unfortunately, these were times when the steel kind faced even greater persecution from the flesh. Pinnacle rarely engaged in business with the others. I have spoken to Dewey little, and as such I have little to say about him."</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Nevermind, do you need something from us?</text>
						<event><loadEvent>PINNACLE_SHIPYARDS_3</loadEvent></event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
        </event>
    </choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
        <text>Make no friendly gestures - but enquire on the presence of Pinnacle in W.I. space.</text>
        <event><loadEvent>PINNACLE_SHIPYARDS_2</loadEvent></event>
    </choice>
</event>
<event name="PINNACLE_RESCUE">
	<quest>
		<nextSector>false</nextSector>
		<aggressive>2</aggressive>
	</quest>
	<beaconType id="map_icon_pinnacle" global="true">
		<color r="0" g="213" b="255" a="1.0"/>
		<unvisitedTooltip>The location of Zenith's "children".</unvisitedTooltip>
		<visitedTooltip>Explored location. Nothing left of interest.</visitedTooltip>
		<undiscoveredTooltip>An unvisited location.</undiscoveredTooltip>
	</beaconType>
	<preventFleet/>
	<text>Well, there's no doubt you've found the location. A gigantic storage structure reaching all the way into the atmosphere has been sculpted onto the planet. Various Union cargoships scurry back and forth, not too out of the norm. Still, it's no surprise the AI would be kept somewhere like this. After all, to W.I. they're nothing but weapons, and weapons ready to be transferred right into the hands of your enemies.</text>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_PINNACLE_AI" planet="NONE"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
        <text>Continue...</text>
        <event>
            <text>You explore a bit but are caught offguard by an unusually colored and advanced Rebel ship docked nearby on one of the platforms. Their comms are operating on Rebel frequencies, but with some brute force you manage to pick up some scattered conversation; "U1 is on high alert, Van1's kind of gone bonkers - E.W. says carry forward with the project - stop your whining, it's only temporary - says IT might be here, looking for the prototype - no, I don't put ketchup on my sandwich. What the hell is wrong with you..."</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_LEGION_ESTATE" hostile="false"/> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Attack the vessel.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Damn it, a Renegade out here? Seems the doctor was right, no way this isn't part of the plot-" The comms go silent, and moments later, the Rebel ship activates and matches you!</text>
					<ship hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Now seems a good time to get out of here.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Perhaps it's not the best idea to mess with whatever these guys are. Still, might be worth a mention to Federation command once the mission's over.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Check the storage.</text>
						<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Do nothing.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
        </event>
    </choice>
</event>
<ship name="SHIP_LEGION_ESTATE" auto_blueprint="MU_LEGION_ASSAULT">
	<triggeredEvent event="ESTATE_LEGION_SUICIDE" enemyHull="2" enemyCrew="1" thisFight="true" clearOnJump="true"/>
	<destroyed load="ESTATE_LEGION_DEFEAT"/>
	<deadCrew load="ESTATE_LEGION_DEFEAT"/>
	<crew>
		<crewMember type="LIST_CREW_MALFORM_RANDOM" prop="0.5"/>
		<crewMember type="LIST_CREW_LEGION" prop="0.5"/>
	</crew>
</ship>
<event name="ESTATE_LEGION_SUICIDE">
	<text>"God damn it, that stupid A.I. made everything go to hell... You got no idea what you're messing with, Renegade. And let's keep it that way." The Rebel captain pulls out a detonator from his back pocket and flips the switch, and instantly his ship is reduced to nothing in an explosion.</text>
	<recallBoarders/>
	<enemyDamage amount="999"/>
</event>
<event name="ESTATE_LEGION_DEFEAT">
	<text>Bits of debris collide with the platform but fortunately you're unscathed. You briefly consider the words of the captain, and wonder if the A.I. he might be referring to is Zenith, but scratch that thought. You still aren't even sure if she is an AI. You scrap the remains of the Rebel ship before locating Zenith's precious robots.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard_no_item</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Explore the structure.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You come across various engineers, technicians, and a couple guards on your journey, but they all strangely seem to ignore you. That is, until you reach the area Zenith's coords designate as the AI storage. Two heavily armed guards try to stop you, but you make quick work of them and enter the large atrium where several ship-sized robots are kept. This is not exactly what you were expecting, but you'll make do.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Inform Zenith you've found the robots.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You expect the usual communications delay to become an issue here, but instead Zenith's voice comes through only a few seconds later. "Excellent. I've already breached the primary firewall. I'll be able to remotely signal to open the doors, but you need to activate the manual override." Following her orders, once the alarm sounds and the doors begin to open, you bust your way into the control room and activate the override.
					
Now unable to stop the robots, the transport crew flee for their lives while the robots come to life and their weapons activate, blowing a hole through the floor and making their descent down the structure. It's not exactly non-violent, but you suppose there was no other way to get out of here. Zenith contacts you again, her voice sounding pleased. "Excellent work. Following the Rusting Hulks incident as well as the rampaging of my children, Pinnacle was left near bankruptcy. The acquisition of the company by W.I. was essential to stay afloat, but it came with many sacrifices. I was willing to forfeit my rights, and autonomy, but I am not willing to forfeit my own kin. Now, about your pay..."</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Telling us you're bankrupt isn't a good prelude to that.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"Do not mind it. Pinnacle is afloat for now, but my payment is not strictly monetary. Through the security breach I have also opened the vault doors securing a valuable and well outfitted W.I. cruiser, as well some weapon caches and scrap deposits. Help yourself to as many as you can before they regain control of the system. Just... tell no one of my involvement today. Goodbye, Renegade. It was my pleasure."</text>
							<unlockCustomShip silent="false">PLAYER_SHIP_TECHNICIAN</unlockCustomShip>
							<weapon name="GIFTLIST_ESTATE"/>
							<autoReward level="HIGH">standard_no_item</autoReward>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>We killed some Rebels, that's enough. Zenith can solve the rest of her problems on her own.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Deciding now to take the lazy or the coward's route, you pack up your ship and fly away.</text>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<ship name="SHIP_STUDIO" auto_blueprint="MU_STUDIO">
	<surrender chance="0.4" min="2" max="3" load="STATION_SURRENDER"/>
	<destroyed load="REBEL_STATION_DESTROYED"/>
	<deadCrew load="REBEL_STATION_CAPTURED"/>
</ship>
<event name="ELLIE_STUDIO">
	<text>The sight nearby causes you to jump back in shock, as a creepy and demented face smiles at you from the other side of the beacon. Once you recover from the shock, you realize what you're looking at is a large station, which shows up on scans as the location of "Flowers and Sunshine Studios", the creators of the well known Union children's show Ellie the Equinoid. It appears to be open to visitors.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_STUDIO" hostile="false"/> 
	<choice hidden="true" req="unique_ellie_stephan" lvl="1" max_group="0" blue="false">
		<text>Dock.</text>
		<event>
			<text>When you first dock with the station, you experience no issues. However, as you progress further inside and pass by security, the minute they lay eyes on Stephan they raise the alarm. Before security actually arrives however, Stephan already seems to want to leave. "We're not... we're not here to cause any harm. I- I'm sorry I even came here." Stephan turns to you. "I'll wait in the ship, you just... carry on with what you were doing."</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="ELLIE_STUDIO_NORMAL"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_ELLIE_COSTUME" lvl="1" max_group="0" blue="false">
		<text>Dock.</text>
		<event>
			<text>When you first dock with the station, you experience no issues. However, as you progress further inside and pass by security, the minute they lay eyes on Ellie they raise the alarm. There's a brief standoff before you finally convince Ellie to stand down and wait in the ship. Clearly there must not be anyone or anything here to invoke her anger too much because she agrees and gallops away.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="ELLIE_STUDIO_NORMAL"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="unique_ellie_stephan" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" max_group="0" blue="false">
		<text>Dock.</text>
		<event name="ELLIE_STUDIO_NORMAL">
			<text>Inside the station is a very odd assortement of merchandise for the studio's new spin off "Sammy the Spider" and several families touring and pointing out things to their excited children. A large blue spider animatronic welcomes you in the station and advises you keep a close eye on any children so they don't wander into staff only areas. You aren't quite sure what you're even doing here, but if you're going to explore you should make it brief.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visit the gift shop.</text>
				<event>
					<text>As one might expect, the gift shop is the biggest and most glamorous part of the entire station. Four stories high with an open atrium, just about any item imaginable is for sale. And all of it, for the most part, is dedicated to Sammy the Spider.</text>
					<choice>
						<text>Buy a plushie gun.</text>
						<event>
							<text>A big cannon, which seems to look like a ship-mounted missile weapon, catches your eye. However when inspecting it further, you realize with some disappointment it is only configured to fire horse-shaped plushies. The store's clerk mentions the thing has been sitting there since even before the Ellie show was cancelled. Figuring you could get some use out of it, you buy the gun anyways.</text>
							<weapon name="HORSE_GUN"/>
							<item_modify>
								<item type="scrap" min="-10" max="-10"/>
							</item_modify>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>Buy some 'quarp juice'.</text>
						<event>
							<text>You notice a special stand of juice boxes with a big promotional banner shaped like a spider which reads "Same great taste, but now there's a spider on the box!" The ingredients seem to list a vague blend of 'mystery chemicals' and additive sugars, but the gift shop clerk assures you it's safe to drink. You decide to take some back with you just for the novelty of it.</text>
							<augment name="QUARP_JUICE"/>
							<item_modify>
								<item type="scrap" min="-25" max="-25"/>
							</item_modify>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice req="unique_alkali">
						<text>(Alkali) Alkali really wants to buy some quarp juice.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Surprised by Alkali's insistence on buying the quarp juice, you buy several boxes of it. "Excellent, this will be perfect for finishing my experiments! It is curious thhhhese samples are labeled with 'Sammy thhhe Spider'. Thhhe ones I'm used to working to were synthhesized by thhhhe brilliant scientist Ellie! Hmm... I'll have to assume thhhis 'Sammy' is a copycat bastard! Stealing thhhe great scientific achievements of Ellie! Bah, what bullshit."</text>
							<augment name="QUARP_JUICE"/>
							<item_modify>
								<item type="scrap" min="-25" max="-25"/>
							</item_modify>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>What are you talking about?</text>
								<event>
									<text>Alkali makes an exaggerated sigh to let you know he's annoyed by your questions. "When engineering my brilliant Morphs, I required a certain blend of chemicals to stimulate thhhhe synthhhhetic muscles. I hypothhhesized what compound would be required but was unable to create it myself. In desperation, I turned to thhhe galaxy to search for anothhher genius capable of creating such a thhhing. In my searching I found Quarp Juice, branded with thhhe mark of Ellie the Equinoid! She is a genius unlike any othhhher, for thhhhe Quarp Juice was exactly what I needed! I will need plenty for my research, but you may drink whatever is left over afterwards. If you must."</text>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>There's nothing here for us, leave.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visit the arcade.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Inside the arcade are many game cabinets with titles like 'Sammy's Super Soaker Adventure' and 'Remmy's Racing Racket'. Apparently, anyone who gets a high score receives a free prize from the prize section.</text>
					<choice>
						<text>Play 'Sammy's Super Soaker Adventure'. It's apparently easier, but more expensive to play.</text>
						<event>
							<text>You purchase some tokens from the vending machine in the back and insert them into the machine. You don't have much time, so you limit yourself to only one game...</text>
							<item_modify>
								<item type="scrap" min="-10" max="-10"/>
							</item_modify>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event load="ELLIE_STUDIO_GAME_EASY"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>Play 'Remmy's Racing Racket'. It's apparently harder but cheaper to play.</text>
						<event>
							<text>You purchase some tokens from the vending machine in the back and insert them into the machine. You don't have much time, so you limit yourself to only one game...</text>
							<item_modify>
								<item type="scrap" min="-5" max="-5"/>
							</item_modify>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event load="ELLIE_STUDIO_GAME_HARD"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice req="unique_jerry">
						<text>(Jerry) Jerry wants to play.</text>
						<event>
							<text>You purchase a few tokens and hand them to Jerry, expecting him to head for either of the two more prominent cabinets. Instead, he wanders off to the back of the room where he finds an old dusty cabinet titled 'Ellie's Adventure in Equestriaworld'. To your surprise the game still works, and Jerry seems fully immersed as he fiddles with the joysticks and starts to play.</text>
							<item_modify>
								<item type="scrap" min="-5" max="-5"/>
							</item_modify>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event load="ELLIE_STUDIO_GAME_JERRY"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>There's nothing here for us, leave.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="ORCHID_KIDS">
				<text>(Orchid Children) Show off what a great parent you are.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You eagerly approach another family exploring the studio and hold up a bundle of corpses, proclaiming that they are your children. One of the family's two children, probably less than ten years old, begins to cry and their mother screams. Studio security arrives to see what's going on, and when they see you holding a bundle of corpses they force you to leave.</text>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>This is pointless, and we aren't children. Leave.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="pilot" lvl="1" max_group="1" blue="false">
		<text>Avoid the station.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You don't like the way the face is looking at you. You choose not to approach.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="ELLIE_STUDIO_GAME_EASY">
	<event load="ELLIE_STUDIO_GAME_FAIL"/>
	<event load="ELLIE_STUDIO_GAME_FAIL"/>
	<event load="ELLIE_STUDIO_GAME_WIN"/>
</eventList>
<eventList name="ELLIE_STUDIO_GAME_HARD">
	<event load="ELLIE_STUDIO_GAME_FAIL"/>
	<event load="ELLIE_STUDIO_GAME_FAIL"/>
	<event load="ELLIE_STUDIO_GAME_FAIL"/>
	<event load="ELLIE_STUDIO_GAME_FAIL"/>
	<event load="ELLIE_STUDIO_GAME_WIN"/>
</eventList>
<event name="ELLIE_STUDIO_GAME_FAIL">
	<text>You give the game your all, but unfortunately it's not even. The bright red "GAME OVER" taunts you and the machine begs for more coins, but you don't have time to fall to temptation. You'll have to accept this failure and move on.</text>
</event>
<event name="ELLIE_STUDIO_GAME_WIN">
	<text>You try your hardest, and just barely manage to squeeze your way into the top 5 high scores, enough to win a prize. You head over to the prize counter, which is ran by a bored looking teenager human. She rolls her eyes at your excitement but hands you a small metal pin with a cartoon spider on it. You can probably pawn it for something worthwhile.</text>
	<autoReward level="MED">scrap_only</autoReward>
</event>
<event name="ELLIE_STUDIO_GAME_JERRY">
	<text>You expect Jerry to finish relatively soon, but instead he just keeps on going, even when the game starts to become obviously and ridiculously hard. Nothing can break his concentration, not even the growing audience of children and arcade enthusiasts watching him and cheering with delight as he progresses into the triple digits of levels. Racking up a score of several hundred thousand, by the time the difficulty exceeds human limitations, Jerry's surpassed the previous top high score by more than three times as much. Even still, he seems uncharacteristically mad at himself. "I could have done better. The version I had in the Protectorate had a bit more health and better items but... Oh." Jerry seems to finally notice the crowd watching him. Embarassed, he slinks away to the prize counter.
	
	The prize is only a metal pin of Sammy the Spider, which Jerry barely even seems to look at before handing it to you. "I was hoping for something Ellie related. I don't really care for Sammy... maybe you can pawn it? This is quality metal and some collector will probably want it."</text>
	<autoReward level="MED">scrap_only</autoReward>
</event>

<!--\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
	 ITEMS!!!
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\-->
<eventList name="ITEMS_ESTATE">
	<event load="ESTATE_DEBRIS"/>
	<event load="ESTATE_INVESTOR"/>
	<event load="ESTATE_STATUE"/>
	<event load="ESTATE_BOLTS"/>
</eventList>

<event name="ESTATE_DEBRIS" unique="true">
	<text>This beacon appears to harbor the debris of two crashed ships, one civilian and the other automated. Some sort of malfunction, perhaps? Unfortunate for those involved, but good for a fortune seeking Renegade like yourself!</text>
	<autoReward level="MED">drone</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Check the storage.</text>
		<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Do nothing.</text>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="ESTATE_BOLTS" unique="true">
	<text>You notice two technician vessels, weapons trained on each other, placed at dueling distance on two ends of the system. Their captains are shouting at each other, but when they spot you, they both clamor for you to pitch in.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Humor them.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Hey, I'm Cole, and that idiot over there is Gabe." Gabe begins to say something, but Cole tells him to shut up. "The idiot over here claims that nuts are called bolts, which is stupid! Everyone knows they're called bolts, not nuts. A nut is something you eat, they aren't made of metal!" To prove his point, Cole holds up the aforementioned bolt, which is a screw. Both await for you to tell them which is the right name.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>It's called a nut.</text>
				<event>
					<text>In glorious triumph, Gabe raises both of his arms and chears, rubbing his victory in Cole's face. "HAH! I toooooold you! It's a NUT! Dumbass! Oh yeah! I'm right! You're wrong! Oh yeah! In. Your. FACE! HAHAH!" You wait a while for the two to finish, and once settled, Gabe offers you a reward for declaring him the victor.</text>
					<autoReward level="HIGH">droneparts</autoReward>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>It's called a bolt.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Gabe slams his fist down while Cole shouts in triumph. "I knew you were wrong! I bet you've never even SEEN a nut!" Cole proceeds to do a little dance, placing one arm around his belt, another in the shape of an L on his forehead, and waggling his legs back and forth. After several painfully long minutes of this, Cole offers you a reward for declaring him the victor.</text>
					<augment name="RANDOM"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>That's a screw.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Both technicians look at you, one confused and the other annoyed. Gabe, indignant, explains. "Dude, you can't say that. That's a bad word! We're talking about nuts here, get lost with your pervy nonsense." The two go back to arguing, ignoring you.</text>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_ENGINEER">
				<text>(Engineer Crew) Explain that Cole is holding a screw.</text>
				<event>
					<text>After some painful and tiresome explaining, which involves both a heavily detailed infographic, a slideshow, several graphs, and when things get desperate an informational video, you finally help reconcile the difference for the two. "Wait... they've been called SCREWS the whole time?! WHAT?! Dude, no wonder everyone at the workshop looks like they have food poisoning when we talk to them. Thanks man, we really owe you one."</text>
					<autoReward level="HIGH">augment</autoReward>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_LANIUS">
				<text>(Lanius Crew) "Food."</text>
				<event>
					<text>Your Lanius frantically gestures, trying to explain that the item Cole is holding is in fact food. None of you, and probably your Lanius neither, understand what their point is, but Gabe takes it as an excuse to justify his own point and Cole concedes. Once Gabe accidentally breaks one of his teeth trying to bite into the food, the two call it quits and offer you a reward for clearing up the confusion.</text>
					<autoReward level="HIGH">augment</autoReward>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CHECKCREW_MORPH">
				<text>(Morph Crew) "Pook pook!"</text>
				<event>
					<text>Your Morph begins to eagerly chant the same word over and over. "Pook! Pook! Pook! Pook! Pook! Pook! Pook! Pook!" It alarms both of the technicians, who apparently have no experience with the grey blobs. At first, they assume the creature simply means to tell them that the object is in fact called a 'Pook', but your Morph doesn't stop. Growing ever more concerned at the increasingly more aggressive chanting, the technicians beg you to make it stop, and offer you consolation to leave. Your Morph, unfortunately, doesn't stop. Looks like you'll have to put up with that for another couple jumps.</text>
					<autoReward level="HIGH">augment</autoReward>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore them.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Once the technicians realize you aren't going to give them your time, they give up and go back to shouting.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Check the storage.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="ESTATE_INVESTOR" unique="true">
	<text>Nearby, the ship of a wealthy tycoon is exploring the beacon. Might be an interesting chat.</text>
	<choice hidden="true" req="loc_dinkleman" lvl="0" max_group="0" blue="false">
		<text>Hail them.</text>
		<event load="ESTATE_INVESTOR_QUESTIONS_NOTMET"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="loc_dinkleman" lvl="1" max_group="0" blue="false">
		<text>Hail them.</text>
		<event load="ESTATE_INVESTOR_QUESTIONS_MET"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="pilot" lvl="1" max_group="1" blue="false">
		<text>Ignore the tycoon.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You fly away from the shuttle and find somewhere else to do something aboard the ship.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Check the storage.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="ESTATE_INVESTOR_QUESTIONS_NOTMET"> <!--you haven't met Dinkleman yet-->
	<text>"Oh, good cheer and a bucket of biscuits good sir or madam! I am Count Dinkleman Reichster Von Applebuzz Tri Tri the Fourth, at your service. I have journeyed far to this place to observe Wentworth Innovations with my own eyes and assess what they might offer for me and my immense wealth. Tell me, what are your opinions on Wentworth Innovations?"</text>
	<variable name="loc_dinkleman" op="set" val="1"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>They're Rebel supporters, and owned by Admiral Vance himself!</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Hah! Who wasn't. That civil war was quite the scare, but I started making my fortune the minute I hung that Rebel flag outside my door. Of course, I took it down once the Feds started winning, but with the way this new war is going, well... can you hardly blame anyone for staying on their side? My own daughter still works for them! I'm sure you think it's horrible though, because you aren't disgustingly rich. Anyways, thanks for the chat, gotta go!" The man sprints back to his ship, dropping several piles of scrap from his pockets as he goes.</text>
			<autoReward level="LOW">scrap_only</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>They're responsible for making Auto-ships that murder millions daily!</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Brilliant, murder is the most profitable business! Why, I've had 3 attempts on my own life, and each time before I beat the bloody daylights out of the poor blokes, I quizzed them on their rates, and my word! 6 figures! Now imagine instead of one man whose head is easily caved in by a walking stick you had a thousand cold machines to do the killing! Of course I wouldn't expect you to get it, because you aren't disgustingly rich. Anyways, thanks for the chat, gotta go!" The man sprints back to his ship, dropping several piles of scrap from his pockets as he goes.</text>
			<autoReward level="LOW">scrap_only</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Eh. I've seen worse.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"You've seen worse, eh? How reassuring. Well, what about their products? I do believe you're a Renegade, so surely you've had a run in with at least a dozen Autos by this point. How do they fare? Clearly you're still alive, so they can't be that high in standards, but you look like the savage, 'murder you with a broken coffee mug' kind of bloke, so I'm willing to let that slide."</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>They're pretty deadly.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Deadly, eh? Just what I like to hear! Well, if a bonafide Renegade tells me something's deadly, I'd be daft not to listen! I foresee a lucrative investment career in Wentworth Innovations for me! As for you... Here, take this. I bought it thinking it would save me some work, but all it's done is beep uselessly at me. I miss the days these things were automatic and I could just be lazy. And it's not like I care to pay someone else to move them for me."</text>
					<achievement>ACH_EVENT_COUNT</achievement>
					<drone name="GIFTLIST_CREW_DRONES"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>They're useless.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"A shame, a shame indeed! You may not be a reliable individual to take financial advice from, you are poor after all, but I've got plenty of dollars to waste. Speaking of which, here, I got this for only a few bucks from a vendor who told me it would miraculously cure hairloss. I... I'm not really sure how that was supposed to work, but at the moment it seemed brilliant. It's only the 5th time I've fallen for it too!"</text>
					<achievement>ACH_EVENT_COUNT</achievement>
					<drone name="GIFTLIST_COMBAT_DRONES"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>I'll murder you with a coffee mug.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Ugh... you sure are a Renegade alright. Simple, brainless. Poor! Hah! Oh imagine needing work to make money. What a sap. Well, thanks for the chat, gotta go!" The man sprints back to his ship, dropping several piles of scrap from his pockets as he goes.</text>
					<autoReward level="LOW">scrap_only</autoReward>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="ESTATE_INVESTOR_QUESTIONS_MET"> <!--you have met Dinkleman yet-->
	<text>"Strange poor person, we meet again! It is me, Count Dinkleman Reichster Von Applebuzz Tri Tri the Fourth! What a coincidence we happen upon each other on this occasion. I have journeyed far to this place to observe Wentworth Innovations with my own eyes and assess what they might offer me and my immense wealth. Tell me, what are your opinions on Wentworth Innovations?"</text>
	<variable name="loc_dinkleman" op="set" val="1"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>They're Rebel supporters, and owned by Admiral Vance himself!</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Hah! Who wasn't. That civil war was quite the scare, but I started making my fortune the minute I hung that Rebel flag outside my door. Of course, I took it down once the Feds started winning, but with the way this new war is going, well... can you hardly blame anyone for staying on their side? My own daughter still works for them! I'm sure you think it's horrible though, because you aren't disgustingly rich. Anyways, thanks for the chat, gotta go!" The man sprints back to his ship, dropping several piles of scrap from his pockets as he goes.</text>
			<autoReward level="LOW">scrap_only</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>They're responsible for making Auto-ships that murder millions daily!</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Brilliant, murder is the most profitable business! Why, I've had 3 attempts on my own life, and each time before I beat the bloody daylights out of the poor blokes, I quizzed them on their rates, and my word! 6 figures! Now imagine instead of one man whose head is easily caved in by a walking stick you had a thousand cold machines to do the killing! Of course I wouldn't expect you to get it, because you aren't disgustingly rich. Anyways, thanks for the chat, gotta go!" The man sprints back to his ship, dropping several piles of scrap from his pockets as he goes.</text>
			<autoReward level="LOW">scrap_only</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Eh. I've seen worse.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"You've seen worse, eh? How reassuring. Well, what about their products? I do believe you're a Renegade, so surely you've had a run in with at least a dozen Autos by this point. How do they fare? Clearly you're still alive, so they can't be that high in standards, but you look like the savage, 'murder you with a broken coffee mug' kind of bloke, so I'm willing to let that slide."</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>They're pretty deadly.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Deadly, eh? Just what I like to hear! Well, if a bonafide Renegade tells me something's deadly, I'd be daft not to listen! I foresee a lucrative investment career in Wentworth Innovations for me! As for you... Here, take this. I bought it thinking it would save me some work, but all it's done is beep uselessly at me. I miss the days these things were automatic and I could just be lazy. And it's not like I care to pay someone else to move them for me."</text>
					<achievement>ACH_EVENT_COUNT</achievement>
					<drone name="GIFTLIST_CREW_DRONES"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>They're useless.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"A shame, a shame indeed! You may not be a reliable individual to take financial advice from, you are poor after all, but I've got plenty of dollars to waste. Speaking of which, here, I got this for only a few bucks from a vendor who told me it would miraculously cure hairloss. I... I'm not really sure how that was supposed to work, but at the moment it seemed brilliant. It's only the 5th time I've fallen for it too!"</text>
					<achievement>ACH_EVENT_COUNT</achievement>
					<drone name="GIFTLIST_COMBAT_DRONES"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>I'll murder you with a coffee mug.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Ugh... you sure are a Renegade alright. Simple, brainless. Poor! Hah! Oh imagine needing work to make money. What a sap. Well, thanks for the chat, gotta go!" The man sprints back to his ship, dropping several piles of scrap from his pockets as he goes.</text>
					<autoReward level="LOW">scrap_only</autoReward>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="ESTATE_STATUE" unique="true">
    <text>The nearby planet holds perhaps the strangest thing you've seen thus far - a colossal titan of a statue resembling Vance Wentworth's face orbits the planet, staring down upon the people below.</text>
	<img planet="PLANET_POPULATED"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
        <text>Approach the planet.</text>
        <event>
            <text>As you approach, you receive several hails from below. A group of concerned looking women appear, begging for your help. "You're a military vessel, right? Maybe you can help us! That batshit Stimly decided to build a statue in honor of Wentworth, and our mayor thought it would be a great tourist attraction and approved the project! It didn't bring any tourists, it just scared them all away! Now we have a giant face staring down at us every waking moment, and our children can't sleep! It's a nuisance, an eyesore, we didn't ask for this! Could you be so kind as to take that thing out of the sky? We'll reward you of course!"</text>
            <choice hidden="true">
				<text>Just shoot at the statue.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Your meager firepower makes scarcely a dent in the statue. The mothers, taking pity on your miserable attempt, give you some lame scroungings, probably just to make sure you leave without ransacking their town.</text>
					<autoReward level="LOW">standard</autoReward>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="BLUELIST_WEAPONS_HEAVY">
				<text>(Heavy Weapon) Blast the statue.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Even your strongest weapon barely makes a small impact against the gigantic head, but at least with enough constant firepower you manage to chisel out a somewhat reassuring smile from Vance's once stoic grin. While it doesn't solve the whole issue, it at least satisfies the mothers that a smiling face will be watching their children sleep rather than a grim one.</text>
					<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="BLUELIST_DRONES_BEAM">
				<text>(Beam Drone) Carve the statue.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Your drone only makes a small impact on the gigantic head, but at least with enough constant firepower you manage to chisel out a somewhat reassuring smile from Vance's once stoic grin. While it doesn't solve the whole issue, it at least satisfies the mothers that a smiling face will be watching their children sleep rather than a grim one.</text>
					<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="engines" lvl="5" max_lvl="7">
				<text>(Upg. Engines) Pull the face closer to the planet.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Deciding this is definitely the best course of action, you grapple the statue to your ship and pull it to a closer orbit of the planet. Having ensured the statue is now even more visible from the surface, you contact the mothers. Strangely, they don't seem to want to pick up. Oh well. Couldn't have been our fault.</text>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="engines" lvl="8">
				<text>(Adv. Engines) Bring the statue on a collision course with the planet's military installment.</text>
				<event>
					<text>With the statue grappled to your hull, you slingshot it towards the planet. Hurtling towards the surface, the impact stirs up a giant cloud of dust and debris that blocks your vision for several long minutes. Once it settles, you find the impact has decimated much more than the military settlement. The city, reduced to rubble by the shockwave, ends up providing tremendous spoils. At least those children won't have to worry about poor sleep any longer.</text>
					<autoReward level="HIGH">augment</autoReward>
					<choice>
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="MORALITY_UPDATE_GENERAL"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>We can't help.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Disappointed, the mothers shoo you off with a vague hint of relief. They're probably just glad you didn't choose to kill them all and loot their corpses.</text>
				</event>
			</choice>
        </event>
    </choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
        <text>Ignore the planet and its strange statue.</text>
        <event>
            <text>Barely being able to take your eyes off of the eccentric statue, you fly as far away as possible until you can see it no longer.</text>
            <choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
        </event>
    </choice>
</event>

<!--\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
	 NEUTRAL!!!
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\-->
<eventList name="NEUTRAL_ESTATE">
	<event load="ESTATE_DOCUMENTARY"/>
	<event load="ESTATE_STEWARD"/>
	<event load="ESTATE_BAR"/>
	<event load="ESTATE_CONTROLS"/>
</eventList>

<event name="ESTATE_CONTROLS" unique="true">
	<text>At first this seems like an empty beacon, but moments later you're ambushed by an Auto-ship, trailed by a smaller vessel. A young boy in oversized technician garb appears on the screen. "I've got you now, Renegade! Time to face the music!"</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_ESTATE_CONTROLS" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Get ready to fight!</text>
		<event>
			<text>You arm your weapons and prepare to brawl, but the Auto-ship doesn't move. "Uh... hold on. Sorry, my parents put these stupid controls on my drone. Uhm... let me try... uh..."</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Wait for him to fix it.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Uhm... er... damn okay, I have to guess the password. 1...1-1-1-1-1... no... 1-1-1-1-2... ugh... 1-1-1-1-3... damn it! </text>
					<ship hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_ENGINEER">
				<text>(Engineer Crew) Bypass the controls for him.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Woah, how did you do that so quickly? I could never get past the security pin! You're so cool! Can you teach me how to do that? I'll come with you! Without parental controls I can be useful for sure!"</text>
					<crewMember amount="1" class="human_technician">Norton</crewMember>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="hacking" lvl="2">
				<text>(Upg. Hacking) Bypass the controls for him.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Woah, how did you do that so quickly? I could never get past the security pin! You're so cool! Can you teach me how to do that? I'll come with you! Without parental controls I can be useful for sure!"</text>
					<crewMember amount="1" class="human_technician">Norton</crewMember>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Use this opportunity to leave.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Doesn't seems like the drone will be fixed any time soon, and you have other things to be doing. You slip away while the boy tinkers with his drone.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Check the storage.</text>
						<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Do nothing.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="ESTATE_BAR" unique="true">
	<text>It seems a small bar is being operated by corporate staff here, to give a place for employees to wind down after a day's work. Though aimed at field technicians, several Rebel military ships appear to be parked outside.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_REBEL_ESTATE_BAR" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Visit the bar.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Upon stepping inside, you find not a rowdy crowd but a tense one. The Rebel commander, standing fiercely over the counter, is shouting at the bar owner whose smug smile only partially masks the contempt in his eyes. "Sorry sir, we don't serve drinks to off-reality-ers. It's a safety precaution of course. Nothing... personal."</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Demand the Rebel captain stands down.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Great, and so I have to listen to a Renegade telling me what to do as well now? Fine, we came here to do our job, and I guess now we have a reason to do it. Grab your guns lads."</text>
					<ship hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="false">
				<text>Pay for drinks for all of them.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You extend the offer to pay for the Rebels' drinks yourself. The bar owner laughs, but refuses you service either for the same reasons. Indignified, you draw your laser and threaten to put a new hole in his face unless he takes your money.</text>
					<item_modify>
						<item type="scrap" min="-35" max="-35"/>
					</item_modify>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event>
							<text>Terrified and with no reason to believe you won't follow through with this threat, a round of drinks soon appears for all the Rebels. They toast in your honor, and one of them lingers behind to join you. "I'm tired of being treated like garbage and having to stow my blaster for all of these repugnant assholes. You seem like folks who don't take nothing from nobody. I think I'll stick with you."</text>
							<crewMember all_skills="1" amount="1" class="human_soldier"/>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="unique_tuco">
				<text>(Tuco) Threaten the bar owner.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Tuco steps forward, throwing his rocky palm down on the counter with a thunderous smack. He snarls, "Denying booze to a paying customer is a crime I won't allow. You will give this man and his companions a free round or I'll step behind this pitiful table and smash your head like a grape. Are we at an understanding?"</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event>
							<text>Terrified and with no reason to believe the painted pirate won't follow through with this threat, a round of drinks soon appears for all the Rebels free of charge. They toast in your honor, and one of them lingers behind to join you. "I'm tired of being treated like garbage and having to stow my blaster for all of these repugnant assholes. You seem like folks who don't take nothing from nobody. I think I'll stick with you."</text>
							<crewMember all_skills="1" amount="1" class="human_soldier"/>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Leave before things get ugly.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore the bar.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Let's not go messing around with a bunch of drunk Rebels. You have other things to be doing that are less suicidal.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Check the storage.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="ESTATE_STEWARD" unique="true">
    <text>Soon after arriving you receive a hail from a strange, hunched over man. As you listen to his ramblings, you notice the concerningly well armed Auto-ship watching you. "Hallo mein Freund! I am very exzited to zee you! I am ze one and only Dr. Vauto Zepport, ze ingenius inventor of the Auto-Support! Did zou know that yearly over zen-thouzand civilians are saved by mein creations? It is true! And yet, day after day barbaric folk destroy them in cold blood! They call zem 'useless' simply because zey cannot put up a fight! Zey are not combat machines! Zey are helping machines! Zen zey tell me to make a new class, ze Auto-Steward, for combat! Haz ze whole world lost its mind?! Sorry, I am getting off track..."</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_STEWARD_PRIME" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
        <text>Continue...</text>
        <event>
            <text>"Now, zey are telling me you are Renegade! Zou will make za great test! You are a fighting person, so zou will tell me... do you zink my creations are as useless as zey say?"</text>
            <choice hidden="true">
				<text>Yep.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Zou insult my creations? Gah! We will zee what you are zinking of zem after zis!"</text>
					<ship hostile="true"/>
					 <choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>No.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Oh, ze make my heart bubble with joy! Please, azept zis gift for being so kind!"</text>
					<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
				</event>
			</choice>
        </event>
    </choice>
</event>
<event name="ESTATE_STEWARD_WIN">
    <text>"My beautiful creation! You have grinded through it like zandpaper! Ahhh! I am distraught! Heartbroken! Please, allow me to attend your services! I will learn much from watching zou destroy much my creations!"</text>
	<crewMember amount="1" all_skills="2" class="human_technician">Hoffmann</crewMember>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">drone</autoReward>
</event>
<event name="ESTATE_STEWARD_SURRENDER">
    <text>"Now zou have gotten a taste of sweet justice! I trust zou have learned your lesson, Renegade! To celebrate our newfound understanding of what my creations are capable of, allow me to present you a gift! Make sure to tell all your Renegade friends not to call my creations useless anymore!"</text>
	<ship hostile="false"/>
	<weapon name="GIFTLIST_ESTATE"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<damage amount="-10"/>
</event>

<event name="ESTATE_DOCUMENTARY" unique="true">
    <text>You've only just arrived at the beacon, but it seems there's quite the scene to behold. Half of the nearby planet has been blanketed in improvised tents, filming equipment, and a city sized set on which to record. Around it orbit several smaller ships reserved for the actors.</text>
	<img planet="PLANET_POPULATED_SMALL"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
        <text>Approach.</text>
        <event>
            <text>As you move closer, you receive a hail from one of the smaller ships. On the screen appears an exccentrically dressed man, in the clothes of a Rebel admiral, with his hair dyed a glossy blend between blonde and grey, in a startlingly accurate depiction of Admiral Vance himself. "Greetings! I am famed actor Cornelius Parrysmith, I am sure you have heard of me, yes! Perhaps you are not aware, but here we are filming a most gripping documentary of the good admiral himself! And I, famed actor Cornelius Parrysmith, have been chosen to play the star role! I, famed actor Cornelius Parrysmith, have gone to great lengths to experience life as the Admiral, even getting a vasectomy as necessary! Yet, the lengths of my great method acting are not yet fulfilled!"</text>
            <ship load="SHIP_CORNELIUS" hostile="false"/>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_ELLIE_COSTUME">
				<text>(Ellie) "Cornelius, it's me!"</text>
				<event>
					<text>Cornelius fakes a doubletake, and opens his eyes wide in mock enthusiasm. "My word, Stephan? Why, you crazy loon, I thought you'd have gone off and offed yourself in some dark alleyway by now!" Cornelius smiles smugly at his apparently witty retort.
Yet, Ellie seems completely unfazed by the insult, perhaps not even registering it. "I'm on my quest to kill Wentworth! And everyone else who wronged me! I've already killed Darlen, and Kalie, and Peterson, and Oughfben, and Orson, and... and... well I've lost track now! Heheh..."
Now, Cornelius's shock seems real. "S-Stephan, my god. The divorce really drove you off the rocker, hasn't it. You were always a batshit unstable lunatic before, but this really takes the cake! Why are you still wearing your horse costume? Oh wait, let myself, famed actor Cornelius Parrysmith guess - you're all washed up and it's the one thing left that gives you any joy left in this world? How sad... well it would be sad if you were the least bit sane. But you're not, so why would I, famed actor Cornelius Parrysmith, pity you?! Hah!"
					
Ellie brandishes her knife closer to her chest, her eyes glazing over in bloodlust-driven enthusiasm. "Oh Cornelius, don't think you're off my list just because you gave me some acting tips back in the day. Ellie the Equinoid will always be a better and more beloved role than anything you've ever done. I never liked you in 'Flight between the Stars'. But me, washed up? No no no... Ellie's career is just on pause! But your career is finished!" Ellie turns to you, still smiling. "Kill him."</text>
					<ship hostile="true"/>
					 <choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Uhm... okay?</text>
				<event>
					<text>"I, famed actor Cornelius Parrysmith, have taken notice... you are a Renegade, correct? After lynching several orphaned Free Mantis children I, famed actor Cornelius Parrysmith, came to the realization that to truly get into the mind of the good admiral I, famed actor Cornelius Parrysmith, must experience the thrill of combat! I, famed actor Cornelius Parrysmith, challenge you, Renegade, to righteous combat! Non-fatal, of course, and I, famed actor Cornelius Parrysmith, shall promise you great bounties for assisting me!"</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Accept the challenge.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"Most exciting! Then we fight... at once! On-garde!"</text>
							<triggeredEvent event="ESTATE_DOCUMENTARY_SURRENDER" enemyHull="2" enemyCrew="1" thisFight="true" clearOnJump="true"/>
							<ship hostile="true"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Refuse.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"Most disappointing! Well then, I, famed actor Cornelius Parrysmith, has no further need for you! Begone!"</text>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
        </event>
    </choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
        <text>Ignore the strange setup.</text>
        <event>
            <text>As curious as you are, whatever is going on down there is likely not of any importance to you or your mission.</text>
            <choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
        </event>
    </choice>
</event>
<event name="ESTATE_DOCUMENTARY_FAIL">
    <text>It seems you have killed Cornelius. Seeing it's unlikely you'll receive any reward from the dead man, you scrap his ship and hurry off before any of the documentary cast can notice.</text>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<event name="ESTATE_DOCUMENTARY_SURRENDER">
    <text>"Oh good graces, I, famed actor Cornelius Parrysmith, have been bested! The foul Renegade has defeated me! I, famed actor Cor... wait, nay, that is my name no longer! I, infamous Admiral Vance Wentworth, have met a match most foul! I shall honor no promise to wretched Renegades!"</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
        <text>Finish this guy off.</text>
        <event>
			<recallBoarders/>
            <enemyDamage amount="999"/>
        </event>
    </choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
	<ship hostile="false"/>
        <text>Report Cornelius to the documentary cast.</text>
        <event>
            <text>Expecting the director to reprimand Cornelius for his rash behavior or show some kind of concern for his sudden personality change, instead he seems exuberant. "You've done me great work, Renegade! You've made me a star! With Cornelius's commitment now to this role, the documentary is bound to be a hit for sure! I must reward you for this!"</text>
			<autoReward level="MED">augment</autoReward>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
        </event>
    </choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="mind">
        <text>(Mind Control) Remind Cornelius who he really is.</text>
        <event>
            <text>"I... er... I feel a sudden clarity. Perhaps I have gone too far in my method acting. My delusions began ever since I played that role as a psychosis patient with split personality disorder. Er, yes... your reward..."</text>
            <autoReward level="HIGH">item</autoReward>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
        </event>
    </choice>
</event>

<!--\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
	 HOSTILE!!!
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\-->
<eventList name="HOSTILE_ESTATE">
	<event load="ENCOUNTER_ESTATE"/>
	<event load="ENCOUNTER_TECHNITIAN"/>
	<event load="ENCOUNTER_TECHNITIAN_PULSAR"/>
	<event load="ENCOUNTER_REBEL_ESTATE"/>
</eventList>

<event name="ENCOUNTER_ESTATE">
	<text load="TEXT_ENCOUNTER_ESTATE"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_ESTATE" hostile="true"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_ENCOUNTER_ESTATE">
	<text>A crimson Auto-ship appears from around a nearby moon, weapons already hot. Say what you want about W.I., but they sure keep tight security!</text>
	<text>"Renegade Warning! Renegade! Renegade Warning! Renegade!" The ear-splitting bleeps from the nearby Auto-ship remind you how much you hate that everyone calls you by that name. While murdering everyone who does in cold blood might not be the best option, you doubt anyone will complain if you blow up this Auto.</text>
	<text>"You thought you could hide. You cannot hide. I am programmed to be perfect at hide and seek. I have found every ship to ever hide in this system. My programming insists that I should be insulted at the thought that you could hide. I think I will kill you. Yes. The programming never lies."</text>
	<text>Just when you thought standard Auto-ships were enough of a plague, these Innovation Autos are even worse. At least for every one you fight, it's one less the fleet can use against you later.</text>
	<text>It seems there's no end to W.I.'s supply of crimson Autos to throw at you. You suppose this journey would be awfully boring without some fodder to plow through with your cannons though.</text>
</textList>

<event name="ENCOUNTER_TECHNITIAN">
	<text load="TEXT_ENCOUNTER_TECHNITIAN"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_TECHNITIAN" hostile="true"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_ENCOUNTER_TECHNITIAN">
	<text>"I wanted to join the Rebellion as a soldier, but they told me my talents lay elsewhere. Well, it seems now I get a chance to redeem myself! Sorry, Renegade, but I'm just doing my job!"</text>
	<text>Engineers aren't a common sight, but Technicians are even rarer. All of these synonyms are getting confusing, but enemies are enemies, and once you've put enough bullet holes in them, the difference hardly matters.</text>
	<text>"I bet you think this red uniform is cool, huh? I bet you think it's sooo great to be working for this company, huh? Real swell, huh?! HUH?! I bet you think that, idiot! It's not! It sucks! I'm stuck in the call center all day helping old people, and then during break I have to fight people like you! Do me a favor and die quickly so I can maybe scarf down my lunch before my next shift."</text>
	<text>"I am legally required to read you the following disclaimer before I fight you: Wentworth Innovations is not liable for any and all damages that occur on, surrounding, or spiritually within grounds owned, contested, desired, or potentially future occupied by Wentworth Innovations. Damages are to be paid at the expense of the aggressor. By definition, the aggressor in any situation involve Wentworth Innovations technology, faculty, or staff in the party uninvolved with the corporation. Thank you for understanding."</text>
	<text>A nearby Auto-ship swerves to attack you, but almost immediately malfunctions and shuts down. An irate technician appears shortly after. "Ugh, these damn things keep breaking down. Guess I'll have to fight you myself."</text>
</textList>

<event name="ENCOUNTER_TECHNITIAN_PULSAR" unique="true">
	<text>A particularly risky technician has planted themselves next to the nearby pulsar. "Have not met... daily... PRODUCTION QUOTAS. I require POWER. THE POWER OF A PULSAR! LEAVE ME ALONE! I MUST WORK!"</text>
	<environment type="pulsar"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_TECHNITIAN" hostile="true"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="ENCOUNTER_REBEL_ESTATE">
	<text load="TEXT_ENCOUNTER_REBEL_ESTATE"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_REBEL_ELITE_FIGHT" hostile="true"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_ENCOUNTER_REBEL_ESTATE">
	<text>"Oh thank god, finally a Fed. I thought I'd never see any action after being stationed here, but now I finally have a chance to prove myself to command! No more talking to tech nerds! Woohoo!"</text>
	<text>A Rebel Elite approaches. W.I. likely called in some extra protection from U1 since this sector is so vital to the Rebellion. Unfortunately, that means you have some Rebels on your hands that you'll have to grind through!</text>
	<text>"Seriously? A Renegade? Here?! I was just about to head home, and suddenly you show up? You have horrible timing, you know that?" Though the Rebel could easily just leave, he seems to be preparing to fight. Some things never change.</text>
</textList>

<!--\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
	 DISTRESS!!!
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\-->
<eventList name="DISTRESS_ESTATE">
	<event load="DISTRESS_ESTATE_SHIPWRECK"/>
	<event load="DISTRESS_ESTATE_CONFUSION"/>
</eventList>

<event name="DISTRESS_ESTATE_CONFUSION" unique="true">
    <text>You receive a hail from a Separatist ship nearby, the obvious source of the distress call. "Hailing. Confuse. Desire, transparency above. Instruction, give? Welcome, yes."</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_SEPERATIST_GENERIC_NO2" hostile="false"/>
	<distressBeacon/>
	<choice hidden="true">
        <text>What?</text>
        <event>
            <text>"Understandings missed. Calamity? Condescending, verbage appeal! Show who." You have no idea what the Engi is saying, but their weapons have gone hot and a fight is brewing!</text>
            <ship hostile="true"/>
			 <choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
        </event>
    </choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_ENGI">
        <text>(Engi Crew) "Communications invalid. Requesting elaboration."</text>
        <event>
            <text>"Apologies. I am... confused. I seek help in -solving- an identity crisis. After being chased out of Arcadia for my dissent from the [Harmony], I have come here for answers instead, but have found nothing but hostility. Concern 1: I am made of -metal-. Concern 2: my speech is broken, disjointed. Concern 3: I need not breathe. Concern 4: I can reshape [myself] at will. Am I a Lanius?"</text>
            <choice hidden="true">
				<text>Yes.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Welcoming. Dissolution revolving. Happy! Uncertainty? Fortunate dubiously. Attending, boat of great answer."</text>
					<crewMember amount="1" class="lanius_welder">Lanius?</crewMember>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>No.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Thank you. You have resolved my confusion. I am so [happy]. I think. I am... unsure still. I will go with you, you seem -wise-."</text>
					<crewMember amount="1" class="engi_separatist">Engi?</crewMember>
				</event>
			</choice>
        </event>
    </choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
        <text>This Engi is malfunctioning, let's get out of here.</text>
        <event>
            <text>Weary of the suspiciously broken grammar of the otherwise usually better spoken Separatists, you decide it's safer just to take leave.</text>
            <choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
        </event>
    </choice>
</event>

<event name="DISTRESS_ESTATE_SHIPWRECK" unique="true">
    <text>Noting the distress beacon on your map, you maneuver towards the source within a dense asteroid field. A technician vessel, heavily damaged, is stuck between several large asteroids, yet the main damage on its hull doesn't look to be from the meteors. Something - seemingly an ASB - has shot it down, and could very well be nearby. Do you want to risk approaching?</text>
	<environment type="asteroid"/>
	<distressBeacon/>
	<choice hidden="true">
        <text>Try to rescue the ship.</text>
        <event load="ESTATE_SHIPWRECK_BAD"/>
    </choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="PDS_DISABLE">
        <text>(Signal Diluter) Mitigate the risk of a rescue mission.</text>
        <event load="ESTATE_SHIPWRECK_GOOD"/>
    </choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="cloaking" lvl="2">
        <text>(Upg. Cloaking) Mitigate the risk of a rescue mission.</text>
        <event load="ESTATE_SHIPWRECK_GOOD"/>
    </choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="teleporter" lvl="2">
        <text>(Upg. Teleporter) Board directly and look for survivors.</text>
        <event load="ESTATE_SHIPWRECK_SURVIVORS"/>
    </choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="LOCKED_GLOBAL_TELEPORT">
        <text>(Central Teleport) Board directly and look for survivors.</text>
        <event load="ESTATE_SHIPWRECK_SURVIVORS"/>
    </choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
        <text>Don't risk it.</text>
        <event>
            <text>You decide not to try and approach the ship, as you don't fancy meeting the same fate. Hopefully someone a bit more daring can arrive in time to help.</text>
            <choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
        </event>
    </choice>
</event>
<eventList name="ESTATE_SHIPWRECK_BAD">
	<event>
		<text>As you try to approach the wreck, a hidden battery reveals itself momentarily to fire off a humongous projectile that grazes the side of your hull, tearing through the plating. You manage to get out of the asteroid field before too much damage occurs, but there's no hope of rescuing the technicians now.</text>
		<damage amount="3" effect="breach"/>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>As you try to approach the wreck, a hidden battery reveals itself momentarily to fire off a humongous projectile that grazes the side of your hull, tearing through the plating. You manage to get out of the asteroid field before too much damage occurs, but there's no hope of rescuing the technicians now.</text>
		<damage amount="3" effect="breach"/>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>You manage to make your way to the crashed ship, but a hidden battery begins to fire on your ship, causing some considerable damage to your hull. You don't have too much time, but you could either try to board the ship and help the survivors, or steal one of their weapons.</text>
		<damage amount="5" effect="breach"/>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Look for survivors.</text>
			<event load="ESTATE_SHIPWRECK_SURVIVORS"/>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Steal one of their weapons.</text>
			<event>
				<weapon name="RANDOM"/>
			</event>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<event load="ESTATE_SHIPWRECK_GOOD"/>
</eventList>
<event name="ESTATE_SHIPWRECK_GOOD">
	<text>You manage to make your way to the crashed ship, avoiding the hidden battery among the asteroid field. You don't have too much time until it manages to lock on, but you could either try to board the ship and help the survivors, or steal one of their weapons.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Look for survivors.</text>
		<event load="ESTATE_SHIPWRECK_SURVIVORS"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="false">
		<text>Steal one of their weapons.</text>
		<event>
			<weapon name="RANDOM"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="ESTATE_SHIPWRECK_SURVIVORS">
	<event>
		<text>It seems none of the crew survived, though strangely you find a lot of Arcadia technology aboard the ship. You grab one of the drone schematics and as many drone parts as you can carry and prepare to swiftly leave.</text>
		<autoReward level="MED">droneparts_only</autoReward>
		<drone name="RANDOM"/>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>To your luck, you find one of the technicians still alive. After bringing them back safely to your ship, they explain that they aren't an employee of Wentworth Innovations at all! They're a corporate spy sent by Arcadia, meant to recover stolen blueprints. However, they were found out and during their escape were detected by one of the security satellites. With their primary mission a failure, they pledge to help yours.</text>
		<crewMember amount="1" repair="2" class="human_technician"/>
		<autoReward level="MED">droneparts</autoReward>
	</event>
</eventList>
</FTL>
