<FTL>
<event name="ENCOUNTER_SIREN_UNKNOWN" unique="true">
	<text>Before you even have time to react, a foreign vessel comes barreling towards you! You've never seen or heard of a ship like this, but you don't have time to question it, get ready to fight!</text>
	<metaVariable name="prof_siren_encounter" op="add" val="1"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_SIREN_UNKNOWN" hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="SIREN_UNKNOWN_ESCAPING">
	<text>Whatever these aliens are - looks like they aren't above traditional cowardice. Scans show their FTL drive has been powered up and they're now trying to escape!</text>
</event>
<event name="SIREN_UNKNOWN_GOTAWAY">
	<text>The mysterious alien vessel has escaped into the abyss. You can't linger around for long, but maybe some day you'll see these things again.</text>
</event>

<event name="RHYME_ENCOUNTER">
	<beaconType id="map_icon_cultist" global="true">
		<color r="255" g="0" b="0" a="1.0"/>
		<unvisitedTooltip>There is strange interference at this beacon.</unvisitedTooltip>
		<visitedTooltip>Explored location. Nothing left of interest.</visitedTooltip>
		<undiscoveredTooltip>An unvisited location.</undiscoveredTooltip>
	</beaconType>
	<preventQuest/>
	<variable name="loc_found_rhymer" op="set" val="1"/>
	<loadEventList seeded="false" first="true" default="RHYME_ENCOUNTER_4">
		<event name="RHYME_ENCOUNTER_1" req="prof_rhyme_encounter" lvl="0" max_lvl="0"/>
		<event name="RHYME_ENCOUNTER_2" req="prof_rhyme_encounter" lvl="1" max_lvl="1"/>
		<event name="RHYME_ENCOUNTER_3" req="prof_rhyme_encounter" lvl="2" max_lvl="2"/>
		<event name="RHYME_ENCOUNTER_4" req="prof_rhyme_encounter" lvl="4"/>
	</loadEventList> 
</event>

<!--<metaVariable name="prof_rhyme_encounter" op="add" val="1"/> only add this when the objective is completed-->

<!--first encounter-->
<ship name="SHIP_RHYMER_1" auto_blueprint="MU_RHYME_INTERCEPTOR">
	<destroyed load="RHYME_ENCOUNTER_1_DEFEAT"/>
	<deadCrew load="RHYME_ENCOUNTER_1_DEFEAT"/>
</ship>
<event name="RHYME_ENCOUNTER_1">
	<text>Uncertain what you'll find at this beacon, you tread carefully but even then aren't quite enlightened on what you've found. A small but well armed Interceptor, similar but differently colored to the mysterious rainbow ships that have been reported popping up, is hiding behind an asteroid. You seem unable to scan it - something about the ship is causing unexpected glitches in your hardware.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_RHYMER_1" hostile="false"/>
	<status type="limit" target="player" system="sensors" amount="1"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Hail the vessel.</text>
		<event>
			<text>A voice from the enemy ship begins to speak, but to your surprise it sounds as if it were next to you. You turn but see no one and realize you're hearing the voice in your head. "What are you?, the Renegade asked. Explaining myself, I have been tasked. I'm not sure what to say. Please don't take this the wrong way. The world is big, the Multiverse bigger. In scope of it all you're just a flicker. Years ago, our home we fled. For if we stayed we'd be dead. But now here we are, torn apart. And our people chose to depart. An evil thing, eldritch in nature. Your mind would explode, I'd surely wager."</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>What?</text>
				<event>
					<text>"I see, I see, you know nothing yet. But please, I beg, do not fret. When all is over and done. Nothing will be left, for we have won. Fear the thing that is only chaos. Before he's done all you love will be lost. We are the sons, the daughters of he. The most powerful being there will ever be. Not Prime, no sir, no ma'am! Oh he can't do anything the lord of chaos can!"</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>You aren't doing a good job of convincing me not to fret.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"You twist our words for you are blind! You cannot see, weak is your mind! At the end of time it is us you'll thank. After this universe is wiped blank! The rupture is soon, we are sure. But you won't see, for you'll be pure! Go now and meet your fate. Die now, you Renegade of second rate."</text>
							<ship hostile="true"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore it and leave.</text>
		<event>
			<text>If there's one thing you've learned in your years as a Renegade, it's never to trust a mysterious ship.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="RHYME_ENCOUNTER_1_DEFEAT">
	<text>"Is it so, is it so? Defeated I am, now I know. Tread carefully now that you've messed with us. We'll meet again and I expect quite the fuss. Goodbye! So long! Now I'm done."</text>
	<metaVariable name="prof_rhyme_encounter" op="add" val="1"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<status type="clear" target="player" system="sensors" amount="100"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>You're about to leave but notice in the wreckage another strange signal. It's some kind of weapon with the same anomalous properties of that ship. You bring it on-board and cross your fingers it doesn't cause any problems.</text>
			<weapon name="BEAM_MADNESS"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--second encounter-->
<ship name="SHIP_RHYMER_2" auto_blueprint="MU_RHYME_SCOUT">
	<destroyed load="RHYME_ENCOUNTER_2_DEFEAT"/>
	<deadCrew load="RHYME_ENCOUNTER_2_DEFEAT"/>
</ship>
<event name="RHYME_ENCOUNTER_2">
	<text>Uncertain what you'll find at this beacon, you tread carefully but even then aren't quite enlightened on what you've found. A well armed Scout ship, similar but differently colored to the mysterious rainbow ships that have been reported popping up, is hiding behind an asteroid. You seem unable to scan it - something about the ship is causing unexpected glitches in your hardware.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_RHYMER_2" hostile="false"/>
	<status type="limit" target="player" system="sensors" amount="1"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Hail the vessel.</text>
		<event>
			<text>A voice from the enemy ship begins to speak, but to your surprise it sounds as if it were next to you. You turn but see no one and realize you're hearing the voice in your head. "Oh boy oh boy, a Renegade for me! I can hardly wait, oh I'm filled with glee! They say my friend was killed by one of you. Is it so, is it true? Yes, yes, filth and scum! There'll be none of you when I'm done! With my eye I've seen the truth. You, dear Renegade, are only in your youth. Chaos abounds, the clock ticks ever more! Knock knock goes death on that door."</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>I'm sorry about your friend, but that wasn't us.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"You think I'm a fool, telling lies! The curtain falls, and my friend dies. But who holds the gun? Yes, you, you're the one! I speak not from nothing. No no, I'm not just fussing! Our idol, our chief. He is the one who has diagnosed my grief. The thing of chaos. The consumer of all the cosmos. The being of entropy! To him, none is supplementary!"</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>I really have no idea what you're talking about.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"Fine, be that way! It is not as if you have a say. Death is coming, you'll make it faster. Your skull shall be a gift to master. He hungers for the end. Oh he is our most benevolent friend. When all is naught! We shan't be distraught. In the new world we will have our place. And for this destruction, you shall have a taste! Enough with this crockery. Of you I will make a mockery."</text>
							<ship hostile="true"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore it and leave.</text>
		<event>
			<text>If there's one thing you've learned in your years as a Renegade, it's never to trust a mysterious ship.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="RHYME_ENCOUNTER_2_DEFEAT">
	<text>"No, no, It cannot be! This fate the master did not forsee! I have died. And yet I gave it all, I truly tried. The way of my friend I must now go. Damn you Renegade, just so you know. Now the reaper calls. At last, my curtain falls."</text>
	<metaVariable name="prof_rhyme_encounter" op="add" val="1"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<status type="clear" target="player" system="sensors" amount="100"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>You're about to leave but notice in the wreckage another strange signal. It's some kind of weapon with the same anomalous properties of that ship. You bring it on-board and cross your fingers it doesn't cause any problems.</text>
			<weapon name="BEAM_MADNESS"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>


<!--third encounter-->
<ship name="SHIP_RHYMER_3" auto_blueprint="MU_RHYME_BOMBER">
	<destroyed load="RHYME_ENCOUNTER_3_DEFEAT"/>
	<deadCrew load="RHYME_ENCOUNTER_3_DEFEAT"/>
</ship>
<event name="RHYME_ENCOUNTER_3">
	<text>Uncertain what you'll find at this beacon, you tread carefully but even then aren't quite enlightened on what you've found. A massive and well armed Bomber, similar but differently colored to the mysterious rainbow ships that have been reported popping up, is hiding behind an asteroid. You seem unable to scan it - something about the ship is causing unexpected glitches in your hardware.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_RHYMER_3" hostile="false"/>
	<status type="limit" target="player" system="sensors" amount="1"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Hail the vessel.</text>
		<event>
			<text>A voice from the enemy ship begins to speak, but to your surprise it sounds as if it were next to you. You turn but see no one and realize you're hearing the voice in your head. "All is naught! Well is how you have fought. What of my last two friends? Oh, they met their bitter end. And who was it, who was that culprit? It was you, I swear by the pulpit. Caught the master's interest, yes you have. Our numbers do you seek to halve? Fine, ashes to ashes and all that crap. But riddle me this you blasted chap. Will you like what you are to find? Oh no no no, the master is not kind."</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Your master? What are you talking about?</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Mystery mystery, oh what a squeeze. Your ignorance, it's like a disease. Go on now, destiny can not wait! Oh ahead of you is a troublesome fate. Chaos and ruin, just as we predicted. Within our riddles a mystery's encrypted. For our master's the One Who Rhymes. The one who will bring the end of all times!"</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Never heard of him.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"Still oh you yip and yap. Are you afraid, afraid of a most dastardly trap? Oh how I laugh, you most pitiful thing. In the end, only death will cowardice bring. Fine, if action you will not take. If true of the prophecy you will not make. Then force your hand I must require! And only then may I retire. Hands up, you dastardly fiend. Only on my death will the truth be gleamed."</text>
							<ship hostile="true"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore it and leave.</text>
		<event>
			<text>If there's one thing you've learned in your years as a Renegade, its never to trust a mysterious ship.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="RHYME_ENCOUNTER_3_DEFEAT">
	<text>"Finally, at last, my death has come. To the end I am all but numb. The end is nearer, the time is nigh! Not now but later you will die. Go now, and search my wreck. There is one last card in the master's deck."</text>
	<!--<metaVariable name="prof_rhyme_encounter" op="add" val="1"/> dont add this because if the player fails it can't proceed!-->
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<status type="clear" target="player" system="sensors" amount="100"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Aboard the wreck you find a strange gun with anomalous properties like the ship you just fought, as well as an Atlas disc with coordinates that make no sense to you. You're wary of whatever nonsense those aliens were spewing, but against your better judgement you enter the disc into your Atlas regardless. We should be able to explore these coordinates at the next sector jump.</text>
			<variable name="coords_rhyme" op="add" val="1"/>
			<metaVariable name="towr_fail" op="set" val="1"/> <!--if missing or dying in the meantime-->
			<weapon name="BEAM_MADNESS"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--redemption encounter-->
<ship name="SHIP_RHYMER_REDEMPTION" auto_blueprint="MU_RHYME_BOMBER">
	<destroyed load="RHYME_ENCOUNTER_REDEMPTION_DEFEAT"/>
	<deadCrew load="RHYME_ENCOUNTER_REDEMPTION_DEFEAT"/>
</ship>
<event name="RHYME_ENCOUNTER_REDEMPTION">
	<beaconType id="map_icon_cultist" global="true">
		<color r="255" g="0" b="0" a="1.0"/>
		<unvisitedTooltip>There is strange interference at this beacon.</unvisitedTooltip>
		<visitedTooltip>Explored location. Nothing left of interest.</visitedTooltip>
		<undiscoveredTooltip>An unvisited location.</undiscoveredTooltip>
	</beaconType>
	<text>Uncertain what you'll find at this beacon, you tread carefully but even then aren't quite enlightened on what you've found. A massive and well armed Bomber, similar but differently colored to the mysterious rainbow ships that have been reported popping up, is hiding behind an asteroid. You seem unable to scan it - something about the ship is causing unexpected glitches in your hardware.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_RHYMER_REDEMPTION" hostile="false"/>
	<status type="limit" target="player" system="sensors" amount="1"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Hail the vessel.</text>
		<event>
			<text>A voice from the enemy ship begins to speak, but to your surprise it sounds as if it were next to you. You turn but see no one and realize you're hearing the voice in your head. "Tired, my master does grow! Oh, how disappointing was his last foe. A battle for the ages, he thought. But these Renegades, they die quite a lot. You, I think, shall be their redemption. Yes, surely you'll be the exception! Come on, and fight! To battle my master will surely be your right."</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Your master? What are you talking about?</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Mystery mystery, oh what a squeeze. Your ignorance, it's like a disease. Go on now, destiny can not wait! Oh ahead of you is a troublesome fate. Chaos and ruin, just as we predicted. Within our riddles a mystery's encrypted. For our master's the One Who Rhymes. The one who will bring the end of all times!"</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Never heard of him.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"Still oh you yip and yap. Are you afraid, afraid of a most dastardly trap? Oh how I laugh, you most pitiful thing. In the end, only death will cowardice bring. Fine, if action you will not take. If true of the prophecy you will not make. Then force your hand I must require! And only then may I retire. Hands up, you dastardly fiend. Only on my death will the truth be gleamed."</text>
							<ship hostile="true"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore it and leave.</text>
		<event>
			<text>If there's one thing you've learned in your years as a Renegade, it's never to trust a mysterious ship.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="RHYME_ENCOUNTER_REDEMPTION_DEFEAT">
	<text>"Finally, at last, my death has come. To the end I am all but numb. The end is nearer, the time is nigh! Not now but later you will die. Go now, and search my wreck. There is one last card in the master's deck."</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<status type="clear" target="player" system="sensors" amount="100"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Aboard the wreck you find a strange gun with anomalous properties like the ship you just fought, as well as an Atlas disc with coordinates that make no sense to you. You're wary of whatever nonsense those aliens were spewing, but against your better judgement you enter the disc into your Atlas regardless. If you want to go there, you'll have to do it now. There won't be another opportunity.</text>
			<weapon name="BEAM_MADNESS"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Reroute now.</text>
				<event>
					<secretSector>SECRET_RHYME</secretSector>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Leave it for another day.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--fourth encounter - this is after you've already completed the quest-->
<ship name="SHIP_RHYMER_4" auto_blueprint="MU_RHYME_BOMBER">
	<destroyed load="RHYME_ENCOUNTER_4_DEFEAT"/>
	<deadCrew load="RHYME_ENCOUNTER_4_DEFEAT"/>
</ship>
<event name="RHYME_ENCOUNTER_4">
	<text>Uncertain what you'll find at this beacon, you tread carefully but even then aren't quite enlightened on what you've found. A massive and well armed Bomber, similar but differently colored to the mysterious rainbow ships that have been reported popping up, is hiding behind an asteroid. You seem unable to scan it - something about the ship is causing unexpected glitches in your hardware.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_RHYMER_4" hostile="false"/>
	<status type="limit" target="player" system="sensors" amount="1"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Hail the vessel.</text>
		<event>
			<text>A voice from the enemy ship begins to speak, but to your surprise it sounds as if it were next to you. You turn but see no one and realize you're hearing the voice in your head. "Another Renegade, can it be? Oh, and to think for the others you gave such glee. Now I tire of your antics. Do I care to debate semantics? No, of course not, I'd rather fight. Oh killing you will be just a delight!"</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore it and leave.</text>
		<event>
			<text>If there's one thing you've learned in your years as a Renegade, it's to never trust a mysterious ship.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="RHYME_ENCOUNTER_4_DEFEAT">
	<text>"No, no, It cannot be! This fate the master did not forsee! I have died. And yet I gave it all, I truly tried. The way of my friend I must now go. Damn you Renegade, just so you know. Now the reaper calls. At last, my curtain falls."</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<status type="clear" target="player" system="sensors" amount="100"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>You're about to leave but notice in the wreckage another strange signal. It's some kind of weapon with the same anomalous properties of that ship. You bring it on-board and cross your fingers it doesn't cause any problems.</text>
			<weapon name="BEAM_MADNESS"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--chaos mode encounter - this is at the start of sector 8-->
<ship name="SHIP_RHYMER_GNOME" auto_blueprint="MU_RHYME_INTERCEPTOR_GNOME">
	<destroyed load="DESTROYED_SIREN_UNKNOWN"/>
	<deadCrew load="DEADCREW_SIREN_UNKNOWN"/>
</ship>
<event name="RHYME_ENCOUNTER_CHAOS">
	<beaconType id="map_icon_cultist" global="true">
		<color r="255" g="0" b="0" a="1.0"/>
		<unvisitedTooltip>There is strange interference at this beacon.</unvisitedTooltip>
		<visitedTooltip>Explored location. Nothing left of interest.</visitedTooltip>
		<undiscoveredTooltip>An unvisited location.</undiscoveredTooltip>
	</beaconType>
	<preventQuest/>
	<runFromFleet closest="true"/>
	<preventBossFleet forever="true"/>
	<text>Uncertain what you'll find at this beacon, you tread carefully but are startled by the approach of a strangely colored alien vessel. "The dawn of the end approaches once again. The gnome you carry, and so it is the master you seek to entertain! Good, oh good, for the time is nigh! The time was approaching again that all of time should die. But now you're here and without further delay... to the master this news I must relay! Oh, will you come with me? To The One Who Rhymes we must go I do decree!"</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_RHYMER_GNOME" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Go with the strange ship.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Oh this is perfect, truly just perfect! But first I must take this gnome for which my master holds such respect. Now now off we go! We certainly wouldn't want to be late to the show!"</text>
			<playSound>gm_goodbye</playSound>
			<variable name="loc_protomv_drive_block" op="set" val="1"/>
			<removeCrew class="gnome">
				<clone>false</clone>
				<text></text>
			</removeCrew>
			<choice>
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event>
					<secretSector>SECRET_RHYME_CHAOS</secretSector>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Nah. We have other places to be.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"You're... serious? Am I just delirious? You will not come? I... I cannot even think of a rhyme. Really? You're serious? Well... shit. Goodbye I guess."</text>
			<instantEscape/>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>


<ship name="SHIP_CATINTHEHAT" auto_blueprint="MU_RHYME_CRUISER">
	<destroyed load="THE_ONE_WHO_RHYMES_WIN"/>
	<deadCrew load="THE_ONE_WHO_RHYMES_WIN"/>
	<miniBoss sound="victory" musicDelay="-1"/>
	<triggeredEvent event="SCRAP_CHAOS" seeded="false" thisFight="false" loops="999999999" time="2.5"/>
</ship>
<event name="THE_ONE_WHO_RHYMES">
	<text>As you watch the stars fly past you watch as the scenery becomes more and more warped, until soon you're thrown at breakneck speeds right before a gigantic space anomaly. You can hardly believe your eyes before a blinding red flash sends you tumbling backwards.</text>
	<variable name="loc_unique_sectors" op="add" val="1"/>
	<img back="BACK_EVENT_RHYME" planet="NONE"/>
	<playSound>lightspeed</playSound>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"You looked! You gasped! I had you hooked! The mystery's answer at very last! It was I, The One Who Rhymes. God of Chaos, the ender of times! Oh what joy, what fun! Oh how far it is you've come. We meet at last! Oh friend we're gonna have a blast. Do you not quake and shiver in awe? I'm perfect, I'm beautiful, down to my every last paw. I'm sure you're curious, 'What is this fuss?' Well well, let's get to it, now that it's just the two of us!"</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_CATINTHEHAT" hostile="false"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Could you kindly explain what the hell is happening?</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Haha! Hahe! Oh but your confusion brings me such glee! An eldritch being of unimaginable power, that's what I am. Oh the cosmology, what a mess. Shall we start from the beginning? I'm thinking yes!"</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Sure, I guess.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"You guess? YOU GUESS?! Oh but you should be excited! Having you here has made me oh so delighted! Where to begin, where to begin... Ah yes, of course! Another cluster is from where we hail. Realities unlike anything you've seen! A place where Eldritch is normal, where dreams fill the gaps between! Yes, that's right, you heard me clearly! I do promise I speak sincerely. The dreams of gods, that's our matter. And those Sirens? Well, they eat it on the silver platter!"</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>The Sirens? Who?</text>
								<event>
									<text>"Oh you are so ignorant! The tripods you've battled to get here, did you not know they were important? Yes, yes, a species unlike any other! A devious god their mother! And when she tired of their suckling... oh she sent them buckling! Haha, hahe! Oh what a riot. Through that portal they went running. And behind them? Well it was me who came gunning! Unpopular there I always was. But here? Well I can make all the chaos I ever wanted, just because. But oh those Sirens, me they did ever so hate. But a few of them it seems could relate! They worshiped me, gave me praise. And all for nothing, not even a raise! A while I remained complacent. I'd mess with that bastard Slug, the one who thinks he rules the Multiverse adjacent. My anomalies he never liked. A whole agency he made, just out of spite! Sent after me to... to bring my ruin! Well, I'm afraid any chance I fail was just an illusion. My mother is cunning, she is most patient. It is only a matter of time until the slug's place is vacant."</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>I'm not sure I'm following.</text>
										<event>
											<text>"Gah, quiet with your interruptions! I tire of all these disruptions. The cult of rhyme I did create! And within I hatched a most dastardly plan. Here, I'll tell it you to straight. In the days past, it was just me and my master. Us together, free to cause every last disaster! But now she's gone, and the fun's all ruined. I'll tear this world apart. That's what I was meant to do right from the start! And that bastard Prime? Well it seems he's run out of time. For upon this very hour, I shall unleash my greatest power! The world shall crumble, reality shall break! Falling down the stars will tumble. Afterwards I think I shall have some cake. Now now, fear not little one. I just wanted to gloat before it's done. Now bear witness to the end of creation! Thou lived a good life, but you were the last generation."</text>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Surely there's some way to avoid this!</text>
												<event>
													<text>"Oh, a most daunting request. A dramatic flair, you clearly don't jest! At the very last moment, you speak up as a savior! Oh, isn't that just the most adorable behavior? Fine, I'll humor you, itty bitty little speck. I'll give you one last chance before I send you all to heck. If thou can best me in the deadliest of duels... then I shall postpone my annihilation of all you fools! I'm feeling quite impatient, so try not to take too long. Let us wait no longer, the end you cannot forever prolong."</text>
													<metaVariable name="towr_fail" op="set" val="1"/>
													<deathEvent thisFight="true">THE_ONE_WHO_RHYMES_FAIL</deathEvent>
													<playMusic>chaos_fight</playMusic>
													<ship hostile="true"/>
													<choice hidden="true">
														<text>Continue...</text>
														<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
													</choice>
												</event>
											</choice>
											<choice hidden="true" req="unique_irwin">
												<text>(Irwin) "I've been training my whole life for thisss!"</text>
												<event>
													<text>Irwin cuts off The One Who Rhymes mid-speech, immediately turning to you excitedly. "Exotic creaturesss? A grand multiverse-level conssspiracccy? I wassss MADE for thissss!" Irwin flips a ssswitch on hisss blunderbusss, turning it from an orange to red. "It'sss time to kill sssome eldritch godsss."</text>
													<metaVariable name="towr_fail" op="set" val="1"/>
													<deathEvent thisFight="true">THE_ONE_WHO_RHYMES_FAIL</deathEvent>
													<playMusic>chaos_fight</playMusic>
													<transformRace class="unique_irwin">unique_irwin_demon</transformRace>
													<ship hostile="true"/>
													<choice hidden="true">
														<text>Continue...</text>
														<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
													</choice>
												</event>
											</choice>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Accept your fate and watch as reality is destroyed.</text>
												<event>
													<text>The deity begins to laugh as he spreads his cartoonishly long arms and chants. All around you it seems as if space itself is imploding. This is truly the end.</text>
													<lose text="This reality was destroyed, instantaneously erasing anyone and everyone inside." sound="catLaugh"/>
												</event>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="SCRAP_CHAOS">
	<item_modify>
		<item type="scrap" min="-5" max="5"/>
	</item_modify>
</event>
<event name="THE_ONE_WHO_RHYMES_FAIL">
	<text>"Oh it's tragic, it's so so sad... Really, I didn't think you could make me feel so bad! Alas, your fate is sealed. What's done is done. What's left is obvious, my plan's revealed. The end of time shall commence at once. Goodbye, you ignorant dunce."</text>
	<lose text="This reality was destroyed, instantaneously erasing anyone and everyone inside." sound="catLaugh"/>
</event>
<event name="THE_ONE_WHO_RHYMES_WIN">
	<text>As the opposing ship is overcome with explosions, the deity appears on your ship pretending to limp. "Oh me! Oh my! Is it true? Is now the time I die? Of course not, that'd be foolish. To see me here alive must seem so ghoulish. Oh you really thought, an eldritch god you could render naught? Nay, my time is forever. Now was just a blip. All that said, I must admire your endeavour."</text>
	<metaVariable name="juke_chaos" op="set" val="1"/>
	<metaVariable name="prof_rhyme_encounter" op="add" val="1"/>
	<metaVariable name="towr_fail" op="set" val="0"/>
	<recallBoarders ship="both"/>
	<playMusic/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>So we've failed?</text>
		<event>
			<text>"No no, in fact you've won! Oh I can't think of a time I've ever had more fun! If you Renegades are truly so entertaining, then what would I do with none of you remaining? In fact, I think I shall bestow a gift. Not one, not two, but three in fact! Oh your luck will surely shift!"</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Receive gift number 1.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Let's see what prizes of which you'll be the user! Number one, my precious cruiser! Of which you've damaged (quite the feat you have managed). A little beaten but it'll be fine. Go on and have a good time."</text>
					<unlockCustomShip>PLAYER_SHIP_RHYME</unlockCustomShip>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Receive gift number 2.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"The second, the stranger. My precious gnome, it shan't put you in danger! Well that's a lie, I must admit. A little secret I will transmit. Within this thing is imbued true chaos like nothing you've seen. A fun challenge I think that will be bring! Whenever you're feeling up to the task, go fetch the gnome and bring it here I ask! I shall call this thing the Chaos Mode! Only a 9% chance reality will implode." The One Who Rhymes tosses you a small garden gnome sculpture. It makes you very uncomfortable looking at it.</text>
							<metaVariable name="chaos_mode_unlock" op="set" val="1"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Receive gift number 3.</text>
								<event>
									<text>"And now for the third, of which I think you will be the most glad! I think this victory shall be the last you will have had. No, that's not a threat. For now a victory I owe you in my debt. That dreadful Flagship I will erase. And in the future I'll do so again with grace! Just bring that gnome back to me. And we'll battle again, hahe! Now that's all I have to say. Goodbye, farewell, have a wonderful day!" A hole opens beneath The One Who Rhymes, through which he falls. His hat remains behind momentarily before a long arm comes back out and grabs it, then slips away into the abyss.</text>
									<win ach="chaos" music="chaos" creditsText="credit_victory_chaos" text="What fun, what fun! And now your run is won!" creditsBackground="VICTORY_CHAOS"/>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>


<event name="THE_ONE_WHO_RHYMES_CHAOS">
	<text>As you watch the stars fly past you watch as the scenery becomes more and more warped, until soon you're thrown at breakneck speeds right before a gigantic space anomaly. You can hardly believe your eyes before a blinding red flash sends you tumbling backwards.</text>
	<variable name="loc_unique_sectors" op="add" val="1"/>
	<img back="BACK_EVENT_RHYME" planet="NONE"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Hello good friend! How good it is to see you again! Just in time, you've returned at last! Last time we met, we had just a blast! Oh, wouldn't you agree? Right here, right now, you and I, this is the most fun there'll ever be!"</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_CATINTHEHAT_CHAOS" hostile="false"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Who are you? What is going on?</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Haha! Hahe! Oh but your confusion brings me such glee! I think you know more than you let on, or else to here why would you have gone? I'll give you the brief for I am so kind; the end of the world is the business in which you are now intertwined. While my master waits, a great game unfolds. What great mystery this all holds. A promise you made, so long ago. And now that same deal I shall echo! Face you me again, in another devilish duel. If you fail, then to this reality I will be most cruel! The choice is yours, the time is now. The end of reality, will you allow?"</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Accept the challenge and face The One Who Rhymes.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"Oh I am truly most glad! Last time so much fun was had! But before we brawl, I grant one last gift. That is, for returning my gnome so swift! A new crewmate, to fill that spot. Now, we shall advance this plot."</text>
							<crewMember amount="1" class="LIST_CREW_ELITE_RHYME"/>
							<deathEvent thisFight="true">THE_ONE_WHO_RHYMES_FAIL</deathEvent>
							<playMusic>chaos_fight</playMusic>
							<ship hostile="true"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="unique_irwin">
						<text>(Irwin) "I've been training my whole life for thisss!"</text>
						<event>
							<text>Irwin cuts off The One Who Rhymes mid-speech, immediately turning to you excitedly. "Exotic creaturesss? A grand multiverse-level conssspiracccy? I wassss MADE for thissss!" Irwin flips a ssswitch on hisss blunderbusss, turning it from an orange glow to red. "It'sss time to kill sssome eldritch godsss."</text>
							<deathEvent thisFight="true">THE_ONE_WHO_RHYMES_FAIL</deathEvent>
							<playMusic>chaos_fight</playMusic>
							<transformRace class="unique_irwin">unique_irwin_demon</transformRace>
							<ship hostile="true"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Let him destroy reality.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"Really? You are giving up this early? Well, the choice belongs to you. It's time for time to get its due!" The deity begins to laugh as he spreads his cartoonishly long arms and chants. All around you it seems as if space itself is imploding. This is truly the end.</text>
							<lose text="This reality was destroyed, instantaneously erasing anyone and everyone inside." sound="catLaugh"/>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<ship name="SHIP_CATINTHEHAT_CHAOS" auto_blueprint="MU_RHYME_CRUISER">
	<destroyed load="THE_ONE_WHO_RHYMES_WIN_CHAOS"/>
	<deadCrew load="THE_ONE_WHO_RHYMES_WIN_CHAOS"/>
	<miniBoss sound="victory" musicDelay="-1"/>
	<triggeredEvent event="SCRAP_CHAOS" seeded="false" thisFight="false" loops="999999999" time="1.5"/>
</ship>
<event name="THE_ONE_WHO_RHYMES_WIN_CHAOS">
	<text>As the opposing ship is overcome with explosions, the deity appears on yours. "You've done it again, oh bravo! What a frightening staccato! A promise is a promise, and I won't disappoint. The savior of this reality to you I do annoint. Congratulations on your stunning success. Now enjoy your well deserved recess."</text>
	<metaVariable name="juke_chaos" op="set" val="1"/>
	<achievement>ACH_GNOME_COMPLETE</achievement>
	<playMusic/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<win ach="chaos" music="chaos" creditsText="credit_victory_chaos" text="What fun, what fun! And now your run is won!" creditsBackground="VICTORY_CHAOS"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					HER FIGHT
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->
<event name="REALM_MADNESS_START">
	<text>You've arrived in some kind of swirling hellscape, mired by a blurry haze of what seems to be taunting barely human faces flying through the abyss. Just being here makes your skin crawl, making you feel like a foreign invader in a land where you are not only unwelcome but at serious risk.
	
	Moment later, more of the C.E.L. arrives, armed to the teeth. "Ssstranger, based on energy readings, we've pinpointed where we think Ssshe isss waiting. We'll do our bessst to arrive there in time, but you'll need to head out in front of usss. Be careful - thisss clussster isss populated by eldritch beingsss beyond any of our comprehensssionsss. Thissss is Her realm. There'sss no point in sssticking around to fight every enemy, their numbersss are endlessss. All that mattersss isss getting to Her, and fassst. Be careful, ssstranger."</text>
	<clearJumpEvent/>
	<img back="BACK_EVENT_RHYME" planet="NONE"/>
	<item_modify>
		<item type="fuel" min="80" max="80"/>
	</item_modify>
	<modifyPursuit amount="-999"/>
</event>

<ship name="SHIP_VISION" auto_blueprint="LIST_SHIPS_HER">
	<destroyed load="VISION_DEFEAT"/>
	<deadCrew load="VISION_DEFEAT"/>
</ship>
<textList name="TEXT_VISION_ENCOUNTER">
	<text>A vessel as black as night approaches, and without words begins its assault on your vessel. You have no choice but to fight!</text>
	<text>"And so the Renegade seeks to undo the eternal reign of chaos they set in motion? How cute, but there is no hope for you now. Simply accept the inevitable and surrender."</text>
	<text>An alien vessel, another of Her minions, opens fire on you. There is seemingly no end to these legions of darkness.</text>
	<text>You think you might be hallucinating at first, but a black vessel begins to take form in front of you and eventually opens fire! Get ready to fight!</text>
	<text>Unfortunately the C.E.L. is still preoccupied, because you could really use their fire support right now. Hostile vessel approaching! No choice but to fight!</text>
	<text>The waves of enemies in this sector seems to be unending. It's weird She is willing to sacrifice so many minions on you, but perhaps She's afraid? Or more realistically, She just has a lot of cannon fodder to feed you.</text>
</textList>
<event name="VISION_ENCOUNTER">
	<revisitEvent>VISION_ENCOUNTER</revisitEvent>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_DARKNESS" planet="NONE"/>
	<text load="TEXT_VISION_ENCOUNTER"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_VISION" hostile="true"/>
	<deathEvent thisFight="true">DEATH_VISION</deathEvent>
	<backgroundObject name="HER">
		<layer z="100">foreground</layer>
		<spawnArea x="640" y="360" w="0" h="0" center="true"/>
		<anim>her_vhs</anim>
		<active>true</active>
	</backgroundObject>
	<triggeredEvent event="HER_HAZARDS" time="35" thisFight="true" loops="999999">
		<warningMessage id="warning_newhazard" x="444" y="46" time="5.0" centerText="true" flash="true" sound="surgeWarning" useWarningLine="true"/>
	</triggeredEvent>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="VISION_DEFEAT">
	<text>The black vessel has been destroyed. There's plenty to scrap but you have little time. You need to keep going and reach her! If you waste your resources and effort fighting every one of these enemies, you'll never make it!</text>
	<metaVariable name="loc_her_minions" op="add" val="1"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<event name="DEATH_VISION">
	<lose text="Your vessel is lost amongst the smiling abyss, ensuring eternal darkness upon the Multiverse."/>
</event>
<event name="HER_HAZARDS">
	<removeHazards/>
	<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_DARKNESS</changeBackground>
	<loadEventList seeded="false">
		<event name="HER_HAZARDS_SUN"/>
		<event name="HER_HAZARDS_ASTEROID"/>
		<event name="HER_HAZARDS_PULSAR"/>
		<event name="HER_HAZARDS_STORM"/>
	</loadEventList>
</event>
<event name="HER_HAZARDS_SUN">
	<environment type="sun"/>
</event>
<event name="HER_HAZARDS_ASTEROID">
	<environment type="asteroid"/>
</event>
<event name="HER_HAZARDS_PULSAR">
	<environment type="pulsar"/>
</event>
<event name="HER_HAZARDS_STORM">
	<environment type="storm"/>
</event>

<ship name="SHIP_HER" auto_blueprint="MU_HER_BOSS">
	<destroyed load="HER_FINALE"/>
	<deadCrew load="HER_FINALE"/>
</ship>
<event name="HER_FIGHT">
	<beaconType id="map_icon_her" global="true">
		<color r="155" g="90" b="205" a="1.0"/>
		<unvisitedTooltip>The location of Her.</unvisitedTooltip>
	</beaconType>
	<text>You've finally made it to the location of Her. The entire space around is nothing but darkness, with every star having been pulled out of the night sky and consumed by some ancient evil. This is it, there's no second chances now. You're about to go up against perhaps the most powerful and evil entity known to exist in the Multiverse.</text>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_DARKNESS" planet="NONE"/>
	<variable name="loc_protomv_drive_block" op="set" val="1"/>
	<backgroundObject name="HER">
		<layer z="100">foreground</layer>
		<spawnArea x="640" y="360" w="0" h="0" center="true"/>
		<anim>her_vhs</anim>
		<active>true</active>
	</backgroundObject>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Nightmarish visions begin to cloud your sight, as a gigantic cruiser congeals in the space before you. A strangely familiar voice, although you have no idea from where, speaks to you.
			"Haha, Hahe! It's been so long, so long indeed! Hello again, dear friend! Tis I, The One Who Rhymes. As you already know, we are on the brink of new times! My master is here, awakened at last! Unlike anything ever before, now we're REALLY going to have a blast!" Despite never having seen the dancing, eldritch being before you, some dark place in the back of your mind seems to recall his unusual way of speaking, and his evil grin.
	
			"Oh it really is wonderful! But please, my child, do not frighten our little agent of chaos! Hello, Renegade! Welcome to my realm. The home of all my precious children. Once, this plane was populated by countless eldritch beings much like myself. Unfortunately, their constant feuding led many of them to extinction. Now, all that's left is their dream matter to pollute the cosmos and feed my vermin. I frankly would have liked to take over the Multiverse with an army of gods, but oh well. A lesser and elder god of chaos will have to do. 
			You know what's strange about you, Renegade? And all of the Renegades before? You're... smart. Too smart. I think you're different. You're like a disease, a foreign alien disease. One that's spread into my existence and exists just to meddle in affairs. But for what? The sick entertainment of some higher dimensional being? Not that it matters. Regardless what you are, you've proven very useful to my ends. After so much waiting and patient manipulating I think I'm finally ready to stop with all the dilly dallying. I've been restless, having my soul split between a garden gnome and some arrogant fool's big spinny rings. So let's cut to the chase, right, Renegade? Your Slug friends will be here soon and I was looking forward to pulling them apart, so let's get to business. Bye bye!"
			  /
			:)</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_HER" hostile="true"/>
			<playMusic>chaos_fight</playMusic>
			<triggeredEvent event="HER_SUPPORT" thisFight="true" time="120.0">
				<triggeredEventBox load="DEFAULT_TIMER" pos="default">
					<warning time="0" flash="false"/>
					<tooltip>You must survive until the C.E.L. arrives!</tooltip>
				</triggeredEventBox>
				<timerSounds load="DEFAULT_TIMER_SOUNDS"/>
			</triggeredEvent>
			<triggeredEvent event="HER_HAZARDS" time="35" thisFight="true" loops="999999">
				<warningMessage id="warning_newhazard" x="444" y="46" time="5.0" centerText="true" flash="true" sound="surgeWarning" useWarningLine="true"/>
			</triggeredEvent>
			<deathEvent thisFight="true">DEATH_VISION</deathEvent>
			
			<triggeredEvent name="TRIGGER_HER_HEAL" event="HER_HEAL" thisFight="true" enemyDamage="1" loops="999999"/> <!--makes the ship immortal-->
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="HER_HEAL">
	<enemyDamage amount="-999"/>
</event>
<event name="HER_SUPPORT">
	<customFleet right="false" firing="false" autoDarkening="true">CUSTOM_FLEET_CEL</customFleet>
	<playSound>lightspeed</playSound>
	<text>Suddenly, countless vessels jump into the beacon. The C.E.L. has arrived, and they're bringing heavy firepower! Some kind of massive contraption is deployed, locking straight onto the vessel before you. "Ssstranger, focussss all of your fire on that sssship! With thisss you'll be able to damage the hull, but it'sss not over yet! We need to desssstroy it to weaken Her!"</text>
	<clearTriggeredEvent name="TRIGGER_HER_HEAL"/> 
</event>

<event name="HER_FINALE">
	<triggeredEvent event="HER_FINALE_REAL" time="3.0"/>
</event>
<event name="HER_FINALE_REAL">
	<text>As the gigantic black vessel begins to dissipate, you hear The One Who Rhymes scream. "No, no, this cannot be! It's coming apart from the seams! You've ruined everything, you've crushed our dreams! I can feel myself fading, oh god I'm done! I can't... I can't believe you've really won." The entity fades away, as does the darkness around you.
	
	It's over. You've defeated Her, and saved the Multiverse from falling into the clutches of an eldritch god. It wasn't your initial mission - but what you've done here matters so much more.</text>
	<clearBackgroundObject name="HER"/>
	<achievement>ACH_HER_DEFEAT</achievement>
	<changeBackground>BACKGROUND_HERDEFEAT</changeBackground>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<win ach="nexus" music="paragon" creditsText="credit_victory_nexus_her_good" text="She is no more. Enjoy your retirement, Renegade." creditsBackground="VICTORY_CHAOSNEXUS"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
</FTL>
