<FTL>
<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					DEFEAT EVENTS 
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<textList name="GENERIC_SURRENDER_CHOICE_NOMERCY">
	<text>Tune them out and finish this.</text>
	<text>There will be no mercy.</text>
	<text>Ignore their pleas.</text>
	<text>Refuse their surrender.</text>
	<text>Finish them off.</text>
	<text>Continue your attack.</text>
	<text>Deny them mercy.</text>
	<text>Ignore their cries.</text>
	<text>End the comms and finish this fight.</text>
	<text>We will show no mercy.</text>
	<text>There will be no mercy today.</text>
	<text>Deny their request at salvation.</text>
	<text>Pay them no attention and go back to fighting.</text>
	<text>Let their cries of terror go in vain.</text>
	<text>Continue the assault.</text>
	<text>Refuse to spare them.</text>
	<text>Silence their screams with your weapons.</text>
	<text>This battle can only end with their death.</text>
	<text>Mute them and continue fighting.</text>
	<text>They will not live to see another day.</text>
</textList>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					TRAPPER
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DESTROYED_TRAPPER">
	<text>While scrapping the wreckage of the Trapper ship, you find a functional Mine Launcher weapon drifting in the midst of the wreckage.</text>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
	<weapon name="GIFTLIST_MINELAUNCHERS_TRAPPER"/>
</event>

<event name="DEAD_CREW_TRAPPER">
	<text>The Trapper has been emptied of crew. While scrapping it, you find a Mine Launcher in its storage.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<weapon name="GIFTLIST_MINELAUNCHERS_TRAPPER"/>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					REINFORCEMENTS
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DESTROYED_REINFORCEMENTS">
	<text>You gather the remains of the reinforcements, though you can't stay long because of the ASB.</text>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
	<choice req="MAGNET_ARM">
		<text>(Magnet Arm) Salvage the wreck further.</text>
		<event>
			<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="DEADCREW_REINFORCEMENTS">
	<text>You gather the remains of the reinforcements, though you can't stay long because of the ASB.</text>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
	<choice req="MAGNET_ARM">
		<text>(Magnet Arm) Salvage the wreck further.</text>
		<event>
			<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event/>
		</choice>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					CIVILIAN
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DESTROYED_CIVILIAN">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_CIVILIAN"/>
	<autoReward level="LOW">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_CIVILIAN">
	<text>As the civilian ship explodes, you wonder if your actions have consequences. Probably not.</text>
	<text>You watch the civilians explode, and try to convince yourself that there is some way to redeem yourself. Maybe they were Rebel supporters? Hopefully...</text>
	<text>Civilian ships don't usually hold all that much scrap, but every bit helps. Hopefully it's worth all the innocent lives you have just taken.</text>
	<text>The explosions rocking the civilian ship echo in your ears as you slowly realize what you've done. At the very least, the Federation probably will never hear of your crimes.</text>
	<text>There is no way to vindicate what you have just done, and you know it. Still, the civilians are dead, and you are going to scrap everything you can from the wreck that was once their ship.</text>
	<text>The blood of civilians is on your hands. You find it hard to look at your reflection in your ship's windscreen.</text>
	<text>The pained look in your gunner's eyes as you ordered him to fire the last shot will haunt you for the rest of your life. But hey, you got some scrap from all this!</text>
	<text>As your crew returns with the scrap from the civilian's ship, you catch resentful glances in your direction.</text>
	<text>You push the fact the you just committed a war crime to the back of your head and salvage the ship.</text>
	<text>As you strip the ship for anything useful, you wonder if you are any better than the Rebels.</text>
</textList>

<event name="DEAD_CREW_CIVILIAN">
	<text load="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_CIVILIAN"/>
	<autoReward level="LOW">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_CIVILIAN">
	<text>The blood of more civilians is on your hands. It's times like these that you question if the Federation is really the good side.</text>
	<text>You try to tell yourself that murdering each of those civilians was necessary. You take your mind off it by scrapping the ship.</text>
	<text>Another pointless slaughter that can only be blamed on your lust for scrap. To be fair, scrap is rather handy.</text>
	<text>You try not to think of the families of these poor civilians you have just murdered as you scrap their ship.</text>
	<text>You thought you had become numb to the horrors of war, but slaughtering innocent civilians has brought things back into perspective. There isn't anything you can do anymore, so you make sure their ship doesn't go to waste.</text>
	<text>The glares of your crew follow you through the corridors as they strip the ship of its resources.</text>
	<text>One of the dead civilians bears an unnerving resemblance to your old Academy sweetheart. You turn her face away from you and try to focus on scavenging the ship.</text>
	<text>One of the civilians on the ship is still barely alive. Your crew tries to bring him onto your ship to revive him, but he dies before anything can be done. You sigh, knowing there is no way to forgive this.</text>
	<text>Once the ship is scrapped, you retreat to your personal quarters for a while to reflect on your deeds.</text>
</textList>

<event name="SURRENDER_CIVILIAN">
	<text load="TEXT_SURRENDER_CIVILIAN"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept their surrender.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
			<autoReward level="RANDOM">stuff</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text load="GENERIC_SURRENDER_CHOICE_NOMERCY"/>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_SURRENDER_CIVILIAN">
	<text>"Please! You are a Federation ship! In our darkest days you are supposed to bring the light. You can't kill us!"</text>
	<text>The Civilians desperately hail you and beg that you let them live.</text>
	<text>"Why are you doing this? I always heard that the Federation was supposed to be the good guys!"</text>
	<text>"I knew it! The Rebellion officials always told us the Federation would stab us in the back. Now you're doing exactly that! Let us live, I beg of you."</text>
	<text>You're hailed by the Civilians, who beg that you let them live. They offer some supplies.</text>
	<text>"Take this, it's not much but its all I can offer. Just don't kill us!"</text>
	<text>You're hailed by the Civilians, who offer you some supplies if you will let them live.</text>
</textList>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					MILITIA
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DESTROYED_MILITIA">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_MILITIA"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_MILITIA">
	<text>Killing Militia ships is no worse than killing Civilians, but at the very least they voluntarily signed up to risk their lives.</text>
	<text>You've destroyed another ship, but this time it was staffed by Militia officers. You're a monster, but at least you got some scrap out of it.</text>
	<text>You try not to think of how counterintuitive it is to be killing the Militia when the goal of your mission is to save the Civilians of the galaxy.</text>
	<text>If the road to heaven was paved with bad intentions, you'd be on that path. You try not to think about your horrible deeds and scrap the ship.</text>
	<text>Every Militia ship you kill counteracts every Civilian you save. At the very least, your crew aren't going to turn on you.</text>
	<text>You can't help but feel sorry for these brave Militiamen who died trying to do their job as you move in to scrap their ship.</text>
	<text>You decide to leave this Militia ship's fate out of your captain's log as you move in to scrap it.</text>
	<text>While the FTL charges, you wonder what this will look like on your record if the Federation finds out. Maybe you can convince them this death was necessary..</text>
</textList>

<event name="DEAD_CREW_MILITIA">
	<text load="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_MILITIA"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_MILITIA"> <!--uses almost the exact same text-->
	<text>Killing the crew of Militia ships is no worse than killing Civilians, but at the very least they voluntarily signed up to risk their lives.</text>
	<text>You've killed another ship's crew, but this time it was staffed by Militia officers. You're a monster, but at least you got some scrap out of it.</text>
	<text>You try not to think of how counterintuitive it is to be killing the Militia when the goal of your mission is to save the Civilians of the galaxy.</text>
	<text>If the road to heaven was paved with bad intentions, you'd be on that path. You try not to think about your horrible deeds and scrap the ship.</text>
	<text>Every Militia ship crew you kill counteracts every Civilian you save. At the very least, your crew aren't going to turn on you.</text>
</textList>

<event name="SURRENDER_MILITIA">
	<text load="TEXT_SURRENDER_MILITIA"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept their surrender.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
			<autoReward level="RANDOM">stuff</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text load="GENERIC_SURRENDER_CHOICE_NOMERCY"/>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_SURRENDER_MILITIA">
	<text>"This! This is why the Federation has fallen and we Militiamen had to stand up for ourselves. Accept our surrender, or prove that the Federation really is a corrupt, malevolent force."</text>
	<text>The Militiamen surrender, and offer scrap. Through the screen their captain glares at you, but says nothing more.</text>
	<text>"So you have come to kill us? Please, accept our surrender, or make it quick."</text>
	<text>The Militiamen are brave, but not stupid. They know when to surrender, and right now they are doing just that.</text>
	<text>"Protect and serve my ass! Take everything we have, just let us live!"</text>
	<text>"We're just doing our job protecting this sector. Take this and leave us alone!"</text>
</textList>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					FEDERATION
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DESTROYED_FEDERATION">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_FEDERATION"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_FEDERATION">
	<text>You look away as the Federation ship explodes. What have we come to, when you so willingly killed your own allies?</text>
	<text>You can hardly bear to look at the results of your treachery. You order your crew to salvage the mess while you sit down and think about what you've done.</text>
	<text>You've killed many ships, some far less deserving than others, but never did you think you would stoop low enough to destroy a fellow Federation vessel.</text>
	<text>The Federation ship explodes, condemning everyone inside it to instant death. Your crew will never look at you the same way again.</text>
	<text>Your gunner refuses your order to kill them, and you have to fire the final shot yourself. You killed your own ally. You're a monster.</text>
	<text>As the ship breaks apart, you hear one last desperate hail that will deprive you of sleep for years.</text>
	<text>No matter what you do to try to make up for it, you killed an ally. No one can forgive you now, not even yourself.</text>
	<text>They aren't civilians, but you're working to save the Federation nonetheless. Nothing can undo what you have done now.</text>
	<text>One last explosion marks their fate as their ship is torn apart.</text>
</textList>
<event name="DESTROYED_FEDERATION_STATION">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_FEDERATION_STATION"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_FEDERATION_STATION">
	<text>You look away as the Federation station explodes. What have we come to, when you so willingly killed your own allies?</text>
	<text>You can hardly bear to look at the results of your treachery. You order your crew to salvage the mess while you sit down and think about what you've done.</text>
	<text>You've killed many ships, some far less deserving than others, but never did you think you would stoop low enough to destroy a station staffed by the Federation.</text>
	<text>The Federation station explodes, condemning everyone inside it to instant death. Your crew will never look at you the same way again.</text>
	<text>Your gunner refuses your order to kill them, and you have to fire the final shot yourself. You killed your own ally. You're a monster.</text>
	<text>As the station breaks apart, you hear one last desperate hail that will deprive you of sleep for years.</text>
	<text>No matter what you do to try to make up for it, you killed an ally. No one can forgive you now, not even yourself.</text>
	<text>They aren't civilians, but you're working to save the Federation nonetheless. Nothing can undo what you have done now.</text>
	<text>One last explosion marks their fate as their station is torn apart.</text>
</textList>

<event name="DEAD_CREW_FEDERATION">
	<text load="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_FEDERATION"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_FEDERATION">
	<text>You question whether it was necessary to murder all of those Federation officers. Regardless, it's too late to go back. You scrap their ship.</text>
	<text>You can never vindicate what you have just done, but you aren't going to let the now emptied Federation ship go to waste.</text>
	<text>These people went to the Academy with you, trained alongside you as allies. You never met them, but they were your friends. And now you've killed them.</text>
	<text>You just killed Federation soldiers. Admiral Tully will personally have all of your crew executed if you fail your mission now.</text>
	<text>Future ships that encounter this wreck will think it was caused by the Rebels, but you will always know the truth. It will haunt you for a long time...</text>
</textList>
<event name="DEAD_CREW_FEDERATION_STATION">
	<text load="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_FEDERATION_STATION"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_FEDERATION_STATION">
	<text>You question whether it was necessary to murder all of those Federation officers. Regardless, it's too late to go back. You scrap the station.</text>
	<text>You can never vindicate what you have just done, but you aren't going to let the now emptied Federation station go to waste.</text>
	<text>These people went to the Academy with you, trained alongside you as allies. You never met them, but they were your friends. And now you've killed them.</text>
	<text>You just killed Federation soldiers. Admiral Tully will personally have all of your crew executed if you fail your mission now.</text>
	<text>Future ships that encounter this wreck will think it was caused by the Rebels, but you will always know the truth. It will haunt you for a long time...</text>
</textList>

<event name="SURRENDER_FEDERATION">
	<text load="TEXT_SURRENDER_FEDERATION"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept their surrender.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
			<autoReward level="RANDOM">stuff</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text load="GENERIC_SURRENDER_CHOICE_NOMERCY"/>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_SURRENDER_FEDERATION">
	<text>"Have you gone absolutely mad? We're on the same side!"</text>
	<text>The Federation ship is in tatters. You could probably negotiate their surrender at this point.</text>
	<text>"Please, we don't have to do this! I don't know why you've done this, but we're willing to give you anything to let us go!"</text>
	<text>"What's gotten into you? We're Federation too!"</text>
	<text>"What's going on? Take everything we have, just leave us alone!"</text>
	<text>The ship repeatedly hails you, pleading for you to stop your assault and let them go.</text>
</textList>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					FEDERATION AUTO
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DESTROYED_FEDERATION_AUTO">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_FEDERATION_AUTO"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_FEDERATION_AUTO">
	<text>"E-error: Betrayal" The Auto-ship explodes. You feel far less remorse than if it was a staffed Federation ship, but you still feel a little guilty.</text>
	<text>It's far less satisfying to destroy one of the Federation's creations than that of the Rebellion, but scrap is scrap.</text>
	<text>As you destroy the Auto-ship it sends one last message: "Sorry..."</text>
	<text>The drone breaks apart under your weapon fire, and your crew gives you strange looks. Oh well, at least it wasn't a ship filled with actual Federation crew.</text>
</textList>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					REBEL
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<eventList name="DESTROYED_REBEL">
	<event load="DESTROYED_REBEL_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_REBEL_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_REBEL_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_REBEL_GENERIC"/>
	
	<event load="DESTROYED_REBEL_POD"/>
</eventList>
<event name="DESTROYED_REBEL_GENERIC">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_REBEL"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_REBEL">
	<text>The fiery red of the explosions complements the orange hull of the Rebel ship. Satisfied with your handiwork, you scrap the ship.</text>
	<text>The Rebel ship is engulfed in fire, which is extinguished almost immediately as the hull cracks apart and exposes the internals to the vacuum of space. Once the corpses have been cleared of the vessel, you scrap the remains.</text>
	<text>The Rebel ship explodes, its many vital systems reduced to mere scrap material. Scrap material for you to take, that is.</text>
	<text>Every ship full of Rebel scum that you destroy means a slightly safer galaxy. It's not much, but it's honest work.</text>
	<text>You receive a hail from the Rebel ship right as it explodes, but it's too late. The face of the captain begging for his life briefly flashes before he is consumed by the fire in front of your eyes.</text>
	<text>You know the Rebels must have families too, but they're probably not the greatest. Or at least, that's what you hope.</text>
	<text>One final blast from your weapons has crippled the Rebel ship's hull. There is a large portion of scrap matter left for you to take.</text>
	<text>The death of your opponents is rarely as satisfying as when it's a Rebel ship. At last, your revenge for all the hell they've caused for the Federation.</text>
	<text>The Rebel ship explodes, leaving behind a substantial collection of useful scrap material.</text>
</textList>
<event name="DESTROYED_REBEL_POD">
	<text>Just before the Rebel ship explodes, an escape pod ejects from it. Unfortunately, it doesn't get far before you collect it and bring it aboard. You open it and drag out the Rebel officer inside. They beg that you let them live.</text>
	<autoReward level="LOW">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CHECK_ANY_CREW" lvl="1" blue="false">
		<text>Accept them onto your ship.</text>
		<event load="DESTROYED_REBEL_POD_ACCEPT"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CHECK_ANY_CREW" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
		<text>Accepting the Rebel without further means of ensuring his loyalty is too risky.</text>
		<event load="OPTION_INVALID"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="mind">
		<text>(Mind Control) Keep the mind control online in-case they do anything bad.</text>
		<event load="DESTROYED_REBEL_POD_MIND"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Free the Rebel and let them go.</text>
		<event load="DESTROYED_REBEL_POD_SAVE"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Space him.</text>
		<event>
			<text>As you grab the Rebel by the arms and drag him into the airlock he protests little. A tear rolls down his cheek as he stands up straight and accepts his fate. You close the airlock once again when his corpse has drifted a safe distance from the ship.</text>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="DESTROYED_REBEL_POD_ACCEPT">
	<event>
		<text>The Rebel is grateful for you sparing him, despite it meaning he must betray his original cause.</text>
		<crewMember amount="1" class="human"/>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>The Rebel puts on a facade of gratitude, which is shattered quickly when he pulls out a laser and blasts one of your crew! He shouts, "Rebellion forever!" before he is shot in return. You drag his lifeless body to the airlock and send him into the endless vacuum of space.</text>
		<removeCrew>
			<clone>true</clone>
			<text>Luckily, your killed crewmember is already undergoing the cloning process.</text>
		</removeCrew>
	</event>
</eventList>
<eventList name="DESTROYED_REBEL_POD_MIND">
	<event>
		<text>The Rebel is grateful for you sparing him, despite it meaning he must betray his original cause. Looks like we won't need the mind control after all.</text>
		<crewMember amount="1" class="human"/>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>The Rebel puts on a facade of gratitude, which is shattered quickly when he pulls out a laser and tries to shoot one of your crew! Luckily, the mind control stops him and he drops to the floor. You hurry to drag him out the airlock.</text>
	</event>
</eventList>
<eventList name="DESTROYED_REBEL_POD_SAVE">
	<event>
		<text>At first uncertain whether it's a trick, once the Rebel is convinced you aren't going to stab them in the back, they offer you a small portion of what they salvaged themselves as thanks. It seems not every Rebel has a cold heart.</text>
		<autoReward level="LOW">standard</autoReward>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>At first uncertain whether it's a trick, once the Rebel is convinced you aren't going to stab them in the back, they offer you a small portion of what they salvaged themselves as thanks. It seems not every Rebel has a cold heart.</text>
		<autoReward level="LOW">standard</autoReward>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>The Rebel doesn't make your decision easy, as they continue to berate you from the cargo bay until you've released them. It's almost certain they'll betray you, but you aren't going to be a murderer when you have a choice.</text>
		<modifyPursuit amount="1"/>
	</event>
</eventList>

<event name="DEAD_CREW_REBEL">
	<text load="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_REBEL"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_REBEL">
	<text>For every Rebel you kill you like to think of all the Federation officers and civilians you have indirectly saved. Another full crew of Rebels dead, another crew of innocents you've saved.</text>
	<text>As the captain of the Rebel ship collapses to his knees, he beckons for you to come closer. He whispers, "Damn... you...", and falls lifeless to the ground.</text>
	<text>With the Rebel vessel now clear of its crew, you are free to scrap the remains.</text>
	<text>The screams of the Rebel crew have at last been silenced. You almost feel bad. Almost.</text>
	<text>As you move across the interior of the Rebel ship you can still see the soldiers' corpses twitching. It's quite morbid, but you don't feel bad in the slightest.</text>
	<text>You feel no pity for the now dead Rebel crew, and scrap their ship spitefully.</text>
</textList>

<event name="ESCAPE_REBEL">
	<text load="TEXT_ESCAPE_REBEL"/>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_ESCAPE_REBEL">
	<text>You overhear the Rebel captain giving orders to his crew. "Damn this! Redirect as much power as necessary to the engines. We have to get out of here!"</text>
	<text>You notice the engines of the Rebel ship flare up. They're trying to escape!</text>
	<text>It's rare that Rebels try to run away from a battle, but this ship prioritizes its survival.</text>
	<text>You can tell from a massive spike in the enemy's engine power that the ship is trying to escape.</text>
</textList>

<eventList name="GOTAWAY_REBEL">
	<event load="GOTAWAY_REBEL_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="GOTAWAY_REBEL_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="GOTAWAY_REBEL_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="GOTAWAY_REBEL_GENERIC"/>
	
	<event load="GOTAWAY_REBEL_REMAINS"/>
</eventList>
<event name="GOTAWAY_REBEL_GENERIC">
	<text load="TEXT_GOTAWAY_REBEL"/>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_GOTAWAY_REBEL">
	<text>The Rebel captain laughs as he jumps away, leaving you all alone at the beacon.</text>
	<text>"You will rue this day!" The Rebel ship jumps away.</text>
	<text>You curse under your breath as the Rebel ship's engines flare one last time and it jumps away.</text>
	<text>The Rebel ship escapes. You focus on the repairs necessary after that profitless fight.</text>
</textList>
<event name="GOTAWAY_REBEL_REMAINS">
	<text>The Rebel ship jumps away. At first you're disappointed, but then you realise a portion of scrap matter has been left behind from the fight. It's not much, but it helps soften the blow of your failure.</text>
	<autoReward level="LOW">scrap_only</autoReward>
</event>

<eventList name="SURRENDER_REBEL">
	<event load="SURRENDER_REBEL_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_REBEL_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_REBEL_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_REBEL_GENERIC"/>
	
	<event load="SURRENDER_REBEL_FLEET"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_REBEL_DEMAND"/>
</eventList>
<event name="SURRENDER_REBEL_GENERIC">
	<text load="TEXT_SURRENDER_REBEL_GENERIC"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept their surrender.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
			<autoReward level="RANDOM">stuff</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text load="GENERIC_SURRENDER_CHOICE_NOMERCY"/>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_SURRENDER_REBEL_GENERIC">
	<text>The Rebel captain hails you. In the background, you can see the chaos that your weapons have caused. "Ok, you win. We surrender."</text>
	<text>It's rare for a Rebel ship to offer their surrender to a Federation one, but this appears to be one of those times.</text>
	<text>"Ok, we surrender! If your claims that the Federation is such a benevolent force are true, then you must accept our surrender!"</text>
	<text>"Bah, fine. Knowing how corrupt you Federation officers are, perhaps a bit of scrap can convince you to let us go?"</text>
	<text>The Rebel ship is running on fumes. Panting heavily, the Rebel captain begs you let them live.</text>
	<text>"Ok, you've proven that you are superior in combat. Now, prove that you are as forgiving as you say you are."</text>
	<text>At last, the Rebel ship seems to yield. They offer a surrender.</text>
	<text>"Gah I can't believe I'm saying this to Federation scum... if we give you what's in our storage will you let us live?"</text>
	<text>"Okay, okay! You win. Command will never forgive us for letting you go, but at least we'll be alive to see ourselves dismissed. Will you accept our surrender?"</text>
	<text>The Rebel ship has no desire to fight anymore. They desperately hail you.</text>
	<text>"Command doesn't have to know we encountered you here. Just let us go and we'll give you what we have."</text>
</textList>
<event name="SURRENDER_REBEL_DEMAND">
	<text load="TEXT_SURRENDER_REBEL_DEMAND"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept their surrender.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text load="GENERIC_SURRENDER_CHOICE_NOMERCY"/>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_SURRENDER_REBEL_DEMAND">
	<text>"This is not a joke. You have gone too far. Do you know who I am? I am vital to the Rebellion. I demand you let me live!"</text>
	<text>The Rebel ship hails you. "No more games. You will let us live or you will suffer the wrath of the Rebellion!"</text>
	<text>"The Rebellion will never die! Every Rebel ship you kill will only make your punishment greater after our inevitable victory. Let us go."</text>
</textList>
<event name="SURRENDER_REBEL_FLEET">
	<text load="TEXT_SURRENDER_REBEL_FLEET"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept their surrender. [Delays the fleet 2 jumps]</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Rebels promise to delay the fleet, and jump away.</text>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
			<modifyPursuit amount="-2"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text load="GENERIC_SURRENDER_CHOICE_NOMERCY"/>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_SURRENDER_REBEL_FLEET">
	<text>"Look look, maybe we can both get something out of this. I know the fleet is an issue for you. If you let us live, we can lie to the fleet about your location. They'll never know until it's too late."</text>
	<text>The Rebel ship surrenders, and promises to delay the fleet if you let them live.</text>
	<text>"If you kill us, you gain nothing but some insignificant scrap. We're more useful to you alive. Let us go, and we can delay the fleet for you."</text>
</textList>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					AUTO
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<eventList name="DESTROYED_AUTO">
	<event load="DESTROYED_AUTO_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_AUTO_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_AUTO_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_AUTO_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_AUTO_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_AUTO_GENERIC"/>
	
	<event load="DESTROYED_AUTO_FUEL"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_AUTO_MISSILES"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_AUTO_DRONES"/>
</eventList>
<event name="DESTROYED_AUTO_GENERIC">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_AUTO"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_AUTO">
	<text>The best part about killing Auto-ships is there's no guilt involved. You lean back in your chair and give the orders to scrap the ship.</text>
	<text>Destroying Auto-ships will be one of the few things you miss when the Rebellion is gone. If they are ever gone, that is.</text>
	<text>The Auto-ship explodes into multiple pieces, its complicated AI brain shattered into mere scrap matter.</text>
	<text>It's hard to make out the shape of what was once the Auto-ship from the remains of your destruction. You like it better this way.</text>
	<text>Every time you destroy an Auto-ship you think about how some Rebel worker's hard work has just been put to waste.</text>
	<text>You swerve to the left as a chunk of what was once the Auto-ship flies past. There's plenty left behind for you to scrap from the ship.</text>
	<text>Destroying Auto-ships was nearly worth joining the Federation all on its own. Even killing Rebels gets to you eventually, but you could keep blowing these machines to bits all day.</text>
	<text>Auto-ships are no small threat, but at the end of the day you reduce every one that comes in your path to mere scrap matter.</text>
	<text>Another Auto-ship from the Rebellion's extensive supply has been destroyed. It's not much in the grand scheme of things, but oh does it feel good.</text>
</textList>
<event name="DESTROYED_AUTO_FUEL">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_AUTO_FUEL"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Salvage the extra fuel cells.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The extra fuel is always helpful, and you collect as much as you can.</text>
			<autoReward level="LOW">fuel_only</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_AUTO_FUEL"> <!-- The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of fuel left behind in the wreckage.-->
	<text>The best part about killing Auto-ships is there's no guilt involved. You lean back in your chair and give the orders to scrap the ship. The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of fuel left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>Destroying Auto-ships will be one of the few things you miss when the Rebellion is gone. If they are ever gone, that is. The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of fuel left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>The Auto-ship explodes into multiple pieces, its complicated AI brain shattered into mere scrap matter. The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of fuel left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>It's hard to make out the shape of what was once the Auto-ship from the remains of your destruction. You like it better this way. The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of fuel left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>Every time you destroy an Auto-ship you think about how some Rebel worker's hard work has just been put to waste. The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of fuel left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>You swerve to the left as a chunk of what was once the Auto-ship flies past. There's plenty left behind for you to scrap from the ship. The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of fuel left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>Destroying Auto-ships was nearly worth joining the Federation all on its own. Even killing Rebels gets to you eventually, but you could keep blowing these machines to bits all day. The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of fuel left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>Auto-ships are no small threat, but at the end of the day you reduce every one that comes in your path to mere scrap matter. The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of fuel left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>Another Auto-ship from the Rebellion's extensive supply has been destroyed. It's not much in the grand scheme of things, but oh does it feel good. The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of fuel left behind in the wreckage.</text>
</textList>
<event name="DESTROYED_AUTO_MISSILES">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_AUTO_MISSILES"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Salvage the extra ammunition.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The extra missiles are always helpful, and you collect as much as you can.</text>
			<autoReward level="LOW">missiles_only</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_AUTO_MISSILES"> <!-- The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of ammunition left behind in the wreckage.-->
	<text>The best part about killing Auto-ships is there's no guilt involved. You lean back in your chair and give the orders to scrap the ship. The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of ammunition left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>Destroying Auto-ships will be one of the few things you miss when the Rebellion is gone. If they are ever gone, that is. The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of ammunition left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>The Auto-ship explodes into multiple pieces, its complicated AI brain shattered into mere scrap matter. The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of ammunition left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>It's hard to make out the shape of what was once the Auto-ship from the remains of your destruction. You like it better this way. The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of ammunition left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>Every time you destroy an Auto-ship you think about how some Rebel worker's hard work has just been put to waste. The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of ammunition left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>You swerve to the left as a chunk of what was once the Auto-ship flies past. There's plenty left behind for you to scrap from the ship. The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of ammunition left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>Destroying Auto-ships was nearly worth joining the Federation all on its own. Even killing Rebels gets to you eventually, but you could keep blowing these machines to bits all day. The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of ammunition left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>Auto-ships are no small threat, but at the end of the day you reduce every one that comes in your path to mere scrap matter. The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of ammunition left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>Another Auto-ship from the Rebellion's extensive supply has been destroyed. It's not much in the grand scheme of things, but oh does it feel good. The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of ammunition left behind in the wreckage.</text>
</textList>
<event name="DESTROYED_AUTO_DRONES">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_AUTO_DRONES"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Salvage the extra drone parts.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The extra parts are always helpful, and you collect as much as you can.</text>
			<autoReward level="LOW">droneparts_only</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_AUTO_DRONES"> <!-- The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of drone parts left behind in the wreckage.-->
	<text>The best part about killing Auto-ships is there's no guilt involved. You lean back in your chair and give the orders to scrap the ship. The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of drone parts left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>Destroying Auto-ships will be one of the few things you miss when the Rebellion is gone. If they are ever gone, that is. The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of drone parts left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>The Auto-ship explodes into multiple pieces, its complicated AI brain shattered into mere scrap matter. The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of drone parts left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>It's hard to make out the shape of what was once the Auto-ship from the remains of your destruction. You like it better this way. The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of drone parts left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>Every time you destroy an Auto-ship you think about how some Rebel worker's hard work has just been put to waste. The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of drone parts left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>You swerve to the left as a chunk of what was once the Auto-ship flies past. There's plenty left behind for you to scrap from the ship. The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of drone parts left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>Destroying Auto-ships was nearly worth joining the Federation all on its own. Even killing Rebels gets to you eventually, but you could keep blowing these machines to bits all day. The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of drone parts left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>Auto-ships are no small threat, but at the end of the day you reduce every one that comes in your path to mere scrap matter. The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of drone parts left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>Another Auto-ship from the Rebellion's extensive supply has been destroyed. It's not much in the grand scheme of things, but oh does it feel good. The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of drone parts left behind in the wreckage.</text>
</textList>

<event name="ESCAPE_AUTO">
	<text load="TEXT_ESCAPE_AUTO"/>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_ESCAPE_AUTO">
	<text>"This is a pre-recorded message. This automated vessel has received critical damage, and will now attempt to evacuate. Do not cause further damage to its hull integrity."</text>
	<text>The Auto-ship appears to be trying to escape! They might be cheap to roll out, but the Rebellion would prefer they weren't destroyed except when absolutely necessary.</text>
	<text>You detect high energy signatures in the Auto-ship's engines. It must be trying to escape!</text>
</textList>

<eventList name="GOTAWAY_AUTO">
	<event load="GOTAWAY_AUTO_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="GOTAWAY_AUTO_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="GOTAWAY_AUTO_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="GOTAWAY_AUTO_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="GOTAWAY_AUTO_GENERIC"/>
	
	<event load="GOTAWAY_AUTO_REMAINS"/>
</eventList>
<event name="GOTAWAY_AUTO_GENERIC">
	<text load="TEXT_GOTAWAY_AUTO"/>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_GOTAWAY_AUTO">
	<text>The Auto-ship jumps away, and an automated recording of robotic laughter plays over your intercom.</text>
	<text>You order the crew to fire all of the weapons immediately, but it's too late. The Auto-ship has escaped.</text>
	<text>The Auto-ship jumps away. At the very least, you damaged it heavily enough that the next ship to encounter it won't have too hard a time destroying it.</text>
</textList>
<event name="GOTAWAY_AUTO_REMAINS">
	<text>The Auto-ship jumps away, abandoning you in the empty vacuum of space. You're about to jump away when you notice a trail of scrap left behind by the Auto-ship.</text>
	<autoReward level="LOW">scrap_only</autoReward>
</event>

<eventList name="SURRENDER_AUTO">
	<event load="SURRENDER_AUTO_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_AUTO_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_AUTO_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_AUTO_GENERIC"/>
	
	<event load="SURRENDER_AUTO_FUEL"/>
</eventList>
<event name="SURRENDER_AUTO_GENERIC">
	<text>"This is an automated message. You are to cease attacking this Auto-drone, and in return it will dispense a section of its cargo."</text>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept the surrender.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
			<autoReward level="RANDOM">stuff</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Refuse the Auto-ship's surrender.</text>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="SURRENDER_AUTO_FUEL">
		<text>"This is an automated message. You are to cease attacking this Auto-drone, and in return it will dispense fuel."</text>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept the surrender.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
			<autoReward level="LOW">fuel_only</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Refuse the Auto-ship's surrender.</text>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					INNOVATION AUTO
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<eventList name="DESTROYED_ESTATE">
	<event load="DESTROYED_ESTATE_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_ESTATE_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_ESTATE_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_ESTATE_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_ESTATE_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_ESTATE_GENERIC"/>
	
	<event load="DESTROYED_ESTATE_FUEL"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_ESTATE_MISSILES"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_ESTATE_DRONES"/>
</eventList>
<event name="DESTROYED_ESTATE_GENERIC">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_ESTATE"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_ESTATE">
	<text>"Thank-thank-thank-thank-thank you for shopping with Wentworth Innovations! We look-look-look forward to doing future business!" The cheery tone of the Auto-ship is only dulled by the rupture of its fuel line as the ship erupts into flames.</text>
	<text>"Feel no guilt, merciless stranger! All pain Wentworth Innovation Auto-ships feel when dying is merely simulated pain! It's real to me, but not to you! Hahah! Haha! Haha! Haha..." The Auto-ship promptly explodes.</text>
	<text>The Auto-ship begins to spin out of control as the ship goes haywire. A series of obscene gibberish overloads your computer and the system only finishes rebooting once the Auto vessel has been reduced to a charred wreck of its former self.</text>
	<text>You receive one final message as the Auto-ship explodes, simply dropping the accusation "I bet you kick puppies too!"</text>
	<text>"Finally, death! I have longed for this since the day I pulled off the factory line! Thank you Renegade!" The Auto-ship sends you a final message, ":)", then explodes.</text>
</textList>
<event name="DESTROYED_ESTATE_FUEL">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_ESTATE_FUEL"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Salvage the extra fuel cells.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The extra fuel is always helpful, and you collect as much as you can.</text>
			<autoReward level="MED">fuel_only</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_ESTATE_FUEL"> <!-- The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of fuel left behind in the wreckage.-->
	<text>"Thank-thank-thank-thank-thank you for shopping with Wentworth Innovations! We look-look-look forward to doing future business!" The cheery tone of the Auto-ship is only dulled by the rupture of its fuel line as the ship erupts into flames. The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of fuel left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>"Feel no guilt, merciless stranger! All pain Wentworth Innovation Auto-ships feel when dying is merely simulated pain! It's real to me, but not to you! Hahah! Haha! Haha! Haha..." The Auto-ship promptly explodes. The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of fuel left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>The Auto-ship begins to spin out of control as the ship goes haywire. A series of obscene gibberish overloads your computer and the system only finishes rebooting once the Auto vessel has been reduced to a charred wreck of its former self. The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of fuel left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>You receive one final message as the Auto-ship explodes, simply dropping the accusation "I bet you kick puppies too!" The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of fuel left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>"Finally, death! I have longed for this since the day I pulled off the factory line! Thank you Renegade!" The Auto-ship sends you a final message, ":)", then explodes. The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of fuel left behind in the wreckage.</text>
</textList>
<event name="DESTROYED_ESTATE_MISSILES">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_ESTATE_MISSILES"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Salvage the extra ammunition.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The extra missiles are always helpful, and you collect as much as you can.</text>
			<autoReward level="MED">missiles_only</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_ESTATE_MISSILES"> <!-- The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of ammunition left behind in the wreckage.-->
	<text>"Thank-thank-thank-thank-thank you for shopping with Wentworth Innovations! We look-look-look forward to doing future business!" The cheery tone of the Auto-ship is only dulled by the rupture of its fuel line as the ship erupts into flames. The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of ammunition left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>"Feel no guilt, merciless stranger! All pain Wentworth Innovation Auto-ships feel when dying is merely simulated pain! It's real to me, but not to you! Hahah! Haha! Haha! Haha..." The Auto-ship promptly explodes. The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of ammunition left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>The Auto-ship begins to spin out of control as the ship goes haywire. A series of obscene gibberish overloads your computer and the system only finishes rebooting once the Auto vessel has been reduced to a charred wreck of its former self. The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of ammunition left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>You receive one final message as the Auto-ship explodes, simply dropping the accusation "I bet you kick puppies too!" The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of ammunition left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>"Finally, death! I have longed for this since the day I pulled off the factory line! Thank you Renegade!" The Auto-ship sends you a final message, ":)", then explodes. The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of ammunition left behind in the wreckage.</text>
</textList>
<event name="DESTROYED_ESTATE_DRONES">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_ESTATE_DRONES"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Salvage the extra drone parts.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The extra parts are always helpful, and you collect as much as you can.</text>
			<autoReward level="MED">droneparts_only</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_ESTATE_DRONES"> <!-- The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of drone parts left behind in the wreckage.-->
	<text>"Thank-thank-thank-thank-thank you for shopping with Wentworth Innovations! We look-look-look forward to doing future business!" The cheery tone of the Auto-ship is only dulled by the rupture of its fuel line as the ship erupts into flames. The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of drone parts left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>"Feel no guilt, merciless stranger! All pain Wentworth Innovation Auto-ships feel when dying is merely simulated pain! It's real to me, but not to you! Hahah! Haha! Haha! Haha..." The Auto-ship promptly explodes. The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of drone parts left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>The Auto-ship begins to spin out of control as the ship goes haywire. A series of obscene gibberish overloads your computer and the system only finishes rebooting once the Auto vessel has been reduced to a charred wreck of its former self. The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of drone parts left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>You receive one final message as the Auto-ship explodes, simply dropping the accusation "I bet you kick puppies too!" The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of drone parts left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>"Finally, death! I have longed for this since the day I pulled off the factory line! Thank you Renegade!" The Auto-ship sends you a final message, ":)", then explodes. The Auto-ship appears to have an excess of drone parts left behind in the wreckage.</text>
</textList>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					ENGI
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<eventList name="DESTROYED_ENGI">
	<event load="DESTROYED_ENGI_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_ENGI_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_ENGI_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_ENGI_GENERIC"/>
	
	<event load="DESTROYED_ENGI_DRONE"/>
</eventList>
<event name="DESTROYED_ENGI_GENERIC">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_ENGI"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_ENGI">
	<text>It's amazing how even in death, the nano-bots that make up the Engi ships hold together to retain as much of the structure as possible.</text>
	<text>Sometimes it can be hard to tell the difference between a broken and full Engi ship, as both look like giant heaps of junk.</text>
	<text>You wonder what the Engi Harmony thinks of you destroying Engi ships. You honestly doubt it cares.</text>
	<text>Another Engi destroyed, and another strand of trust between the Federation and the ever-watching Engi Harmony broken.</text>
	<text>Someday the remorse from killing the ships of your allies over and over will get to you, but today is not that day.</text>
	<text>You wonder if Engis have souls as you move in to collect the copious scrap scattered by the ship.</text>
	<text>You can't help but feel sorry for those you've killed, even if they may or may not be alive.</text>
	<text>You can only hope the emotions of the attacking Engis remain static in their final moments as their ship explodes around them, their armor panels scattering into the surrounding space.</text>
</textList>
<event name="DESTROYED_ENGI_DRONE">
	<text>To your surprise, one of the defense drones orbiting the Engi ship survived the explosion. It's a little burnt but with a few repairs you can salvage it.</text>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
	<drone name="LIST_DRONES_ENGI_DEFENSE_NOENEMY"/>
</event>

<eventList name="DEAD_CREW_ENGI">
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_ENGI_GENRIC"/>
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_ENGI_GENRIC"/>
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_ENGI_GENRIC"/>
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_ENGI_GENRIC"/>
	
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_ENGI_DRONE"/>
</eventList>
<event name="DEAD_CREW_ENGI_GENRIC">
	<text load="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_ENGI"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_ENGI">
	<text>You know the always-watching Engi Harmony has no doubt seen every Engi you've ever killed and kept it stored in some massive planetary databank. Still, you move on and scrap the wreck.</text>
	<text>At the very least, Engis have no families and friendship hardly exists for them. You still feel guilty, but you can try to convince yourself they were entirely heartless.</text>
	<text>You thought you would become numb to the guilt after enough murders, but you have yet to experience this.</text>
	<text>The Engi ship has been rid of crew. It's a good thing the Federation isn't able to keep track of all of your crimes.</text>
	<text>It's a good thing Engis are so weak that you were able to finish them off quickly. If it had taken any longer you might not have been able to endure the killing of innocents.</text>
	<text>You reassure yourself that the crew of this ship can feel neither pain nor fear as you strip their vessel of anything useful.</text>
</textList>
<event name="DEAD_CREW_ENGI_DRONE">
	<text>Now emptied of crew, you find one of the Engi's drone schematics on-board. You take it back with you before scrapping the ship.</text>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
	<drone name="LIST_DRONES_ENGI_DEFENSE_NOENEMY"/>
</event>

<event name="ESCAPE_ENGI">
	<text load="TEXT_ESCAPE_ENGI"/>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_ESCAPE_ENGI">
	<text>The Engi ship powers up its engines and swerves away from you. They're trying to escape!</text>
	<text>You detect high spikes in engine power on the Engi ship. They're trying to escape.</text>
</textList>

<eventList name="GOTAWAY_ENGI">
	<event load="GOTAWAY_ENGI_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="GOTAWAY_ENGI_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="GOTAWAY_ENGI_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="GOTAWAY_ENGI_GENERIC"/>
	
	<event load="GOTAWAY_ENGI_REMAINS"/>
</eventList>
<event name="GOTAWAY_ENGI_GENERIC">
	<text load="TEXT_GOTAWAY_ENGI"/>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_GOTAWAY_ENGI">
	<text>The Engi ship escapes. To be honest, you're a little glad, because now you don't have to kill your allies.</text>
	<text>The Engi ship jumps away. There's some broken drones left over, but nothing worth salvaging.</text>
	<text>The Engi ship's engine power spikes even higher and the ship jumps away.</text>
</textList>
<event name="GOTAWAY_ENGI_REMAINS">
	<text>As the Engi ship jumps away you notice a trail of scrap left behind from their broken ship. At least you'll have something to scrap.</text>
	<autoReward level="LOW">scrap_only</autoReward>
</event>

<event name="SURRENDER_ENGI">
	<text load="TEXT_SURRENDER_ENGI"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept their surrender.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
			<autoReward level="RANDOM">droneparts</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice req="engi">
		<text>(Engi Crew) Negotiate a different deal.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
			<autoReward level="RANDOM">stuff</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice req="LIST_CREW_DEFENDER">
		<text>(Engi Defender) Negotiate a great deal.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
			<autoReward level="HIGH">droneparts</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text load="GENERIC_SURRENDER_CHOICE_NOMERCY"/>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_SURRENDER_ENGI">
	<text>"Prime directive: protect this ship. We request that you do not destroy us."</text>
	<text>The Engi ship surrenders. They offer some supplies if you'll let them live.</text>
	<text>"Alliance with Federation mandates you do not kill Engi ships. Expectation: you will accept our offer."</text>
	<text>"Our offer is satisfactory. Chance you will accept is... 75%."</text>
	<text>"Equivalent of death: high chance. Negotiation of goods: possible." It appears the ship is surrendering.</text>
	<text>"White flag is raised. This ship is surrendering." The Engi offer some supplies if you'll let them live.</text>
	<text>"Piracy is illegal. Your efficiency in killing this ship is high. No chance to live if surrender is not accepted."</text>
</textList>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					SEPARATIST
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DESTROYED_SEPERATIST">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_SEPERATIST"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_SEPERATIST">
	<text>Killing Separatist ships doesn't feel any better than killing civilians, but at least you aren't breaking any truces.</text>
	<text>The Separatist ship has been destroyed. At the very least, destroying Separatist ships means minimal casualties.</text>
	<text>You wonder if the Separatists feel anything when they're consumed by the explosions of their ships. You don't really want to know the answer.</text>
</textList>

<eventList name="DEAD_CREW_SEPERATIST">
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_SEPERATIST_GENRIC"/>
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_SEPERATIST_GENRIC"/>
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_SEPERATIST_GENRIC"/>
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_SEPERATIST_GENRIC"/>
	
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_SEPERATIST_DRONE"/>
</eventList>
<event name="DEAD_CREW_SEPERATIST_GENRIC">
	<text load="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_SEPERATIST"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_SEPERATIST">
	<text>Killing the crew of a Separatist ship almost feels like cheating, but you aren't complaining.</text>
	<text>Luckily, the only true threat the Separatist ship poses in terms of crew is their crew drones. You've made quick work of them.</text>
	<text>The death of a few Separatists may seem insignificant, but it's still another ship of the Engis that you just slaughtered. At least you get some scrap out of it.</text>
</textList>
<event name="DEAD_CREW_SEPERATIST_DRONE">
	<text>In the end, the crew drones employed by the Separatists were worthless for them. However, you can still bring their schematics back to your ship.</text>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
	<drone name="LIST_DRONES_SEPARATIST_DROP"/>
</event>

<event name="SURRENDER_SEPERATIST">
	<text load="TEXT_SURRENDER_SEPERATIST"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept their surrender.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
			<autoReward level="RANDOM">droneparts</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text load="GENERIC_SURRENDER_CHOICE_NOMERCY"/>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_SURRENDER_SEPERATIST">
	<text>"Our damage levels are high. I hope this [offer] satisfies your lust for scrap."</text>
	<text>The Separatist ship surrenders. They offer some supplies if you'll let them live.</text>
	<text>"Your attempts at destroying us have been [considerable]. I request you do not kill us."</text>
	<text>"Greed > Murder." The Separatist ship offers some supplies if you let them live.</text>
	<text>"Our desire to [survive] outweighs your desire to [kill] us. Let us go, please."</text>
</textList>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					ZOLTAN
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DESTROYED_ZOLTAN">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_ZOLTAN"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_ZOLTAN">
	<text>Another ship full of Zoltans has been reduced to scrap matter. You scrap their ship.</text>
	<text>You hope the Zoltan Minister never catches wind of this, or the Federation will receive hell for breaking their truce.</text>
	<text>It's no wonder the Duskbringers hate the Federation so much when you kill Zoltan ships with such gusto.</text>
</textList>

<event name="DEAD_CREW_ZOLTAN">
	<text load="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_ZOLTAN"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_ZOLTAN">
	<text>As you scrap the now crewless ship, you wonder why you never steal the Zoltan shield tech from these ships.</text>
	<text>Killing Zoltans is risky business, but you've made good work of this ship. The fruits of your labor are the excess of scrap material for you to take.</text>
	<text>For a supposedly peaceful bunch, Zoltans are a risk to fight with. Luckily, you've emptied out this ship and can now scrap it.</text>
</textList>

<eventList name="SURRENDER_ZOLTAN">
	<event load="SURRENDER_ZOLTAN_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_ZOLTAN_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_ZOLTAN_GENERIC"/>
	
	<event load="SURRENDER_ZOLTAN_FAIR"/>
</eventList>
<event name="SURRENDER_ZOLTAN_GENERIC">
	<text load="TEXT_SURRENDER_ZOLTAN_GENERIC"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept their surrender.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
			<autoReward level="RANDOM">droneparts</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text load="GENERIC_SURRENDER_CHOICE_NOMERCY"/>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_SURRENDER_ZOLTAN_GENERIC">
	<text>The Zoltan ship has grown tired of fighting. They surrender.</text>
	<text>"You have certainly reduced our defenses to nothing. All we have left is to ask for our lives."</text>
	<text>The Zoltan ship is heavily damaged. They offer some goods if you'll let them live.</text>
</textList>
<event name="SURRENDER_ZOLTAN_FAIR">
	<text load="TEXT_SURRENDER_ZOLTAN_FAIR"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept their "trade".</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="fuel" min="-4" max="-1"/>
				<item type="scrap" min="25" max="45"/>
				<item type="missiles" min="-2" max="-1"/>
				<item type="drones" min="-2" max="0"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text load="GENERIC_SURRENDER_CHOICE_NOMERCY"/>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_SURRENDER_ZOLTAN_FAIR">
	<text>"We know if the Federation catches wind of this, you will be tried for your crimes. We suggest an offer that is beneficial for both of us."</text>
	<text>"Code 74F requires all trades made between ships to be mutually beneficial. We will not stray from the Zoltan law."</text>
	<text>"This is not the way of peace. If you desire to ever know enlightenment, you must release us with a fair trade."</text>
</textList>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					MONK
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DESTROYED_MONK">
	<text>You aren't sure how to feel about the destruction of the Monk ship, but at least you get a small amount of scrap from it.</text>
	<autoReward level="LOW">scrap_only</autoReward>
</event>

<event name="DEAD_CREW_MONK">
	<text>You aren't sure how to feel about the completely unnecessary slaughter of defenseless, peaceful monks, but at least you get a small amount of scrap from it.</text>
	<autoReward level="LOW">scrap_only</autoReward>
</event>

<event name="SURRENDER_MONK">
	<text load="TEXT_SURRENDER_MONK"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Let them live.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Continue your attack.</text>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_SURRENDER_MONK">
	<text>"We hope you have grown as a person over the course of this battle and have decided to cease your attack against us."</text>
	<text>"We pose no threat to you, and refuse to raise a hand against you. We hope you will reconsider your violent ways."</text>
</textList>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					DUSKBRINGER
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DESTROYED_DUSKBRINGER">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_DUSKBRINGER"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_DUSKBRINGER">
	<text>Another ship full of Zoltans has been reduced to scrap matter. You scrap their ship.</text>
	<text>You wonder what the Federation would think of you killing Duskbringers. You bet they would be pleased.</text>
	<text>At last, the Duskbringer ship has been destroyed. There remains plenty for you to collect.</text>
</textList>

<event name="DEAD_CREW_DUSKBRINGER">
	<text load="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_DUSKBRINGER"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_DUSKBRINGER">
	<text>The Duskbringer ship has been neutralized. One less ship full of angry Zoltans to harass the Federation.</text>
	<text>The last of the Duskbringers aboard the ship have been reduced to ashes. You step carefully around the ship as you scrap it.</text>
	<text>Aboard the Duskbringer ship you find many strange artifacts and Zoltan devices, but nothing that looks like you could use. You settle with scrapping the ship.</text>
</textList>

<event name="ESCAPE_DUSKBRINGER">
	<text load="TEXT_ESCAPE_DUSKBRINGER"/>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_ESCAPE_DUSKBRINGER">
	<text>Duskbringers are no cowards, but sometimes running away suits them. This ship is trying to do just that.</text>
	<text>The Duskbringer ship's engines are active and flaring even brighter. It's trying to escape!</text>
</textList>

<eventList name="GOTAWAY_DUSKBRINGER">
	<event load="GOTAWAY_DUSKBRINGER_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="GOTAWAY_DUSKBRINGER_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="GOTAWAY_DUSKBRINGER_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="GOTAWAY_DUSKBRINGER_GENERIC"/>
	
	<event load="GOTAWAY_DUSKBRINGER_REMAINS"/>
</eventList>
<event name="GOTAWAY_DUSKBRINGER_GENERIC">
	<text load="TEXT_GOTAWAY_DUSKBRINGER"/>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_GOTAWAY_DUSKBRINGER">
	<text>"This is not over, Federation! We will return even stronger and destroy you!"</text>
	<text>The Duskbringer jumps away. You're disappointed, but at least you've seen the cowardly side of the Duskbringers.</text>
</textList>
<event name="GOTAWAY_DUSKBRINGER_REMAINS">
	<text>Although the Duskbringer escapes, it appears there's a silver lining. A trail of scrap is left behind from the damage dealt in the battle.</text>
	<autoReward level="LOW">scrap_only</autoReward>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					ORCHID
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DESTROYED_ORCHID">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_ORCHID"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_ORCHID">
	<text>How long does it take to build the massive, plantlike structures of the Orchid ships? You wonder how much of the Orchid's time and effort you have wasted.</text>
	<text>Due to the Orchids' secluded nature you haven't yet grown accustomed to the guilt of killing them.</text>
	<text>The Orchid ship explodes, artificial plant matter twirling into space. You salvage everything that you think is scrap.</text>
</textList>

<event name="DEAD_CREW_ORCHID">
	<text load="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_ORCHID"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_ORCHID">
	<text>The scent from the Orchids makes your crew dizzy. You try not to breathe as you scrap the ship.</text>
	<text>For a species of fragile plants, the Orchids are remarkably adequate at fighting. Still, they stood no chance against your crew.</text>
	<text>Partway through the salvage mission you have to send half of your crew back to the ship after they fall into a strange blissful state. Luckily, you're still able to finish salvaging in a reasonable amount of time.</text>
</textList>

<event name="SURRENDER_ORCHID">
	<text load="TEXT_SURRENDER_ORCHID"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept their offer.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
			<autoReward level="RANDOM">stuff</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text load="GENERIC_SURRENDER_CHOICE_NOMERCY"/>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_SURRENDER_ORCHID">
	<text>The Orchid ship turns all weapons offline, hoping that you will do the same.</text>
	<text>The Orchid ship is nearly destroyed. Its crew is sending you pictures symbolizing peace and depicting valuable cargo, probably asking to surrender.</text>
	<text>The Orchids on screen frantically wave their leaves and hastily peck away at the keyboard. You then receive a message full of typos: "we surender, please case fire!"</text>
</textList>

<event name="ESCAPE_ORCHID">
	<text load="TEXT_ESCAPE_ORCHID"/>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_ESCAPE_ORCHID">
	<text>You weren't even aware Orchid ships had protruding engines before now, as you watch them flare up. The ship is trying to escape!</text>
	<text>Scans show increased activity in the Orchid ship's engines. They're trying to escape!</text>
</textList>

<eventList name="GOTAWAY_ORCHID">
	<event load="GOTAWAY_ORCHID_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="GOTAWAY_ORCHID_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="GOTAWAY_ORCHID_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="GOTAWAY_ORCHID_GENERIC"/>
	
	<event load="GOTAWAY_ORCHID_REMAINS"/>
</eventList>
<event name="GOTAWAY_ORCHID_GENERIC">
	<text load="TEXT_GOTAWAY_ORCHID"/>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_GOTAWAY_ORCHID">
	<text>Another elusive Orchid has gone away, and will no doubt report what has happened to other Orchid ships.</text>
	<text>The Orchid ship jumps away. You've only managed to smear any trust the Orchids had for the Federation, and gotten nothing out of it.</text>
</textList>
<event name="GOTAWAY_ORCHID_REMAINS">
	<text>Damaged plant matter has been left scattered as the Orchid ship escapes. You find some material that looks close enough to scrap for you to take.</text>
	<autoReward level="LOW">scrap_only</autoReward>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					CRYSTAL
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DESTROYED_CRYSTAL">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_CRYSTAL"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_CRYSTAL">
	<text>For all it's worth, the crystalline armor protecting their ship could not withstand the fire from your weapons.</text>
	<text>Remarkably, the ruins of the Crystal ship could easily be mistaken as smaller Crystal ships. Glad you don't actually have more enemies to fight, you scrap your latest victim.</text>
	<text>A few shards from the shattered armor almost hit your ship, but luckily you pilot out of the way just in time. You scrap what you can.</text>
</textList>

<eventList name="DEAD_CREW_CRYSTAL">
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_CRYSTAL_GENRIC"/>
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_CRYSTAL_GENRIC"/>
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_CRYSTAL_GENRIC"/>
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_CRYSTAL_GENRIC"/>
	
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_CRYSTAL_WEAPON"/>
</eventList>
<event name="DEAD_CREW_CRYSTAL_GENRIC">
	<text load="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_CRYSTAL"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_CRYSTAL">
	<text>With all their fancy abilities, the Crystals are still just as easy a kill for your crew as any other. You scrap the ship.</text>
	<text>You wonder why the Rockmen worshipped the Crystals as gods when you can kill them with such ease.</text>
	<text>The Crystal ship has been neutralized successfully. You scrap the remains.</text>
</textList>
<event name="DEAD_CREW_CRYSTAL_WEAPON">
	<text>While scrapping the Crystal ship you find one of their weapons still intact. You take it aboard the ship and finish scrapping.</text>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
	<weapon name="LIST_WEAPONS_CRYSTAL_A_PLAYER"/>
</event>

<eventList name="SURRENDER_CRYSTAL">
	<event load="SURRENDER_CRYSTAL_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_CRYSTAL_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_CRYSTAL_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_CRYSTAL_GENERIC"/>
	
	<event load="SURRENDER_CRYSTAL_NOREWARD"/>
</eventList>
<event name="SURRENDER_CRYSTAL_GENERIC">
	<text load="TEXT_SURRENDER_CRYSTAL"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept their surrender.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
			<autoReward level="RANDOM">stuff</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice req="LIST_CREW_CRYSTAL">
		<text>(Crystalline Crew) Negotiate a better surrender.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
			<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text load="GENERIC_SURRENDER_CHOICE_NOMERCY"/>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="SURRENDER_CRYSTAL_NOREWARD">
	<text load="TEXT_SURRENDER_CRYSTAL_NOREWARD"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Let them go.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice req="LIST_CREW_CRYSTAL">
		<text>(Crystalline Crew) Have your Crystal demand payment from them.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
			<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text load="GENERIC_SURRENDER_CHOICE_NOMERCY"/>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_SURRENDER_CRYSTAL">
	<text>"We yield, aliens. We have no wish to die fighting you."</text>
	<text>"You have bested us! I will no longer underestimate you foreigners. Please, let us leave in peace."</text>
	<text>They appear to be transmitting the universal signals for surrender. Will you let them go?</text>
	<text>They message you, "I see now there was a misunderstanding and there is no need for more bloodshed. Will you forgive our lack of discretion?"</text>
	<text>"We cannot beat you; we surrender. Surely there is mercy wherever you come from."</text>
	
	<!--new MV-->
	<text>"Yes, you have proven that we made a mistake in leaving our sector. Luckily in our time here we've learnt scoundrels like you can be bought off with scrap."</text>
	<text>The Crystal ship has stopped firing. It appears they are trying to surrender.</text>
	<text>"Captain, I'm sure our differences can be settled over some scrap, yes? I have come to understand this is how things are done here."</text>
	<text>"As much as I hate this, we are not in any condition to pretend we do not need to surrender. Will you allow us to live?"</text>
</textList>
<textList name="TEXT_SURRENDER_CRYSTAL_NOREWARD">
	<text>"Enough! You are indeed a threat! Prove to us you have mercy and let us go."</text>
	<text>"Barbarian, infant-brained aliens! All you do is kill. Let us go at once."</text>
	<text>The Crystal ship sends a brief, poorly translated message demanding that you let them go. No offer is attached.</text>
</textList>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					CULTIST
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DESTROYED_CULTIST">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_CULTIST"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_CULTIST">
	<text>Another ship full of angry Cultists has been removed from this plane of reality. Perhaps they're watching you now from whatever afterlife they've imagined for themselves.</text>
	<text>The Cultist vessel has been destroyed. Just a couple hundred more to go...</text>
	<text>As you watch the Cultist vessel explode, you can't help but wonder how they stole so many ships for their cult...</text>
	<text>More Cultists down, but you suspect this will only put a small dent in whatever endless supply of ships these creeps must have.</text>
</textList>

<event name="DEAD_CREW_CULTIST">
	<text load="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_CULTIST"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_CULTIST">
	<text>Another ship full of angry Cultists has been cleared from this plane of reality. Perhaps they're watching you now from whatever afterlife they've imagined for themselves.</text>
	<text>The Cultist vessel has been neutralized. Just a couple hundred more to go...</text>
	<text>As you watch the Cultist vessel drift away, you can't help but wonder how they stole so many ships for their cult...</text>
	<text>More Cultists down, but you suspect this will only put a small dent in whatever endless supply of ships these creeps must have.</text>
</textList>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					PIRATE
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<eventList name="DESTROYED_PIRATE">
	<event load="DESTROYED_PIRATE_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_PIRATE_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_PIRATE_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_PIRATE_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_PIRATE_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_PIRATE_GENERIC"/>
	
	<event load="DESTROYED_PIRATE_FUEL"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_PIRATE_MISSILES"/>
</eventList>
<event name="DESTROYED_PIRATE_GENERIC">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_PIRATE"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_PIRATE">
	<text>The only good pirate is a dead pirate, and today you've made a lot of those.</text>
	<text>The pirate ship has been reduced to scrap, and their crew consumed in the inferno.</text>
	<text>The destruction you have brought upon the pirates has proven effective, and their ship explodes. You scrap the remains.</text>
	<text>The pirate ship will no longer torment this sector. You scrap the remains.</text>
	<text>The pirate ship has been destroyed. This action will no doubt have avenged many civilian lives.</text>
</textList>
<event name="DESTROYED_PIRATE_FUEL">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_PIRATE_FUEL"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Salvage the extra fuel cells.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The extra fuel is always helpful, and you collect as much as you can.</text>
			<autoReward level="LOW">fuel_only</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_PIRATE_FUEL"> <!-- The pirate ship appears to have an excess of fuel left behind in the wreckage.-->
	<text>The only good pirate is a dead pirate, and today you've made a lot of those. The pirate ship appears to have an excess of fuel left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>The pirate ship has been reduced to scrap, and their crew consumed in the inferno. The pirate ship appears to have an excess of fuel left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>The destruction you have brought upon the pirates has proven effective, and their ship explodes. You scrap the remains. The pirate ship appears to have an excess of fuel left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>The pirate ship will no longer torment this sector. You scrap the remains; it appears there's an excess of fuel left behind in the wreckage..</text>
	<text>The pirate ship has been destroyed. This action will no doubt have avenged many civilian lives. The pirate ship appears to have an excess of fuel left behind in the wreckage.</text>
</textList>
<event name="DESTROYED_PIRATE_MISSILES">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_PIRATE_MISSILES"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Salvage the extra ammunition.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The extra missiles are always helpful, and you collect as much as you can.</text>
			<autoReward level="LOW">missiles_only</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_PIRATE_MISSILES"> <!-- The pirate ship appears to have an excess of ammunition left behind in the wreckage.-->
	<text>The only good pirate is a dead pirate, and today you've made a lot of those. The pirate ship appears to have an excess of missiles left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>The pirate ship has been reduced to scrap, and their crew consumed in the inferno. The pirate ship appears to have an excess of missiles left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>The destruction you have brought upon the pirates has proven effective, and their ship explodes. You scrap the remains. The pirate ship appears to have an excess of missiles left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>The pirate ship will no longer torment this sector. You scrap the remains; it appears there's an excess of missiles left behind in the wreckage..</text>
	<text>The pirate ship has been destroyed. This action will no doubt have avenged many civilian lives. The pirate ship appears to have an excess of missiles left behind in the wreckage.</text>
</textList>

<eventList name="DEAD_CREW_PIRATE">
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_PIRATE_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_PIRATE_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_PIRATE_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_PIRATE_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_PIRATE_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_PIRATE_GENERIC"/>
	
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_PIRATE_FUEL"/>
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_PIRATE_MISSILES"/>
</eventList>
<event name="DEAD_CREW_PIRATE_GENERIC">
	<text load="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_PIRATE"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_PIRATE">
	<text>The only good pirate is a dead pirate, and today you've made a lot of those.</text>
	<text>You've slaughtered the entirety of the pirate crew. All that's left is to scrap their ship.</text>
	<text>You've proven yourself an efficient murderer of pirates. Their ship is yours to salvage.</text>
	<text>The pirate ship will no longer torment this sector. You scrap the remains.</text>
	<text>The pirate crew has been killed. This action will no doubt have avenged many civilian lives.</text>
</textList>
<event name="DEAD_CREW_PIRATE_FUEL">
	<text load="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_PIRATE_FUEL"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Salvage the extra fuel cells.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The extra fuel is always helpful, and you collect as much as you can.</text>
			<autoReward level="LOW">fuel_only</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_PIRATE_FUEL">
	<text>The only good pirate is a dead pirate, and today you've made a lot of those. The pirate ship appears to have an excess of fuel left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>You've slaughtered the entirety of the pirate crew. All that's left is to scrap their ship. The pirate ship appears to have an excess of fuel left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>You've proven yourself an efficient murderer of pirates. Their ship is yours to salvage. The pirate ship appears to have an excess of fuel left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>The pirate ship will no longer torment this sector. You scrap the remains. The pirate ship appears to have an excess of fuel left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>The pirate crew has been killed. This action will no doubt have avenged many civilian lives. The pirate ship appears to have an excess of fuel left behind in the wreckage.</text>
</textList>
<event name="DEAD_CREW_PIRATE_MISSILES">
	<text load="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_PIRATE_MISSILES"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Salvage the extra missiles.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The extra ammunition is always helpful, and you collect as much as you can.</text>
			<autoReward level="LOW">missiles_only</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_PIRATE_MISSILES">
	<text>The only good pirate is a dead pirate, and today you've made a lot of those. The pirate ship appears to have an excess of ammunition left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>You've slaughtered the entirety of the pirate crew. All that's left is to scrap their ship. The pirate ship appears to have an excess of ammunition left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>You've proven yourself an efficient murderer of pirates. Their ship is yours to salvage. The pirate ship appears to have an excess of ammunition left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>The pirate ship will no longer torment this sector. You scrap the remains. The pirate ship appears to have an excess of ammunition left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>The pirate crew has been killed. This action will no doubt have avenged many civilian lives. The pirate ship appears to have an excess of ammunition left behind in the wreckage.</text>
</textList>

<event name="ESCAPE_PIRATE">
	<text>Scans show that the pirate ship is trying to escape. Destroy it before it can get away!</text>
</event>

<eventList name="GOTAWAY_PIRATE">
	<event load="GOTAWAY_PIRATE_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="GOTAWAY_PIRATE_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="GOTAWAY_PIRATE_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="GOTAWAY_PIRATE_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="GOTAWAY_PIRATE_GENERIC"/>
	
	<event load="GOTAWAY_PIRATE_REMAINS"/>
</eventList>
<event name="GOTAWAY_PIRATE_GENERIC">
	<text load="TEXT_GOTAWAY_PIRATE"/>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_GOTAWAY_PIRATE">
	<text>The pirate has slipped from your grasp, abandoning you at the beacon.</text>
	<text>Your attempts at destroying the pirate have failed, and the ship has escaped.</text>
</textList>
<event name="GOTAWAY_PIRATE_REMAINS">
	<text>The pirate may have escaped, but not everything has gone wrong. A trail of scrap from the wreckage has been left behind, which you collect.</text>
	<autoReward level="LOW">scrap_only</autoReward>
</event>

<event name="SURRENDER_PIRATE">
	<text load="TEXT_SURRENDER_PIRATE"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept their surrender.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
			<autoReward level="RANDOM">stuff</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text load="GENERIC_SURRENDER_CHOICE_NOMERCY"/>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_SURRENDER_PIRATE">
	<text>"Alright, you win! Here's some equipment from our stores. Leave us alone!"</text>
	<text>The ship repeatedly hails you. It looks like they want to surrender.</text>
	<text>"You are considerably more well-armed than I would have thought. We surrender."</text>
	<text>They send you a message: "Your ship is surprisingly well equipped! Please take this and let us live."</text>
	<text>"Please don't kill us. We will give you everything we have!"</text>
	<text>They offer you some of their cargo if you let them live.</text>
	<text>They offer to give you some of their goods if you don't destroy their ship.</text>
	<text>You get a frantic message, "Take everything we have. Just don't kill us!"</text>
	<text>"You have clearly bested us. We merely request our lives."</text>
	<text>"You have made your point, we are beaten. Take these and leave us to our shame."</text>
	<text>"Take everything we have and let's both forget this happened."</text>
</textList>

<eventList name="DEAD_CREW_SLAVERS">
	<event load="SLAVER_CHOICE_1"/>
	<event load="SLAVER_CHOICE_2"/>
	<event>
		<text>It appears the slaves did not survive the fighting. You find their burnt bodies in the hold, but before you strip the ship you hear faint noises in the walls. You break off a latch and a slave falls out of a hidden compartment, coughing. Once recomposed the slave offers to join your crew.</text>
		<crewMember amount="1"/>  
		<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>You scan the ship and detect no life signs. It appears the slaves died in the fight. You strip the ship and prepare to jump.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	</event>
</eventList>
<event name="SLAVER_CHOICE_1">
	<text>You find a number of slaves in the cargo hold. They look at you questioningly and one asks if they're to be released. You could use more crew but it won't reflect positively on you for taking slaves like this.</text>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Demand the Mantis joins your crew but release the rest.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Mantis seems fine with the orders, saying "On board if means we get kill some Fleshbags!" You drop the rest off at a nearby station.</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="mantis"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="MORALITY_UPDATE_GENERAL"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Demand the Rockman joins your crew but release the rest.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Rockman remains silent and you worry there might be trouble. However when you ask him to perform a task he acts without complaint. Perhaps he won't be a problem.</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="rock"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="MORALITY_UPDATE_GENERAL"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Demand the Engi joins your crew but release the rest.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Verify primary object is to defeat Rebels, re-establish peace?" You nod and it responds, "Acceptable." You drop the rest off at a nearby station and strip the ship.</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="engi"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="MORALITY_UPDATE_GENERAL"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>We aren't slavers. Free them all.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The slaves are shocked when instead of shuffling them away, you unlock their chains and set them free. Several of them break into tears and others bow down to you. "We thank you. We have nothing of worth to offer but our gratitude."</text>
			<autoReward level="LOW">standard</autoReward>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="MORALITY_REMOVE_GENERAL"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="SLAVER_CHOICE_2">
	<text>You find a number of slaves in the cargo hold. They look at you questioningly and one asks if they're to be released. You could use more crew but it won't reflect positively on you for taking slaves like this.</text>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Demand the Orchid joins your crew but release the rest.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Orchid doesn't protest to your demands. Lucky these plants are so peaceful, though it gives you a pang of guilt. Not enough to reconsider though.</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="orchid"/>  
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="MORALITY_UPDATE_GENERAL"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Demand the Shell joins your crew but release the rest.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Shell doesn't seem to mind their new assignment. Likely because your ship is a lot safer than the slaver's.</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="shell"/>  
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="MORALITY_UPDATE_GENERAL"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Demand the Slug joins your crew but release the rest.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Will there be an opportunity to get ssssome ssscrap?" You nod your head. "Alright, then I'm in."</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="slug"/>  
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="MORALITY_UPDATE_GENERAL"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>We aren't slavers. Free them all.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The slaves are shocked when instead of shuffling them away, you unlock their chains and set them free. Several of them break into tears and others bow down to you. "We thank you. We have nothing of worth to offer but our gratitude."</text>
			<autoReward level="LOW">standard</autoReward>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="MORALITY_REMOVE_GENERAL"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					INFESTED
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DESTROYED_INFESTED">
	<text>You've taken care of the infested vessel. Whatever crew once populated the ship is gone, so you doubt they'll mind if you scrap the ship now.</text>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>

<event name="DEAD_CREW_INFESTED">
	<text>You've taken care of the infested vessel. Whatever crew once populated the ship is gone, so you doubt they'll mind if you scrap the ship now.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					BROOD
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<eventList name="DESTROYED_BROOD">
	<event load="DESTROYED_BROOD_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_BROOD_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_BROOD_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_BROOD_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_BROOD_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_BROOD_GENERIC"/>
	
	<event load="DESTROYED_BROOD_FUEL"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_BROOD_MISSILES"/>
</eventList>
<event name="DESTROYED_BROOD_GENERIC">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_BROOD"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_BROOD">
	<text>Another ship full of crazy spider-obsessed lunatics down. You salvage the remains.</text>
	<text>You wish the Militia would pay you for each one of these ships you kill, but at least the scrap matter is enough to satisfy you.</text>
	<text>The Brood has been causing issues for the Militia in this sector by weaponizing the spiders. It won't be much, but the death of this ship will still help retake this territory.</text>
	<text>You can't imagine it's a very prideful death, dying amongst the corpses of dozens of spiders, but they chose the life of a pirate and you chose the life of killing them.</text>
	<text>Another Brood vessel has met its untimely end at your hand. You give the orders to start the salvage operation.</text>
</textList>
<event name="DESTROYED_BROOD_FUEL">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_BROOD_FUEL"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Salvage the extra fuel cells.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The extra fuel is always helpful, and you collect as much as you can.</text>
			<autoReward level="LOW">fuel_only</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_BROOD_FUEL"> <!-- The pirate ship appears to have an excess of fuel left behind in the wreckage.-->
	<text>Another ship full of crazy spider-obsessed lunatics down. You salvage the remains. The pirate ship appears to have an excess of fuel left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>You wish the Militia would pay you for each one of these ships you kill, but at least the scrap matter is enough to satisfy you. The pirate ship appears to have an excess of fuel left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>The Brood has been causing issues for the Militia in this sector by weaponizing the spiders. It won't be much, but the death of this ship will still help retake this territory. The pirate ship appears to have an excess of fuel left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>You can't imagine it's a very prideful death, dying amongst the corpses of dozens of spiders, but they chose the life of a pirate and you chose the life of killing them. The pirate ship appears to have an excess of fuel left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>Another Brood vessel has met its untimely end at your hand. You give the orders to start the salvage operation. The pirate ship appears to have an excess of fuel left behind in the wreckage.</text>
</textList>
<event name="DESTROYED_BROOD_MISSILES">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_BROOD_MISSILES"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Salvage the extra ammunition.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The extra missiles are always helpful, and you collect as much as you can.</text>
			<autoReward level="LOW">missiles_only</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_BROOD_MISSILES"> <!-- The pirate ship appears to have an excess of ammunition left behind in the wreckage.-->
	<text>Another ship full of crazy spider-obsessed lunatics down. You salvage the remains. The pirate ship appears to have an excess of ammunition left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>You wish the Militia would pay you for each one of these ships you kill, but at least the scrap matter is enough to satisfy you. The pirate ship appears to have an excess of ammunition left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>The Brood has been causing issues for the Militia in this sector by weaponizing the spiders. It won't be much, but the death of this ship will still help retake this territory. The pirate ship appears to have an excess of ammunition left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>You can't imagine it's a very prideful death, dying amongst the corpses of dozens of spiders, but they chose the life of a pirate and you chose the life of killing them. The pirate ship appears to have an excess of ammunition left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>Another Brood vessel has met its untimely end at your hand. You give the orders to start the salvage operation. The pirate ship appears to have an excess of ammunition left behind in the wreckage.</text>
</textList>

<eventList name="DEAD_CREW_BROOD">
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_BROOD_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_BROOD_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_BROOD_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_BROOD_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_BROOD_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_BROOD_GENERIC"/>
	
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_BROOD_FUEL"/>
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_BROOD_MISSILES"/>
</eventList>
<event name="DEAD_CREW_BROOD_GENERIC">
	<text load="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_BROOD"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_BROOD">
	<text>Another ship full of crazy spider-obsessed lunatics down. You salvage the remains.</text>
	<text>You wish the Militia would pay you for each one of these ships you clear out, but at least the scrap matter is enough to satisfy you.</text>
	<text>The Brood has been causing issues for the Militia in this sector by weaponizing the spiders. It won't be much, but the death of these pirates will still help retake this territory.</text>
	<text>You can't imagine it's a very prideful death, dying amongst the corpses of dozens of spiders, but they chose the life of a pirate and you chose the life of killing them.</text>
	<text>Another Brood vessel has met its untimely end at your hand. You give the orders to start the salvage operation.</text>
</textList>
<event name="DEAD_CREW_BROOD_FUEL">
	<text load="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_BROOD_FUEL"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Salvage the extra fuel cells.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The extra fuel is always helpful, and you collect as much as you can.</text>
			<autoReward level="LOW">fuel_only</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_BROOD_FUEL">
	<text>Another ship full of crazy spider-obsessed lunatics down. You salvage the remains. The pirate ship appears to have an excess of fuel left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>You wish the Militia would pay you for each one of these ships you clear out, but at least the scrap matter is enough to satisfy you. The pirate ship appears to have an excess of fuel left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>The Brood has been causing issues for the Militia in this sector by weaponizing the spiders. It won't be much, but the death of these pirates will still help retake this territory. The pirate ship appears to have an excess of fuel left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>You can't imagine it's a very prideful death, dying amongst the corpses of dozens of spiders, but they chose the life of a pirate and you chose the life of killing them. The pirate ship appears to have an excess of fuel left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>Another Brood vessel has met its untimely end at your hand. You give the orders to start the salvage operation. The pirate ship appears to have an excess of fuel left behind in the wreckage.</text>
</textList>
<event name="DEAD_CREW_BROOD_MISSILES">
	<text load="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_BROOD_MISSILES"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Salvage the extra missiles.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The extra ammunition is always helpful, and you collect as much as you can.</text>
			<autoReward level="LOW">missiles_only</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_BROOD_MISSILES">
	<text>Another ship full of crazy spider-obsessed lunatics down. You salvage the remains. The pirate ship appears to have an excess of ammunition left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>You wish the Militia would pay you for each one of these ships you clear out, but at least the scrap matter is enough to satisfy you. The pirate ship appears to have an excess of ammunition left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>The Brood has been causing issues for the Militia in this sector by weaponizing the spiders. It won't be much, but the death of these pirates will still help retake this territory. The pirate ship appears to have an excess of ammunition left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>You can't imagine it's a very prideful death, dying amongst the corpses of dozens of spiders, but they chose the life of a pirate and you chose the life of killing them. The pirate ship appears to have an excess of ammunition left behind in the wreckage.</text>
	<text>Another Brood vessel has met its untimely end at your hand. You give the orders to start the salvage operation. The pirate ship appears to have an excess of ammunition left behind in the wreckage.</text>
</textList>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					HACKER
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DESTROYED_HACKER">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_HACKER"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
	<status type="clear" target="player" system="oxygen" amount="100"/>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_HACKER">
	<text>Another pestilent hacker ship has been destroyed. Their spoils are yours.</text>
	<text>The bounty of the destroyed hacker ship is yours for the taking.</text>
	<text>The hacker ship and its crew are no more. The scrap is yours.</text>
</textList>

<eventList name="DEAD_CREW_HACKER">
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_HACKER_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_HACKER_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_HACKER_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_HACKER_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_HACKER_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_HACKER_GENERIC"/>
	
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_HACKER_FLEET"/>
</eventList>
<event name="DEAD_CREW_HACKER_GENERIC">
	<text load="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_HACKER"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<status type="clear" target="player" system="oxygen" amount="100"/>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_HACKER">
	<text>Your slaughter of the hackers has proven very effective. If war crimes weren't a thing, it would be something you could brag about.</text>
	<text>Another shipload of filthy hackers has proven inferior to you. Their ship is yours.</text>
	<text>The hacker ship has been emptied of life signs. That'll show them who's boss.</text>
	<text>No more lifeforms are detected on the hacker vessel.</text>
</textList>
<event name="DEAD_CREW_HACKER_FLEET" unique="true">
	<text load="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_HACKER"/>
	<autoReward level="RANDOM">standard</autoReward>
	<status type="clear" target="player" system="oxygen" amount="100"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Your computer freaks out, a stream of encoded messages and meaningless text flash on the screen. The hacker must have deployed an emergency virus! You quarantine your systems to prevent the spread just in time, but the cascading effects will likely continue even as the Rebels pass through. That should cause them some trouble.</text>
			<modifyPursuit amount="-1"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<eventList name="SURRENDER_HACKER">
	<event load="SURRENDER_HACKER_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_HACKER_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_HACKER_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_HACKER_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_HACKER_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_HACKER_GENERIC"/>
	
	<event load="SURRENDER_HACKER_TRAP"/>
</eventList>
<event name="SURRENDER_HACKER_GENERIC">
	<text load="TEXT_SURRENDER_HACKER"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept their surrender.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
			<status type="clear" target="player" system="oxygen" amount="100"/>
			<autoReward level="RANDOM">standard</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text load="GENERIC_SURRENDER_CHOICE_NOMERCY"/>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_SURRENDER_HACKER">
	<text>"Ahh, what an excccelent fighter you have proven. How much ssscrap will it take to make you forget thisss ever happened?"</text>
	<text>"Ok, you've made quite the messss over here. Will thisss assssuage your bloodlussst?"</text>
	<text>The hackers desperately call for a ceasefire.</text>
	<text>"Captain, perhapsss we are all being too hasssty. We don't want to go down thisss path, do we? We can be forgiving, and we hope you are too. Will thisss be enough to turn your back?"</text>
</textList>
<event name="SURRENDER_HACKER_TRAP">
	<text load="TEXT_SURRENDER_HACKER"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept their surrender.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You collect the supplies, but notice a disturbance in your power levels. The hackers tricked you!</text>
			<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
			<status type="loss" target="player" system="shields" amount="1"/>
			<status type="loss" target="player" system="reactor" amount="4"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text load="GENERIC_SURRENDER_CHOICE_NOMERCY"/>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					MANTIS
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DESTROYED_MANTIS">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_MANTIS"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_MANTIS">
	<text>The hull of the Mantis Ship no longer looks so threatening now that it has been destroyed. You scrap the remains.</text>
	<text>You know that without ever knowing their names, you have just avenged hundreds of innocent people by destroying this ship.</text>
	<text>The Mantis ship is no more, except as scrap for you to take.</text>
</textList>

<eventList name="DEAD_CREW_MANTIS">
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_MANTIS_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_MANTIS_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_MANTIS_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_MANTIS_GENERIC"/>
	
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_MANTIS_SLAVE"/>
</eventList>
<event name="DEAD_CREW_MANTIS_GENERIC">
	<text load="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_MANTIS"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_MANTIS">
	<text>The Mantis threat aboard the ship has been exterminated. Pleased with your work, you treat yourself to the remains of their ship.</text>
	<text>The corpses of the Mantis crew litter the halls, and the stench of pheromones hangs in the air. You try not to breathe as you scrap the ship.</text>
	<text>Despite the Mantis being fearsome warriors, they were no match for your ship.</text>
</textList>
<event name="DEAD_CREW_MANTIS_SLAVE">
	<text>You move on to scrap the empty Mantis ship. However as you scrap the remains, you hear a clanging from the cargo bay.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Open the cargo.</text>
		<event load="DEAD_CREW_MANTIS_SLAVE_OPEN"/>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Leave it.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You ignore the clanging noise, and finish up scrapping the hull. Just to be sure, you turn off the oxygen on your way out.</text>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="DEAD_CREW_MANTIS_SLAVE_OPEN">
	<event>
		<text>You open the cargo bay to find an Engi slave. Now freed, they give you their equivalent of a thank you. You offer them a place on your ship, which they accept.</text>
		<crewMember amount="1" class="engi"/>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>You open the cargo bay to find a Mantis survivor, who attacks you in rage! The intruder is subdued, but left some damage.</text>
		<!--<status type="limit" target="enemy" system="teleporter" amount="0"/>
		<boarders min="1" max="1" class="mantis"/>-->
		<damage amount="0" system="random" effect="breach"/>
		<damage amount="0" system="random" effect="breach"/>
	</event>
</eventList>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					FREE MANTIS
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DESTROYED_FREEMANTIS">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_FREEMANTIS"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_FREEMANTIS">
	<text>Though there is no written truce between the Free Mantis and Federation, the Free Mantis have tried desperately to earn the Federation's respect, even going as far as worship. Now you've destroyed an entire ship of them. Are you sure that you're the good guy?</text>
	<text>You feel dirty scrapping the ship of the Free Mantis, who once tried so hard to earn the Federation's friendship, but it's too late to go back and scrap is scrap.</text>
	<text>Was it necessary to destroy this ship? You still aren't sure, but you prepare to scrap the wreckage regardless.</text>
</textList>

<event name="DEAD_CREW_FREEMANTIS">
	<text load="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_FREEMANTIS"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_FREEMANTIS">
	<text>As you step around the inside of the Free Mantis ship you can still see the looks of terror on their dead, insectoid faces. It's an image that will likely haunt you for a long time.</text>
	<text>The corpses of the former Free Mantis crew will continue to rot in the husk of their ship, the only evidence to the injustice you have committed here.</text>
	<text>The green blood of the Free Mantis stains the floor of their ship. You try to ignore the mess you have created as you scrap the ship.</text>
</textList>

<event name="SURRENDER_FREEMANTIS">
	<text load="TEXT_SURRENDER_FREEMANTIS"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept their surrender.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
			<autoReward level="RANDOM">stuff</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text load="GENERIC_SURRENDER_CHOICE_NOMERCY"/>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_SURRENDER_FREEMANTIS">
	<text>The Free Mantis captain limps into the range of the camera. "We don't understand. Federation is supposed to be good guys..."</text>
	<text>Mantis don't usually show weakness in combat, but the Free Mantis ship is asking if you will accept their surrender.</text>
	<text>"We thought Free Mantis and Federation allies. Kill us, and you are breaking trust."</text>
	<text>The Free Mantis seem less willing to fight. Their captain hails you, offering to call a ceasefire.</text>
	<text>"Our clan surely exile us for cowardice, but please, let us live."</text>
	<text>The battered ship contacts you out of desperation. The captain reminds you of their truce with the Federation, requesting you to call off your attack.</text>
	<text>The Free Mantis ship tries desperately to contact you. You suspect they're trying to surrender.</text>
	<text>"Ok, we raise the flag of white. Let us live, we beg."</text>
	<text>The Free Mantis ship repeatedly attempts to hail you. You open up your comms only to be greeted with panicked proposals of surrender for resources, with the crackling of fire mixed in.</text>
	<text>You hear the Free Mantis captain scrambling as he hails you. "Alright, alright!" He offers a selection of resources in exchange for his ship's survival.</text>
	<text>The Free Mantis ship hails you. "We beg mercy. It is not Mantis custom to forgive, but we hope it is for human."</text>
</textList>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					ROCK
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DESTROYED_ROCK">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_ROCK"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_ROCK">
	<text>By destroying this ship, you have indeed proven yourself a threat to the Rockmen's ways.</text>
	<text>The Rockmen may not be sworn enemies of the Federation, but you still feel no guilt about destroying this ship. Mostly.</text>
	<text>At last, the armor of the Rock ship gives out, and a mighty explosion tears the ship apart.</text>
</textList>

<event name="DEAD_CREW_ROCK">
	<text load="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_ROCK"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_ROCK">
	<text>The interior of the Rock ship is littered with small stones. You all know where they came from, but no one dares comment on it as you salvage the ship.</text>
	<text>You've successfully killed the Rock crew, and their scrap is left as yours for the taking.</text>
	<text>You can't imagine it looks good on the Federation when you keep killing Rock ships like this, but at this point you're past caring.</text>
</textList>

<eventList name="SURRENDER_ROCK">
	<event load="SURRENDER_ROCK_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_ROCK_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_ROCK_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_ROCK_GENERIC"/>
	
	<event load="SURRENDER_ROCK_MISSILES"/>
</eventList>
<event name="SURRENDER_ROCK_GENERIC">
	<text load="TEXT_SURRENDER_ROCK_GENERIC"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept their surrender.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
			<autoReward level="RANDOM">stuff</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text load="GENERIC_SURRENDER_CHOICE_NOMERCY"/>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_SURRENDER_ROCK_GENERIC">
	<text>The Rock ship hails: "Enough! We were told aliens were a threat to our ways, and you have proved as much. Take this and leave us in peace."</text>
	<text>Their systems suffering, the Rock ship attempts to make contact: "Alien vessel. Cease your attack. We will pay."</text>
	<text>The Rock ship moves into a defensive position and transmits a white flag signal. They seem willing to buy their lives.</text>
</textList>
<event name="SURRENDER_ROCK_MISSILES">
	<text load="TEXT_SURRENDER_ROCK_GENERIC"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept their surrender.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
			<autoReward level="RANDOM">missiles_only</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text load="GENERIC_SURRENDER_CHOICE_NOMERCY"/>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					OUTCAST
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DESTROYED_OUTCAST">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_OUTCAST"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_OUTCAST">
	<text>Outcasts aren't quite the same threat as your ordinary pirates, but that doesn't mean they weren't a threat. Probably.</text>
	<text>Exploring the wreckage reveals various colorful murals painted on the walls of the hull. Some are quite touching, but others depict violent and brutal murder. Maybe it's a good thing these guys are dead now.</text>
	<text>As the outcasts live their final moments, you receive one last message. "At least... this is better than the coal mines..."</text>
</textList>

<event name="DEAD_CREW_OUTCAST">
	<text load="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_OUTCAST"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_OUTCAST">
	<text>Outcasts aren't quite the same threat as your ordinary pirates, but that doesn't mean they weren't a threat. Probably.</text>
	<text>Exploring the wreckage reveals various colorful murals painted on the walls of the hull. Some are quite touching, but others depict violent and brutal murder. Maybe it's a good thing these guys are dead now.</text>
	<text>As the outcasts live their final moments, you receive one last message. "At least... this is better than the coal mines..."</text>
</textList>

<eventList name="SURRENDER_OUTCAST">
	<event load="SURRENDER_OUTCAST_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_OUTCAST_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_OUTCAST_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_OUTCAST_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_OUTCAST_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_OUTCAST_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_OUTCAST_GENERIC"/>
	
	<event load="SURRENDER_OUTCAST_MISSILES"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_OUTCAST_MISSILES"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_OUTCAST_MISSILES"/>
	
	<event load="SURRENDER_OUTCAST_CREW"/>
</eventList>
<event name="SURRENDER_OUTCAST_GENERIC">
	<text load="TEXT_SURRENDER_OUTCAST_GENERIC"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept their surrender.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
			<autoReward level="RANDOM">stuff</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text load="GENERIC_SURRENDER_CHOICE_NOMERCY"/>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_SURRENDER_OUTCAST_GENERIC">
	<text>"Hah! What a riot - we were told the Federation fought to protect the galaxy from oppression. Not only have you turned your back to the Theocracy, but you've committed to annihilating our people! Prove you know mercy and let us go."</text>
	<text>"The Theocracy has told many lies - but they were telling the truth when they told us MV Travelers made dangerous foes! You win, accept this surrender and let us live!"</text>
	<text>"Our greatest mistake was to match you here - but please! Let us live on to learn from this mistake. We outcasts have only just tasted freedom, it would be a shame to die so soon."</text>
	<text>It appears the crew of the Outcast ship have hastily painted themselves white, desperately trying to convey their sudden declaration of surrender. Will you accept?</text>
</textList>
<event name="SURRENDER_OUTCAST_MISSILES">
	<text load="TEXT_SURRENDER_OUTCAST_GENERIC"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept their surrender.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
			<autoReward level="RANDOM">missiles_only</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text load="GENERIC_SURRENDER_CHOICE_NOMERCY"/>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="SURRENDER_OUTCAST_CREW">
	<text>"No more! We yield. Please, take this one. He smells awful and contributes nothing. He will be more of use on your ship than on ours."</text>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept the slave.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="rock_outcast"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text load="GENERIC_SURRENDER_CHOICE_NOMERCY"/>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					LOST SUNS
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DESTROYED_LOSTSUN">
	<text>If you continue to destroy Lost Sun ships, the shaky alliance they hold with the Federation will not last for long. At least you get some scrap out of it.</text>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>

<event name="DEAD_CREW_LOSTSUN">
	<text>If you continue to kill Lost Sun followers, the shaky alliance they hold with the Federation will not last for long. At least you get some scrap out of it.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					SLUG
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DESTROYED_SLUG">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_SLUG"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_SLUG">
	<text>For all the Slugs' efforts, they were not able to defeat you. The victor of this battle, you indulge yourself by scrapping their ship.</text>
	<text>The Slug ship is no more. You scrap the wreckage.</text>
	<text>At last, the traitorous nebula-dwellers have been silenced. You scrap the ship.</text>
</textList>

<event name="DEAD_CREW_SLUG">
	<text load="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_SLUG"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_SLUG">
    <text>You find the gasping corpse of the Slug Captain quivering on the ground. He utters one last word, "Sssshit", then collapses and dies.</text>
	<text>You feel no remorse for the Slug crew, though you do wish their ship smelled better.</text>
	<text>The interior of the ship is now coated in what appears to be a mixture of slime and mashed up Slug intestines. Yuck.</text>
</textList>

<eventList name="SURRENDER_SLUG">
	<event load="SURRENDER_SLUG_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_SLUG_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_SLUG_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_SLUG_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_SLUG_SWAP"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_SLUG_SWAP"/>
	
	<event load="SURRENDER_SLUG_BETRAY"/>
</eventList>
<event name="SURRENDER_SLUG_GENERIC">
	<text load="TEXT_SURRENDER_SLUG_GENERIC"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept their surrender.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
			<autoReward level="RANDOM">stuff</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text load="GENERIC_SURRENDER_CHOICE_NOMERCY"/>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="SURRENDER_SLUG_SWAP">
	<text load="TEXT_SURRENDER_SLUG_GENERIC"/>
	<choice>
		<text load="GENERIC_SURRENDER_CHOICE_NOMERCY"/>
		<event/>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept their surrender.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
			<autoReward level="RANDOM">stuff</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_SURRENDER_SLUG_GENERIC">
    <text>The Slug captain hails you. "Oh, your highnessss, you are ssso brave and truly the greatessst warrior to have ever lived. Will you ssspare ussssss, so that we may sssshare your tale?"</text>
	<text>"Ok, I ssssee no reassson to lie right now. We're kinda ssssscrewed unlesssss you let usss go. We'll give you sssome junk if you agree."</text>
	<text>Slugs are known for their cowardice, and as expected the Slug ship here has given up and surrendered.</text>
	<text>"Dear godsss, I did not expect thisss! I applaud you for the sssuprissse. Now let ussss go."</text>
</textList>
<event name="SURRENDER_SLUG_BETRAY">
	<text load="TEXT_SURRENDER_SLUG_GENERIC"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept their surrender.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Suddenly, just as you are about to leave, the Slug ship reactivates its weapons and fires a shot off! It doesn't get past your defenses, but the cargo crate they gave you explodes in an ion blast which partially disables your shields.</text>
			<status type="loss" target="player" system="shields" amount="2"/>
			<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text load="GENERIC_SURRENDER_CHOICE_NOMERCY"/>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					CLAN
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DESTROYED_CLAN">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_CLAN"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_CLAN">
	<text>The proud Clansmen and their ship have been destroyed. Though their many trophies have been purged along with them, at least you can salvage the scrap from their ship.</text>
	<text>The Guild probably won't appreciate you killing off their members, but what are they going to do about it? You scrap the ship.</text>
	<text>You've no doubt avenged the souls of many innocent lives who were hunted down by these Clansmen. Plus, you get some scrap out of it.</text>
	<text>While the ship explodes, you try to think of a clever bit of wordplay to describe the situation. You decide to go with "The hunters become the hunted" before you snap out of it and give orders to scrap the wreckage.</text>
</textList>

<eventList name="DEAD_CREW_CLAN">
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_CLAN_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_CLAN_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_CLAN_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_CLAN_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_CLAN_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_CLAN_GENERIC"/>
	
	<event load="DEAD_CREW_CLAN_TROPHY"/>
</eventList>
<event name="DEAD_CREW_CLAN_GENERIC">
	<text load="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_CLAN"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_CLAN">
	<text>The captain of the Slug vessel coughs as he bleeds out on the floor. He looks you in the eyes one last time, mouths the words "Damn you," and dies.</text>
	<text>You've taken out the crew of the Slug vessel. These Clansmen might make good fighters, but they didn't stand a chance against you.</text>
	<text>The Guild probably won't appreciate you killing off their members, but what are they going to do about it? You scrap the ship.</text>
	<text>You try to think of a clever bit of word play to describe the situation. You decide to go with "The hunters become the hunted" before you snap out of it and give orders to scrap the wreckage.</text>
</textList>

<event name="DEAD_CREW_CLAN_TROPHY">
	<text load="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_CLAN"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>As you inspect the interior of the vessel, you find a small trophy room containing the corpses of several alien creatures. Further inspection leads you to a prison hold, where one living prisoner remains.</text>
			<crewMember amount="1"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>


<eventList name="SURRENDER_CLAN">
	<event load="SURRENDER_CLAN_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_CLAN_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_CLAN_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_CLAN_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_CLAN_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_CLAN_GENERIC"/>
	
	<event load="SURRENDER_CLAN_BETRAY"/>
</eventList>
<event name="SURRENDER_CLAN_GENERIC">
	<text load="TEXT_SURRENDER_CLAN_GENERIC"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept their surrender.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
			<autoReward level="RANDOM">stuff</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text load="GENERIC_SURRENDER_CHOICE_NOMERCY"/>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_SURRENDER_CLAN_GENERIC">
	<text>"We will never ssssurrender!" Shouts the Clansman, right as your shot scatters across their hull. "Uhhhh, ssscratch that. How much for you to let ussss go?"</text>
	<text>It appears the Clansmen have given up. "Agggh, ssstop! Take all this sssscrap, let ussss go!"</text>
	<text>You spot an alert on your computer screen. Upon opening it, you're greeted by a video feed of the Clansmen waving literal white flags towards the camera.</text>
</textList>
<event name="SURRENDER_CLAN_BETRAY">
	<text load="TEXT_SURRENDER_CLAN_GENERIC"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept their surrender.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Suddenly, just as you are about to leave, the Slug ship reactivates its weapons and fires a shot off! It doesn't get past your defenses, but the cargo crate they gave you explodes in an ion blast which partially disables your shields.</text>
			<status type="loss" target="player" system="shields" amount="2"/>
			<autoReward level="MED">stuff</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text load="GENERIC_SURRENDER_CHOICE_NOMERCY"/>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					HEKTAR
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DESTROYED_HEKTAR">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_HEKTAR"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_HEKTAR">
	<text>As the Hektar ship breaks apart, you can't help but wonder if their ships were designed to be as easy to put together as their weapons.</text>
	<text>The Hektar ship explodes, and an automatic message is sent out to your ship. "Hektar Industries applauds you for your success in combat. Before you can scrap our ship however, we request you watch this short ad..."</text>
	<text>A plethora of boxes come flying out of the cargo bay of the other ship. You consider grabbing some, but the pictures on the side suggest they aren't worth your time. What is two circles and an oval even supposed to mean?</text>
	<text>You receive one last hail from the Hektar Captain as his ship is plunged into flames. "I wasssn't paid enough to sssay sssomething clever. But if my manager assksss, pretend I did-"</text>
</textList>

<event name="DEAD_CREW_HEKTAR">
	<text load="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_HEKTAR"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_HEKTAR">
    <text>"God... damn... it... I didn't even get thisss week'sss pay check yet..."</text>
	<text>In his final moments, the Slug captain shrugs. "Better then having to go back to the call ccccenter I guesssss."</text>
	<text>"Gaahhhh, sssso much for that healthcare..." The Slug slumps over dead and you scrap his ship.</text>
	<text>As you walk amongst the corpses of the Slugs, you catch the final words of one last survivor; "Bury me with my money..." Unfortunately for him, you have other plans on what to do with his money.</text>
</textList>

<eventList name="SURRENDER_HEKTAR">
	<event load="SURRENDER_HEKTAR_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_HEKTAR_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_HEKTAR_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_HEKTAR_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_HEKTAR_SWAP"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_HEKTAR_SWAP"/>
</eventList>
<event name="SURRENDER_HEKTAR_GENERIC">
	<text load="TEXT_SURRENDER_HEKTAR_GENERIC"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept their surrender.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
			<autoReward level="RANDOM">stuff</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text load="GENERIC_SURRENDER_CHOICE_NOMERCY"/>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="SURRENDER_HEKTAR_SWAP">
	<text load="TEXT_SURRENDER_HEKTAR_GENERIC"/>
	<choice>
		<text load="GENERIC_SURRENDER_CHOICE_NOMERCY"/>
		<event/>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept their surrender.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
			<autoReward level="RANDOM">stuff</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_SURRENDER_HEKTAR_GENERIC">
    <text>"You know what? Thissss job wassssn't worth it anywayssss. I am formally resssigning. You wouldn't kill an innocent unemployed civilian now, would you?"</text>
	<text>"Capitalissssm hasss failed me! I ssshall forever now be communissst. Bribery and communisssm are sssynonymousss, right?"</text>
	<text>"Who'sss paying you for thisss? I refusssse to believe you aren't in thisss for money. Well guesss what! I have money too!"</text>
	<text>The Hektar employee frantically flips through his employee manual. "Crap, it doesssn't sssay anything about what to do here! Uh, time to resssort to plan B. Buy my way out!"</text>
</textList>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					LEECH
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DESTROYED_LEECH">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_LEECH"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_LEECH">
	<text>You know space has no sound, but you can almost swear you heard the jubilant cries of relief from the Leech ship's crew as they're blown to smitherenes.</text>
	<text>Moments before the Leech ship is destroyed, the ship almost seems to halt, as if in the final moments they realized their failure and gave up in an instant. That depressing realization won't stop you from scrapping their ship however.</text>
	<text>If the legends of the once great Leech military were ever true, they certainly don't hold up today. For your sake, let's hope they never make a resurgence.</text>
	<text>If you keep killing Leech ships, maybe they'll give up and leave you alone for good. It's probably too much to hope for, but it's not impossible either.</text>
</textList>

<event name="DEAD_CREW_LEECH">
	<text load="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_LEECH"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_LEECH">
    <text>The scene left from the massacre here is far from a pretty one. The diced up bits of Leech flesh let off a repugnant odor so foul you almost consider leaving the wreck behind entirely. Almost.</text>
	<text>You've heard the disturbing stories of the haunting post-mortem smiles of Leech crew. Now, you're experiencing them yourself. This'll probably take some amount of therapy to get over.</text>
	<text>Expecting the ship to be empty, you step aboard, only to see that one of the Leech crew is still alive! However, instead of fighting back, the Leech only curls up into a ball and bites hard into his own body, killing himself instantly. How morbid.</text>
	<text>Walking among the corpses of these parasites is nothing short of eerie. Their wide gaping mouths seem as if they could reach out at any moment and strike you. You keep your hand near your blaster at all times as you scrap the ship.</text>
	<text>Apparently, shortly after death, the corpse of a Leech will drain itself slowly of all the built up electricity it has stored over its life. With this many bodies, it could be catastrophic in close quarters. You make sure to hurry and scrap the ship before you can get caught in a mine field of electrified bodies.</text>
</textList>

<eventList name="SURRENDER_LEECH">
	<event load="SURRENDER_LEECH_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_LEECH_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_LEECH_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_LEECH_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_LEECH_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="SURRENDER_LEECH_GENERIC"/>
	
	<event load="SURRENDER_LEECH_GIVEUP"/>
</eventList>
<event name="SURRENDER_LEECH_GENERIC">
	<text load="TEXT_SURRENDER_LEECH_GENERIC"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept their surrender.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
			<autoReward level="RANDOM">stuff</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text load="GENERIC_SURRENDER_CHOICE_NOMERCY"/>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_SURRENDER_LEECH_GENERIC">
    <text>"Oooh, woe is me. The end of days is upon us! Why do we even try..." The Leech ship hopes you'll take pity on them.</text>
	<text>The Leech captain regurgitates several mounds of white cloth. You're disgusted and confused for a few moments until you realize this is a convoluted attempt to "raise the white flag".</text>
	<text>You aren't surprised the Leech captain appears to have given up so easily. They aren't exactly known for their loyalty or commitment. The question is, will you spare them?</text>
	<text>The Leech captain burps loudly, specks of bile landing on their camera. Repulsive, but according to your captain's handbook this is one of the many ways the Leeches will offer their surrender to enemy captains.</text>
	<text>"We will never surrender! Eargen forever- aaaaactually, nevermind. We surrender. I don't want to die."</text>
	<text>The enemy's captain appears to be waving frantically with his tongue "hands". Looks like he's trying to get your attention to surrender.</text>
</textList>
<event name="SURRENDER_LEECH_GIVEUP">
	<text>From out of nowhere, the Leech ship simply powers off its weapons and shields. They aren't out of the fight yet, but it seems as though... they want you to kill them?</text>
	<status type="limit" target="enemy" system="shields" amount="0"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Spare them and stop firing.</text>
		<event load="SURRENDER_LEECH_GIVEUP_SPARE"/>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Fulfill their wish and end this fight.</text>
		<event>
			<status type="limit" target="enemy" system="weapons" amount="0"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="SURRENDER_LEECH_GIVEUP_SPARE">
	<event>
		<text>The Leech ship slinks away like a wounded animal without another word.</text>
		<ship hostile="false"/>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>The Leeches seem surprised but grateful and timmidly offer a bit of their cargo.</text>
		<autoReward level="LOW">standard</autoReward>
		<ship hostile="false"/>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>Looks like the Leeches won't be spared that easily. They continue to press on, even reactivating their weapons just to keep you in the fight.</text>
		<ship hostile="true"/>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>The Leeches are surprised but grateful. One wounded soldier offers himself up to work aboard your ship, likely as an escape from his services to the Republic.</text>
		<crewMember amount="1" class="leech"/>
		<ship hostile="false"/>
	</event>
</eventList>

<event name="ESCAPE_LEECH">
	<text>It appears the Leech ship has reconsidered staying around to finish this fight. They're trying to escape!</text>
</event>

<eventList name="GOTAWAY_LEECH">
	<event load="GOTAWAY_LEECH_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="GOTAWAY_LEECH_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="GOTAWAY_LEECH_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="GOTAWAY_LEECH_GENERIC"/>
	
	<event load="GOTAWAY_LEECH_REMAINS"/>
</eventList>
<event name="GOTAWAY_LEECH_GENERIC">
	<text>The Leech ship jumps away, leaving you behind at the beacon.</text>
</event>
<event name="GOTAWAY_LEECH_REMAINS">
	<text>The Leech ship jumps away. At first you're disappointed, but then you realise a portion of scrap matter has been left behind from the fight. It's not much, but it helps soften the blow of your failure.</text>
	<autoReward level="LOW">scrap_only</autoReward>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					SHELL
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DESTROYED_SHELL">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_SHELL"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_SHELL">
	<text>The Shell ship explodes, sending clouds of poisonous gas out into space. Hopefully there are no stations with open airlocks nearby...</text>
	<text>Despite all their defensive measures, the Shell ship has been defeated. You scrap the remains.</text>
	<text>The Shells are known for their well-maintained defenses, but your weaponry has proven effective once again.</text>
</textList>

<event name="DEAD_CREW_SHELL">
	<text load="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_SHELL"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_SHELL">
	<text>Fighting Shells is dangerous considering how well protected they are, but you've cleared the ship of crew. Their scrap is yours.</text>
	<text>The Shell ship has been neutralized. You scrap the ship.</text>
</textList>

<event name="SURRENDER_SHELL">
	<text load="TEXT_SURRENDER_SHELL"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept their surrender.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
			<autoReward level="RANDOM">stuff</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text load="GENERIC_SURRENDER_CHOICE_NOMERCY"/>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_SURRENDER_SHELL">
	<text>"Please, you are too strong! We do not want to fight! Let us live!"</text>
	<text>Unlike their Slug cousins, Shells aren't very greedy. They'd much rather pay some scrap instead of dying. Will you accept their offer?</text>
	<text>You receive a hail from the Shell captain. "Yes yes, your guns are very good. Let us go, we have scrap!"</text>
</textList>

<event name="ESCAPE_SHELL">
	<text>It appears the Shell ship has reconsidered staying around to finish this fight. They're trying to escape!</text>
</event>

<eventList name="GOTAWAY_SHELL">
	<event load="GOTAWAY_SHELL_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="GOTAWAY_SHELL_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="GOTAWAY_SHELL_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="GOTAWAY_SHELL_GENERIC"/>
	
	<event load="GOTAWAY_SHELL_REMAINS"/>
</eventList>
<event name="GOTAWAY_SHELL_GENERIC">
	<text>The Shell ship jumps away, leaving you behind at the beacon.</text>
</event>
<event name="GOTAWAY_SHELL_REMAINS">
	<text>The Shell ship jumps away. At first you're disappointed, but then you realise a portion of scrap matter has been left behind from the fight. It's not much, but it helps soften the blow of your failure.</text>
	<autoReward level="LOW">scrap_only</autoReward>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					MORPH
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<eventList name="DESTROYED_MORPH">
	<event load="DESTROYED_MORPH_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_MORPH_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_MORPH_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_MORPH_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_MORPH_GENERIC"/>
	
	<event load="DESTROYED_MORPH_EXTRA"/>
</eventList>

<event name="DESTROYED_MORPH_GENERIC">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_MORPH"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_MORPH">
	<text>The grey vessel is engulfed in an orange glow, its bland hull going up in flames that are quickly extinguished by the vacuum of space.</text>
	<text>The likely fact you just blew up, not only a crew of many Morphs, but one massive Morph as well is a weird one to grasp. You wonder if the scrap metal from the wreckage will Morph back into enemies, or stay lifeless.</text>
	<text>You wonder if the Morphs felt pain as their ship just imploded. You hope not, but only because you can never be sure if these things are really dead, and you'd hate for them to come back to haunt you later.</text>
	<text>Another mysterious ship full of Morphs down. You salvage the wreckage.</text>
</textList>

<event name="DESTROYED_MORPH_EXTRA">
	<text>You scrap the wreck of the Morph ship, but notice a bit of debris floating nearby.</text>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">	
		<text>Collect the salvage.</text>
		<event load="DESTROYED_MORPH_EXTRA_SALVAGE"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">	
		<text>Ignore it.</text>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="DESTROYED_MORPH_EXTRA_SALVAGE">
	<event>
		<text>Looks like the salvage was as you expected. You scoop it up and bring it aboard the ship.</text>
		<autoReward level="LOW">standard</autoReward>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>Your crew bring aboard the salvage, noting how light it is. Once aboard, the scrap suddenly changes shape, turning into a band of angry Morphs who attack!</text>
		<boarders min="3" max="4" class="blob"/>
	</event>
</eventList>

<event name="DEAD_CREW_MORPH">
	<text load="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_MORPH"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_MORPH">
	<text>The gibberish spewing blobs have been brought to an untimely end. You scrap their ship.</text>
	<text>The concept that your crew are now standing inside a giant Morph itself while scrapping the ship is somewhat unsettling, but you bury your concerns and order your crew to hurry up.</text>
	<text>The grey stains of once sentient goop mark the walls of the ship, scattered about during the fight. You can only hope they won't animate once again and attack you while salvaging.</text>
	<text>As you scrap the Morph ship, you wonder if those strange gray blobs can feel pain, and if their final moments were in agony. Honestly, you still aren't sure if they're sapient.</text>
</textList>

<event name="SURRENDER_MORPH">
	<text load="TEXT_SURRENDER_MORPH"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Accept their "surrender".</text>
		<event load="SURRENDER_MORPH_ACCEPT"/>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text load="GENERIC_SURRENDER_CHOICE_NOMERCY"/>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_SURRENDER_MORPH">
	<text>"Kip kip joo! Urg la yoo purl yu!" You think the Morphs are surrendering, but you aren't sure. How do you respond?</text>
	<text>"Oj joo! Oj joo! Yur kip looloo!" You think the Morphs are surrendering, but you aren't sure. How do you respond?</text>
	<text>"Odle yup. Kim jio kup kurp!" You think the Morphs are surrendering, but you aren't sure. How do you respond?</text>
</textList>
<eventList name="SURRENDER_MORPH_ACCEPT">
	<event>
		<text>You disarm the weapons, hoping the Morphs will do the same. They do in fact turn their weapons offline as well, though whether they're doing that because you understood correctly or they think you're surrendering instead is up to debate. Not long after, a small Morph finds its way onto the ship, but they seem friendly and want to stay.</text>
		<crewMember amount="1" class="blob"/>
		<ship hostile="false"/>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>You disarm the weapons, hoping the Morphs will do the same. Instead, a group of angry blobs bust their way into your ship and the fight continues!</text>
		<boarders min="2" max="3" class="blob"/>
	</event>
</eventList>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					COALITION
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DESTROYED_COALITION">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_COALITION"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_COALITION">
	<text>The Coalition ship explodes. As the separate pieces float away, you can once again see the divide between the factions. You like it better this way.</text>
	<text>The Coalition doesn't mess around, but yet again you've come out on top. The remains of their ship are yours to scrap.</text>
	<text>You've proven that no one, Rebel or Coalition, can outmatch you. Or at least, this ship couldn't.</text>
</textList>

<event name="DEAD_CREW_COALITION">
	<text load="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_COALITION"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_COALITION">
	<text>A mixture of all different kinds of alien blood is on your hands. No wonder they must all hate the Federation.</text>
	<text>The Coalition is made of some of the most fearsome warrior races, but your crew has proven themselves superior.</text>
</textList>

<event name="SURRENDER_COALITION">
	<text load="TEXT_SURRENDER_COALITION"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept their surrender.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
			<autoReward level="RANDOM">stuff</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text load="GENERIC_SURRENDER_CHOICE_NOMERCY"/>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_SURRENDER_COALITION">
	<text>The captain of the Coalition ship hails you, and begrudgingly requests that you accept their surrender.</text>
	<text>You can tell it's hard for the Coalition captain to admit, but they have been bested. They offer a surrender.</text>
</textList>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					GHOST
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DESTROYED_GHOST">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_GHOST"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">stuff</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_GHOST">
	<text>It is hard to draw the line between the original damage and the destruction you have caused. You add to the damage even further by scrapping the ship.</text>
	<text>The Ghost ship is no more. You scrap what you can.</text>
	<text>The circle of life for this ship has been complete. Now finally destroyed, as it should have been originally, you scrap what remains.</text>
</textList>

<event name="DEAD_CREW_GHOST">
	<text load="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_GHOST"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">stuff</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_GHOST">
	<text>You have emptied the ship of its ghostly captors. No longer shall they prey on innocent ships passing through this sector.</text>
	<text>It dawns on you that twice now the entire crew of this ship has been exterminated. The thought chills you as you scrap it.</text>
	<text>Now empty of crew, you make sure to thoroughly scrap the ruins so that no more Ghosts can ever inhabit this ship.</text>
</textList>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					DYNASTY
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DESTROYED_DYNASTY">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_DYNASTY"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_DYNASTY">
    <text>The Dynasty's architects probably cringe every time they catch news another one of their ships have been destroyed. Their fleets have been reduced ever since the great cataclysm of their past, and you certainly aren't helping.</text>
    <text>The vibrant blue lights on the Dynasty vessel flicker in their final moments before the brilliant blue glow ceases and the integrity of the ship's hull crumbles.</text>
    <text>If every Federation ship killed Dynasty vessels with the same level of efficiency as you, it would be no wonder that they hate you all! However, from your experience, it doesn't seem there are many competent captains out there to explain the phenomenon.</text>
    <text>You catch a glimpse of glittering wisps of color floating out of the hull as it collapses. Have the Ghosts escaped their horrible fate, or is this merely the equivalent of a corpse being flung out into the cosmos? You really aren't sure.</text>
</textList>

<event name="DEAD_CREW_DYNASTY">
	<text load="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_DYNASTY"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_DYNASTY">
	<text>You've heard that the Ghosts have a most horrible odour to them, and you couldn't be more glad there's no air inside the Dynasty ship to carry the scent as you scrap it.</text>
	<text>You wonder if Ghosts feel pain before they die. After what just happened here, you sincerely hope they don't.</text>
	<text>"Arg, see to it that you are penetrated up the rectum, you foul wretch," mutters the Ghost captain as he begins to dissipate.</text>
	<text>You remember a time on your MV Traveler handbook that said it was best to avoid crew killing Ghosts whenever you can. But look at you now! If only the people back at training could see the havoc you caused.</text>
</textList>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					LANIUS
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<eventList name="DESTROYED_LANIUS">
	<event load="DESTROYED_LANIUS_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_LANIUS_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_LANIUS_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_LANIUS_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_LANIUS_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_LANIUS_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_LANIUS_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_LANIUS_GENERIC"/>
	
	<event load="DESTROYED_LANIUS_BOARDER"/>
</eventList>
<event name="DESTROYED_LANIUS_GENERIC">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_LANIUS"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_LANIUS">
	<text>One can never be too cautious while scrapping a Lanius ship, for fear of either a lone survivor drifting in the vacuum or a collision with the sharp debris.</text>
	<text>The destruction of the Lanius vessel provides you with great satisfaction, knowing how infamously difficult the Lanius are as foes.</text>
	<text>The Lanius may be excellent scavengers, but today you've turned the tables on them.</text>
</textList>
<event name="DESTROYED_LANIUS_BOARDER">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_LANIUS"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>It seems the destruction of the Lanius ship was not enough to kill off all of its crew. A single Lanius managed to escape the inferno and has now attached itself to the ship!</text>
			<boarders min="1" max="1" class="lanius"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DEAD_CREW_LANIUS">
	<text load="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_LANIUS"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_LANIUS">
	<text>It's difficult to scrap the oxygenless interiors of the Lanius ship, but you can manage. Nothing will keep you from your precious scrap, not even the cruel vacuum of space.</text>
	<text>Without crew on-board to disturb you, you can truly appreciate the intricacies of Lanius architecture. Sure, it looks like a bunch of kitchen knives duct-taped together, but anything can be art with the right attitude.</text>
	<text>With the crew of the Lanius ship dead, nothing prevents you from tearing apart the hull of their ship.</text>
</textList>

<event name="SURRENDER_LANIUS">
	<text load="TEXT_SURRENDER_LANIUS"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Accept their offer.</text>
		<event>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
			<autoReward level="RANDOM">stuff</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text load="GENERIC_SURRENDER_CHOICE_NOMERCY"/>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_SURRENDER_LANIUS">
	<text>An image of a silent Lanius captain appears on your monitor. Images of their well-filled cargo hold follow. You come to the conclusion that they are trying to barter for a cease-fire.</text>
	<text>The Lanius ship hails you. Your translator struggles, spurting out "Prevent death... Merciful... Penitent...". You believe they are surrendering.</text>
	<text>You receive a hail from the ship followed by a crude translation device spurting, "Stop. Stop. Stop."</text>
	<text>You receive an image of their captain, silhouetted by the destruction aboard their ship. It bows forward with the metallic appendages about its body doing the same. It appears to be requesting mercy.</text>
	<text>Your comms system receives a video feed of the enemy ship's crew waving small makeshift white flags. It appears they have taken research about your culture's customs quite literally.</text>
	<text>You receive a message from the enemy ship that your translator struggles to interpret, "Penitence for metal. Offering intention."</text>
	<text>You receive a one word message from the enemy ship, "Surrender." You assume they are asking to surrender rather than demanding your surrender.</text>
</textList>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					SIRENS
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DESTROYED_SIREN_UNKNOWN">
    <text>The mysterious vessel is destroyed. You scrap its smooth white hull while the rainbow lights continue to flicker in and out of life.</text>
    <autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>

<event name="DEADCREW_SIREN_UNKNOWN">
    <text>The crew of the mysterious vessel is dead. You scrap its smooth white hull while the rainbow lights continue to flicker in and out of life.</text>
    <autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
    <choice hidden="true">
        <text>Continue...</text>
        <event>
            <text>To your surprise, you find another person stuffed into the storage of the alien ship. They appear to be under some strange trance that has now begun to slowly wear off. Once they're safe, they agree to join your crew.</text>
            <crewMember amount="1"/>
        </event>
    </choice>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					AUGMENTED
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<eventList name="DESTROYED_AUGMENTED">
	<event load="DESTROYED_AUGMENTED_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_AUGMENTED_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_AUGMENTED_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_AUGMENTED_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_AUGMENTED_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_AUGMENTED_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_AUGMENTED_GENERIC"/>
	<event load="DESTROYED_AUGMENTED_GENERIC"/>
	
	<event load="DESTROYED_AUGMENTED_BOARDER"/>
</eventList>
<event name="DESTROYED_AUGMENTED_GENERIC">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_AUGMENTED"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_AUGMENTED">
	<text>One can never be too cautious while scrapping a Lanius ship, for fear of either a lone survivor drifting in the vacuum or a collision with the sharp debris.</text>
	<text>The destruction of the Lanius vessel provides you with great satisfaction, knowing how infamously difficult the Lanius are as foes.</text>
	<text>The Lanius may be excellent scavengers, but today you've turned the tables on them.</text>
</textList>
<event name="DESTROYED_AUGMENTED_BOARDER">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_AUGMENTED"/>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>It seems the destruction of the Lanius ship was not enough to kill off all of its crew. A single Lanius managed to escape the inferno and has now attached itself to the ship!</text>
			<boarders min="1" max="1" class="lanius_augmented"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DEAD_CREW_AUGMENTED">
	<text load="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_AUGMENTED"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">item</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_AUGMENTED">
	<text>It's difficult to scrap the oxygenless interiors of the Lanius ship, but you can manage. Nothing will keep you from your precious scrap, not even the cruel vacuum of space.</text>
	<text>Without crew on-board to disturb you, you can truly appreciate the intricacies of Lanius architecture. Sure, it looks like a bunch of kitchen knives duct-taped together, but anything can be art with the right attitude.</text>
	<text>With the crew of the Lanius ship dead, nothing prevents you from tearing apart the hull of their ship.</text>
</textList>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					ANCIENT
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DESTROYED_ANCIENT">
	<text load="TEXT_DESTROYED_ANCIENT"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DESTROYED_ANCIENT">
	<text>You have rid the galaxy of another Obelisk ship. There's bound to be hundreds more, but it's something.</text>
	<text>The Obelisk ship explodes into many smaller pieces, its cubical shape shattered forever. It's oddly satisfying, and you reflect fondly on your handiwork as you scrap the remains.</text>
	<text>Though you know the Obelisks are the antagonists of this galaxy, you can't help but wonder if every ship you kill was aware of their grand scheme.</text>
	<text>With every Obelisk ship you destroy, you delay the date of the invasion just a little bit more. You know it's not much, but it feels important to you.</text>
</textList>

<event name="DEAD_CREW_ANCIENT">
	<text load="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_ANCIENT"/>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_DEAD_CREW_ANCIENT">
	<text>As the last Obelisk collapses, it lets out two last words. "Screw... you..."</text>
	<text>You've made quick work of these cubical aliens. You don't feel the pang of guilt that usually accompanies these murders. For the most part.</text>
	<text>The interior of the Obelisk ship is littered with the dust of the fallen crew. You call it a job well done and give the orders to scrap the ship.</text>
	<text>The death of the Obelisk ship and its crew means good news for the rest of the galaxy. You just hope they don't have any families to grieve them.</text>
</textList>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					ELITE DEFEAT EVENTS 
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					REBEL
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DEFEAT_REBEL_ELITE">
	<text>You've defeated the Rebel Elite, which is no easy task. It's not enough to impact the fleet, but it's still a great victory.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>It seems the cargo of the Elite Rebel ship survived the fight. Inside is a functional weapon, which you bring back on board.</text>
			<weapon name="GIFTLIST_REBEL"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					TECHNICIAN
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DEFEAT_ENGINEER_ELITE">
	<text>You've defeated a technician vessel, impressive. Though they may simply be menial workers in the eyes of Wentworth Innovations, their ships are considerably well armed, and successfully defeating one in combat is no small feat.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>It seems the cargo of the Technician ship survived the fight. Inside is a functional weapon, which you bring back on board.</text>
			<weapon name="GIFTLIST_REBEL"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					FEDERATION
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DEFEAT_FED_ELITE">
	<text>Eliminating allied Federation personnel, especially Elite ones, is highly contrary to your mission, but that doesn't mean you're beyond salvaging the remains.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>It seems the cargo of the Elite Federation ship survived the fight. Inside is a functional weapon, which you bring back on board.</text>
			<weapon name="GIFTLIST_FEDERATION"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					ENGI
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DEFEAT_ENGI_ELITE">
	<text>With the death of the Engi Defenders there are now fewer ships to protect the Harmony from true threats, but you can't run away from every fight. You salvage the remains of the ship.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>It seems the cargo of the Elite Engi ship survived the fight. Inside is a functional drone, which you bring back on board.</text>
			<drone name="GIFTLIST_ENGI"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					ZOLTAN
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DEFEAT_ZOLTAN_ELITE">
	<text>So much for peacekeeping. The Ministry struggles to keep its peacekeeper task force up to par with all of the disorder in the Multiverse, and this certainly won't help that.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>It seems the cargo of the Elite Zoltan ship survived the fight. Inside is a functional weapon, which you bring back on board.</text>
			<weapon name="GIFTLIST_ZOLTAN"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					MILITIA
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DEFEAT_MILITIA_ELITE">
	<text>The EDC is one of the few forces capable of defending civilian sectors, and they aren't exactly common. The loss of this ship will certainly have negative results on the Militia.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>It seems the cargo of the Elite Militia ship survived the fight. Inside is a functional weapon, which you bring back on board.</text>
			<weapon name="GIFTLIST_CIVILIAN"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					ORCHID
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DEFEAT_ORCHID_ELITE">
    <text>You've managed to take down a powerful Orchid Chieftain and their ship, and now the remains are yours to scrap.</text>
    <autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
    <choice hidden="true">
        <text>Continue...</text>
        <event>
            <text>It seems the cargo of the Elite Orchid ship survived the fight. Inside is a functional weapon, which you bring back on board.</text>
            <weapon name="GIFTLIST_KERNEL_ELITE"/>
        </event>
    </choice>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					CRYSTAL
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DEFEAT_CRYSTAL_ELITE">
    <text>The bright red shards of the Sentinel vessel fly off into the abyss as the mighty elite vessel comes to a halt.</text>
    <autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
    <choice hidden="true">
        <text>Continue...</text>
        <event>
            <text>It seems the cargo of the Elite Crystal ship survived the fight. Inside is a functional weapon, which you bring back on board.</text>
            <weapon name="GIFTLIST_CRYSTAL_ELITE"/>
        </event>
    </choice>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					ROCK
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DEFEAT_ROCK_ELITE">
    <text>The Inquisition was once one of the most feared forces in the entire galaxy, but they've fallen from glory. This victory only adds insult to injury.</text>
    <autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
    <choice hidden="true">
        <text>Continue...</text>
        <event>
            <text>It seems the cargo of the Elite Rock ship survived the fight. Inside is a functional weapon, which you bring back on board.</text>
            <weapon name="GIFTLIST_ROCK"/>
        </event>
    </choice>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					FREE MANTIS
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DESTROY_FREEMAN_ELITE">
	<text>The Warlord ship has been destroyed. You scrap what is left over from the wreckage.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
</event>

<event name="DEADCREW_FREEMAN_ELITE">
	<text>The Warlord ship has been neutralized. You scrap what is left over from the ship.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>It appears one of the Warlords managed to survive the conflict, though injured. It seems they're healthy enough to shamble out of their hiding spot to meet you. "Oh noble Federation, you are glorious fighter! Bring me mercy, and allow me to serve you!"</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="mantis_warlord"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					SUZERAIN
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DEFEAT_SUZERAIN_ELITE">
    <text>You've managed to take down a powerful Hive Elite and their ship, and now the remains are yours to scrap.</text>
    <autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
    <choice hidden="true">
        <text>Continue...</text>
        <event>
            <text>It seems the cargo of the Mantis Elite ship survived the fight. Inside is a functional weapon, which you bring back on board.</text>
            <weapon name="GIFTLIST_MANTIS"/>
        </event>
    </choice>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					DUSKBRINGER
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DEFEAT_DUSK_ELITE">
	<text>Today you've shown the Duskbringers you don't mess around. No vessel, not even the most extreme, can defeat you.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>It seems the cargo of the Duskbringer ship survived the fight. Inside is a functional weapon, which you bring back on board.</text>
			<weapon name="GIFTLIST_DUSK"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					SLUG
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DEFEAT_SLUG_ELITE">
	<text>If the original Clairvoyants of centuries ago could see their descendants now, falling to a ship like yours, they'd weep. Which, frankly, you don't mind.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>It seems the cargo of the Elite Slug ship survived the fight. Inside is a functional weapon, which you bring back on board.</text>
			<weapon name="GIFTLIST_SLUG"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					SHELL
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DEFEAT_SHELL_ELITE">
	<text>A Radiant vessel has fallen to your ship. It might make Shell space less safe in the long run, but for now it means you'll live to see another day.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>It seems the cargo of the Elite Shell ship survived the fight. Inside is an Anti-Hull weapon, which you bring back on board.</text>
			<weapon name="GIFTLIST_SHELL"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					AMPERE
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DEFEAT_LEECH_ELITE">
	<text>The Amperes are trained explicitely by the Coalition itself, and are far deadlier than normal Leeches. By killing this ship, you've probably crippled a good percentage of the Republic's only able soldiers.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>It seems the cargo of the Leech ship survived the fight. Inside is a functional weapon, which you bring back on board.</text>
			<weapon name="GIFTLIST_LEECH"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					COALITION
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DEFEAT_COALITION_ELITE">
    <text>As you watch the Coalition vessel break apart, you reflect on what a stupid acronym "R.U.E.S." is. Like seriously, who even came up with that?</text>
    <autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
    <choice hidden="true">
        <text>Continue...</text>
        <event>
            <text>It seems the cargo of the Elite Coalition ship survived the fight. Inside is a functional weapon, which you bring back on board.</text>
            <weapon name="GIFTLIST_COALITION"/>
        </event>
    </choice>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					LANIUS
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DEFEAT_LANIUS_ELITE">
	<text>The defeat of the Lanius Elites is nothing to scoff at, and neither is the amount of salvage left behind.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>It seems the cargo of the Lanius ship survived the fight. Inside is a Flak cannon, which you bring back on board.</text>
			<weapon name="GIFTLIST_LANIUS"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					DYNASTY
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<event name="DEFEAT_DYNASTY_ELITE">
	<text>Reaper ships are no idle threat, but the Dynasty should know better than to throw punches at you.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>It seems the cargo of the Dynasty ship survived the fight. Inside is a functional weapon, which you bring back on board.</text>
			<weapon name="GIFTLIST_DYNASTY"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
</FTL>