<FTL>

<event name="TEST_HEKTAR_STORE">
	<text>Demo Store.</text>
	<store>STORE_HEKTAR_DEMO</store>
</event>
<event name="HEKTAR_VIRTUAL_STORE">
	<store>STORE_HEKTAR_VIRTUAL</store>
</event>

<event name="HEKTAR_HEADQUARTERS">
	<preventQuest/>
	<text>This distress beacon has landed you somewhere unexpected - a lush terraformed paradise, housing in its center a vast ring shaped building which is home to none other than Hektar HQ. Strangely, the distress beacon is broadcasting only on a few specific frequencies, one of which is a more secretive Federation channel.</text>
	<img back="BACK_EVENT_HEKTARHQ" planet="NONE"/>
	<distressBeacon/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Investigate.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You land on the HQ landing pad, surprised to find no intervention from any kind of security. As you approach the building however, you're stopped by a rather dangerous looking security system, which refuses you entry.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Attempt to gain access.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Your attempt at entry is met by alarms, which activate security turrets that fire upon your ship! Fortunately, you're able to shut them down and gain access afterwards, but your ship has taken a beating.</text>
					<damage amount="5"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="BILLY"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_VARIANT_HEKTAR">
				<text>(Hektar Employee) Attempt to gain access.</text>
				<event load="BILLY"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="hacking" lvl="2">
				<text>(Upg. Hacking) Attempt to gain access.</text>
				<event load="BILLY"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="BLUELIST_CREW_NODOORS">
				<text>(Phasing Crew) Attempt to gain access.</text>
				<event load="BILLY"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="unique_metyunt">
				<text>(Metyunt) Attempt to gain access.</text>
				<event load="BILLY"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Give up.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Let this one go - could be a trap.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Very strange for such a signal to be so far out here. It has to be a trap, there's no other explanation, right? You prepare to leave.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Check the storage.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="BILLY">
	<text>Looks like your attempt to enter was successful. You carry on throughout the building, but it's clear things aren't too good in here. Faint blood stains decorate the walls, mostly the bright green sludge known to spill out of dead Slugs. It's weeks old though, a forboding omen of the state of what you might find deeper inside.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>At last, you come across an open office door. Stepping inside, you find a blue Slug slumped over a desk, silently sobbing to himself. He perks up when he sees you, and his demeanor quickly changes between shock, terror, anger, and finally defeat. "Sssso, you've finally come to kill me? I knew the deadline would arrive... Well, you have me now. I give up. Jusssst kill me."</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Who are you? And who is trying to kill you?</text>
				<event>
					<text>The Slug seems to realize you aren't who he expected. "Wait - you aren't Taurussss! I'm SSSSAVED! SSSSAVED! Hahah! I am Billy Hektar, CCCCEO of Hektar and Great Grand-child to Carle Hektar, founder of Hektar Industriesss! I knew that sssignal would reach sssomeone eventually! Unfortunately, I've been trapped in my officccce for monthssss, forccced to run thisss company like a crime ring rather than a bussssinessss..."</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>You trapped yourself in your office?</text>
						<event>
							<text>"What? No, you dumbassss. Hektar hasss alwaysss been the underdog, but when I inherited the company along with my brother, we hoped to make thissss company really sssshine! And then Zulfiqar came along and completely monopolized the entire weapon indussstry. I tried to sssave the company, but my brother didn't appreccciate my methodssss. Sssso what if I enssslaved a ssspecies of primitive lizardssss?!"</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>I don't see how that led to you being trapped in an office.</text>
								<event>
									<text>"I'm getting there, relax! After he left the company... okay well, I kind of forccced him out. But that'ssss not the point! Thingssss went downhill. I couldn't keep my invessstorsss paid. One by one, they left. Sssoon, only sssome grease ssstain named Tony Senior and that bassstard Vael wasss left. That handsssome ssson of a bitch... er, I mean, that sssson of a bitch."</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Wait- Do you mean THE Vael? Leader of the Syndicate?!</text>
										<event>
											<text>"The one in charge of all mercccenariessss in the galaxy? Yeah that one. Oh, and by the way. Might be important to mention that by entering thissss faccility, you've set off an alarm, and now he'ssss probably going to send an assssassssin to come and kill usss both. Fair warning, and all that."</text>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>Get the hell out of here!</text>
												<event>
													<text>As you're hurrying out of the office, you stop to notice a second ship has landed on next to yours. A massive Stealth like vessel, and next to it is a human, dressed in a painted MFK uniform. "A nice ship you got there, partner. Now, hand over the Slug and no one gets hurt."</text>
													<ship load="SHIP_TAURUS" hostile="false"/>
													<choice hidden="true">
														<text>Who the hell are you?</text>
														<event>
															<text>The man pauses as if contemplating how to respond. "Name's Taurus. One of Vael's 'enforcers'. Folks like you call us the Angels o' Death. Ain't that fitting?" He turns his attention to Billy. "Now now Billster, your time is up. Vael's tired of your malarkey. You oughta know by now when you mess with men like him, you better keep your promises." He turns back to you. "Now, last time I'm gonna ask. Hand over the Slug, and we can all walk away like nothing happened."</text>
															<choice hidden="true">
																<text>Refuse.</text>
																<event>
																	<text>"Ain't that sweet. I was hoping you'd refuse. You've got one sweet bounty on your skull and I'd love to cash you in." Taurus smiles menacingly then dashes back to his ship, whose engines have already powered up. This is going to be a rough one.</text>
																	<crewMember amount="1" class="unique_billy" all_skills="2">Billy</crewMember>
																	<ship hostile="true"/>
																	<choice hidden="true">
																		<text>Continue...</text>
																		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
																	</choice>
																</event>
															</choice>
															<choice hidden="true">
																<text>Hand over Billy.</text>
																<event>
																	<text>Taurus smiles smugly, mockingly shakes your hand, then handcuffs Billy and escorts him back to his ship. "This goes without saying, but you best hope we don't run into each other again, partner. There's one hell of a bounty on your head, and frankly, I'm making a mistake not cashing it in..."</text>
																</event>
															</choice>
														</event>
													</choice>
												</event>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Kill him.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You have no idea who this guy is, but you don't care. I mean, he literally said to kill him. Why wouldn't you oblige? You shoot the Slug square in the head, killing him almost instantly and painting the wall green. Looks like that's the end to this mystery.</text>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="BILLY_SAVE">
	<text>With Billy now safe, you take one last trip past the wreckage. To your surprise, you dig out what appears to be a highly advanced weapon powered by bizarrely foreign yet similar tech. You aren't sure where it's from, but you'll take it. Billy also has a team come in to scan the ship and retrieve its blueprint, which will make a fine addition to your hangar.</text>
	<variable name="loc_angels_killed" op="add" val="1"/>
	<variable name="ach_crew_billy" op="set" val="1"/>
	<weapon name="LIST_WEAPONS_NEWGEN"/>
	<variable name="ach_boss_deathbringer" op="set" val="1"/>
	<unlockCustomShip silent="false">PLAYER_SHIP_ANGEL</unlockCustomShip>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Billy seems to be making himself comfortable in your ship's lounge. "I think nowsss asss good of a time asss any for old Billy to take a relaxing vacation from all of thisss chaossss. And taxesss. Sssay, ssstranger, where you headed?"</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>We're off to save all of reality from the interdimensional Rebellion.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"O-oh. Wait... interdimensssional heroesss probably don't pay their taxessss, do they? Hahah baby, no more taxesss here I come! Oh, and sssaving reality issss cool too, I guessss."</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>One last thing - what about our debt?</text>
						<event>
							<text>"Right... right... Yeah I can take care of that, fair isss fair. You know, it might be a good idea to let everyone here go now. Thisss will be a PR disssasster if it ever got out..."</text>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="BILLY_DEAD">
	<text>You look around the ship to see where Billy went, but it dawns on you - he didn't survive the fight. Looks like you won't be clearing off that debt any time soon then...</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>You make one last trip back to the Angel's ship, and see what you might find inside. To your surprise, you dig out what appears to be a highly advanced weapon powered by bizzarely foreign yet similar tech. You aren't sure where it's from, but you'll take it.</text>
			<weapon name="LIST_WEAPONS_NEWGEN"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<ship name="SHIP_HEKTAR_BOSS" auto_blueprint="MU_HEKTAR_BOSS">
	<destroyed>
		<text>The Hektar ship has been defeated. Maybe you should feel guilty, considering they were just employees following orders, but you don't feel any sympathy whatsoever.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">weapon</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="HEKTAR_SHIPYARDS_WIN"/>
		</choice>
	</destroyed>
	<deadCrew>
		<text>The Hektar ship has been defeated. Maybe you should feel guilty, considering they were just employees following orders, but you don't feel any sympathy whatsoever.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">weapon</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="HEKTAR_SHIPYARDS_WIN"/>
		</choice>
	</deadCrew>
	<!--intentionally no lizards!-->
</ship>
<event name="HEKTAR_SHIPYARDS">
	<preventQuest/>
	<text>At first this beacon seems rather unassuming, until you spot the massive spherical shipyard hovering above the ground. Upon further inspection, beneath it appears to be a rural village of some sort, definitely not one of a space-faring species at least. The village below is bustling with what looks to be lizard creatures. You've noticed these guys working aboard Hektar ships before, but with an educated guess you can assume this is where they live. Very strange, but as you approach the shipyard, it becomes apparent there's more here than you first observed. An orange spectacled lizard with a suit and backwards tie is screaming into a megaphone trying to calm down a crowd of irate lizards with picket signs and armed weapons.</text>
	<img back="BACK_EVENT_HEKTARSHIPYARD" planet="NONE"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Speak to the manager.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You land your ship nearby, unnoticed by the crowd. The lizard in charge turns to you, while you catch shouts of "traitor" and more offensive terms being hurled towards them. "Yes, yes, hello. I am Metyunt, the manager of this facility and caretaker of the Lizard... uh... population. Workforce. Yes, that's the word." Metyunt pushes the glasses back up onto his face, unfazed while a flaming stone is thrown nearby and some lizard rioters tear apart a Hektar ship in the background. You also notice a very large Slug ship hovering above the crowd. It's not firing yet, but you suspect if the crowd pushes things too far, this is their plan to suppress it.</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_HEKTAR_BOSS" hostile="false"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Your 'workforce' doesn't seem too happy.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Metyunt seems slightly uncomfortable. "Yes, I am glad to see you are not in fact blind. These riots are common, but what can you do? They call me a traitor because I 'sold out my own species to a corporation', but look at it this way. It's paid labor, and they signed the contracts. We were living in squalor, but our queen-chief Thek and her council thought it wise to make some... trade agreements with Hektar after we were approached by two Slugs with a deal. I'm just the mediator, and we're better off with this path anyways. Hektar supplies our species with weapons and armaments, and we supply them with work. If we didn't arrange this, then soon enough we'd either be forced to migrate to some wasteland planet by a Ministry contractor looking to build a new law school, or left for dead when the Rebels come calling." 
					
					Metyunt reaches for a bottle of eye drops and drips them into his eye, then ducks as some alien fruit comes whirling by. "I'm doing my best to keep the working conditions fair and orderly, but they just can't see that! I need them to open their eye, because if it weren't for me, Hektar would be a hell of a lot crueler." 
					
					Metyunt makes a sideways glance up at the ship above you both.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>That doesn't sound like helping your species.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"Well I'm sorry if you don't agree, but as I may remind you, you're in debt to the Hektar corporation, so I'm not inclined to take advice from you. I suggest you leave, I have enough to handle at the present moment." Metyunt only barely finishes his sentence when an explosion sends you all flying forward as one of the rioters accidentally sets off an explosive charge in one of the ships stored in the hangar. The Hektar officers watching spring into action and Metyunt follows behind them latching onto the one in charge and trying to stop him from giving the order to fire. The Slug grabs the lizard by the tail and flings Metyunt away, then orders the vessel above to open fire on the crowd. The lizards scatter as lasers pelt them from above. If you're going to get involved, now is the time to do so!</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Protect the crowd.</text>
								<event>
									<text>You rush back to your ship as quick as possible and return to the hangar to fight the vessel.</text>
									<ship hostile="true"/>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Continue...</text>
										<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Hurry out of here.</text>
								<event/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>They're just blind, you're right. Side with Metyunt.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Using all the might in your voice that you can muster, you call out to the crowd and demand they stand down. They refuse, but using a charismatic technique in the Renegade business called "pointing your gun at someone", the lizards seem to see the reason in your words and go scurrying back to their huts. Strangely, Metyunt seems more perturbed than relieved by this, but the Hektar officers who were watching are grateful and offer a reward.</text>
							<weapon name="GIFTLIST_MODULES"/>
							<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="unique_guntput">
						<text>(Guntput) "You are big idiot! Our species still in danger!"</text>
						<event>
							<text>Metyunt does a double take when he sees Guntput aboard your crew. "Shaman? Wh-what are you doing here?" Guntput wacks him on the top of his head with a large branch laying nearby.
							
							"Hektar has betrayed us, fool! The weapons never came, and the queen-chief has abandoned us! Now, we are being taken as slaves, yet you stand here and say we are better off? You are either naive idiot or malevolent jester! Take your pick!" Guntpunt swipes his spear at Metyunt, who leaps backwards as several Hektar employees shuffle forward and draw their guns in precaution, but Metyunt tells them to put their guns away.
							"Shaman, I'm tr-"
							"Do not call me that name! You do not owe me respect when you have abandoned our species for greedy capitalist slimemongers!"
							"Okay, then Guntp-"
							"No, do not call me by name either! You are not deserving to utter it!"
							"Please, I'm trying to reason with you! I didn't abandon our species, I did my best to HELP us! Thek made up her mind on the deal, all I did was negotiate a more hospitable offer. It wasn't even going to be paid labor! There's only so much leeway I can get with Hektar, but I did everything I could!"
							"Nonsense and malarkey! You are lying through teeth. If you did not abandon us, then why are you living here, wearing suit and backwards tie, monocle and carrying clipboard!"
							
							Metyunt is left at a loss for words, but before he can find any, an explosion sends you all flying forward as one of the rioters accidentally sets off an explosive charge in one of the ships stored in the hangar. The Hektar officers watching spring into action and Metyunt follows behind them latching onto the one in charge and trying to stop him from giving the order to fire. The Slug grabs the lizard by the tail and flings Metyunt away, then orders the vessel above to open fire on the crowd. The lizards scatter as lasers pelt them from above. If you're going to get involved, now is the time to do so!</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Protect the crowd.</text>
								<event>
									<text>As you rush back to your ship Guntput turns around and yells one final insult at Metyunt, "Now we go to save our species, unlike you ever could! Maybe you can learn something from it!"</text>
									<ship hostile="true"/>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Continue...</text>
										<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Hurry out of here.</text>
								<event/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>This isn't our business. Stay uninvolved.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore the planet.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Curious as it is, it's very unlikely there's anything here that requires your input.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Check the storage.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="HEKTAR_SHIPYARDS_WIN">
	<text>With the ship out of the way, you return to the shipyard. During the battle, the rioters seem to have taken control a large portion of the hangar, but the remaining Hektar staff are pushing back. This could end in even more bloodshed if you don't step in.</text>
	<variable name="ach_boss_hektarloyalty" op="set" val="1"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Convince Metyunt to talk them into standing down.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You call out to Metyunt, appealing to him to defuse the situation. He falters but calls out to Hektar, demanding they stand down. They refuse at first, but once Metyunt threatens to get Billy involved they stand down. Once Hektar has cleared out, the lizards swarm the rest of the place and capture Metyunt while cheering for your crew. All that seems in question now is the fate of Metyunt.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>He deserves a second chance.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The lizards groan, but they aren't going to question you after how much you helped them. Metyunt seems shocked he hasn't been torn limb from limb yet. "Well uh, I uh... why did you spare me? Second chances? My kind doesn't believe in those, but I guess I'm too far displaced from our traditions to care." It's obvious the lizards don't want Metyunt around. You offer to drop him off somewhere else in the sector, but he declines. "I'm afraid it is best if I find a different occupation. Hektar will have to make do without my help, because I'm done. I guess I'll stick with you now. Oh, and before we go, let me repay you..."</text>
					<unlockCustomShip silent="false">PLAYER_SHIP_HEKTAR</unlockCustomShip>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="DOOR_OPEN_SONG_METYUNT"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>He's had his chance. He shouldn't get any more.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The lizards agree, and a makeshift gallow is constructed from which Metyunt is hung. You didn't quite expect things to be taken that far, but it's too late now. The lizards applaud their new found freedom, though chances are it won't last as soon as you're gone and Hektar sends in reinforcements. Nevertheless, the lizards thank you and offer a reward "borrowed" from another Hektar ship.</text>
					<autoReward level="MED">stuff</autoReward>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>We can't risk it. Take what you've got and leave.</text>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="EXIT_HEKTAR">
	<text>You've finally found the exit to this dreadful sector.</text>
	<variable name="loc_hektarexit" op="set" val="1"/>
	<choice req="loc_hektarexit" lvl="0" max_group="0" hidden="true" blue="false"> <!--theoretically you can never get this except in the fleet so Im just going to make it that for simplisities sake-->
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>You're stopped before you can leave by a massive Hektar vessel. "Sssorry, but you may not leave thisss sssector! You sssstill owe Hektar Indusssstriessss a lot of money!"</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_HEKTAR_EXIT_BOSS" hostile="false"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Looks like we'll have to fight our way out!</text>
				<event>
					<text>The only way out now is to fight! You power up your weapons and prepare to engage.</text>
					<ship hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_VARIANT_BILLY">
				<text>(Billy) Have Billy clear you for leaving.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Fortunately, it only takes a few minutes before Billy returns, and you're allowed to leave. Guess it pays to have the CEO of a major corporation aboard your ship.</text>
					<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
					<weapon name="HEKTAR_MODULAR_WEAPONS"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="unique_metyunt">
				<text>(Metyunt) Have Metyunt clear you for leaving.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Fortunately, it only takes a few minutes before Metyunt returns, and you're allowed to leave. Guess it pays to have the staff manager of a major corporation aboard your ship.</text>
					<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
					<weapon name="HEKTAR_MODULAR_WEAPONS"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice req="loc_hektarexit" lvl="1" max_group="0" hidden="true" blue="false"> <!--theoretically you can never get this except in the fleet so Im just going to make it that for simplisities sake-->
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Looks like the Rebel fleet has taken control of the beacon! You'll have to fight your way out!</text>
			<customFleet right="false" firing="true" autoDarkening="false">CUSTOM_FLEET_REBEL</customFleet>
			<environment type="PDS" target="player"/>
			<ship load="SHIP_REBEL_FLEET_S" hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="engines" lvl="6">
				<text>(Adv. Engines) Try to escape the Elite.</text>
				<event load="FLEET_ESCAPE"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_JERRY">
				<text>(Jerry) "Hello!"</text>
				<event>
					<text load="TEXT_ENCOUNTER_REBEL_JERRY_HELLO"/>
					<ship hostile="false"/> 
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="NEBULA_EXIT_HEKTAR">
	<text>You've finally found the exit to this dreadful sector.</text>
	<variable name="loc_hektarexit" op="set" val="1"/>
	<environment type="nebula"/>
	<choice req="loc_hektarexit" lvl="0" max_group="0" hidden="true" blue="false"> <!--theoretically you can never get this except in the fleet so Im just going to make it that for simplisities sake-->
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>You're stopped before you can leave by a massive Hektar vessel. "Sssorry, but you may not leave thisss sssector! You sssstill owe Hektar Indusssstriessss a lot of money!"</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_HEKTAR_EXIT_BOSS" hostile="false"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Looks like we'll have to fight our way out!</text>
				<event>
					<text>The only way out now is to fight! You power up your weapons and prepare to engage.</text>
					<ship hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_VARIANT_BILLY">
				<text>(Billy) Have Billy clear you for leaving.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Fortunately, it only takes a few minutes before Billy returns, and you're allowed to leave. Guess it pays to have the CEO of a major corporation aboard your ship.</text>
					<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
					<weapon name="HEKTAR_MODULAR_WEAPONS"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="unique_metyunt">
				<text>(Metyunt) Have Metyunt clear you for leaving.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Fortunately, it only takes a few minutes before Metyunt returns, and you're allowed to leave. Guess it pays to have the staff manager of a major corporation aboard your ship.</text>
					<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
					<weapon name="HEKTAR_MODULAR_WEAPONS"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice req="loc_hektarexit" lvl="1" max_group="0" hidden="true" blue="false"> <!--theoretically you can never get this except in the fleet so Im just going to make it that for simplisities sake-->
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Looks like the Rebel fleet has taken control of the beacon! You'll have to fight your way out!</text>
			<customFleet right="false" firing="true" autoDarkening="false">CUSTOM_FLEET_REBEL</customFleet>
			<environment type="PDS" target="player"/>
			<ship load="SHIP_REBEL_FLEET_S" hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="engines" lvl="6">
				<text>(Adv. Engines) Try to escape the Elite.</text>
				<event load="FLEET_ESCAPE"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_JERRY">
				<text>(Jerry) "Hello!"</text>
				<event>
					<text load="TEXT_ENCOUNTER_REBEL_JERRY_HELLO"/>
					<ship hostile="false"/> 
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
		CLEARING EVENTS!!!!!
		CLEARING EVENTS!!!!!
		CLEARING EVENTS!!!!!
-->
<eventList name="CLEARING_HEKTAR">
	<event load="HEKTAR_UNION"/>
	<event load="HEKTAR_SUZERAIN"/>
	<event load="DISTRESS_HEKTAR_GHETTO"/>
	<event load="HEKTAR_INVESTOR"/>
</eventList>

<event name="HEKTAR_INVESTOR" unique="true">
	<text>Nearby, the ship of a wealthy tycoon is exploring the beacon. Might be an interesting chat.</text>
	<choice hidden="true" req="loc_dinkleman" lvl="0" max_group="0" blue="false">
		<text>Hail them.</text>
		<event load="HEKTAR_INVESTOR_QUESTIONS_NOTMET"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="loc_dinkleman" lvl="1" max_group="0" blue="false">
		<text>Hail them.</text>
		<event load="HEKTAR_INVESTOR_QUESTIONS_MET"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="pilot" lvl="1" max_group="1" blue="false">
		<text>Ignore the tycoon.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You fly away from the shuttle and find somewhere else to do something aboard the ship.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Check the storage.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="HEKTAR_INVESTOR_QUESTIONS_NOTMET"> <!--you haven't met Dinkleman yet-->
	<text>"Oh, chip chap cheerio good fellow! I am Count Dinkleman Reichster Von Applebuzz Tri Tri the Fourth, at your service. I have taken a long venture to these lands to see what treasures Hektar might have to offer me and my immense wealth. Tell me, good sir or madam, what are your opinions on Hektar?"</text>
	<variable name="loc_dinkleman" op="set" val="1"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>They're tricking people into being trapped in this sector.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Good heavens, what a genius idea! Forcing people into paying off an imaginary debt by trapping them in a massive market place, then hiding it in a nebula where the Federation will never find it? Delightful! I'm sure you think it's horrible though, because you aren't disgustingly rich. Anyways, thanks for the chat, gotta go!" The man sprints back to his ship, dropping several piles of scrap from his pockets as he goes.</text>
			<autoReward level="LOW">scrap_only</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>They're literally enslaving people.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Oh, well you know what they say in 'the business'. Actually, I don't. I'm not in 'the business'. But somewhere, I'm sure they have some justfiable reasons for slavery. Clearly, you wouldn't know, because you aren't disgustingly rich. Anyways, thanks for the chat, gotta go!" The man sprints back to his ship, dropping several piles of scrap from his pockets as he goes.</text>
			<autoReward level="LOW">scrap_only</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Meh, they're alright.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Just alright, eh? Well, what about their products? You have a large military vessel at your disposal. Do you enjoy the use of Hektar's signature modular weaponry?"</text>
			<choice hidden="true" req="HEKTAR_MODULAR_WEAPONS" blue="false">
				<text>They're pretty good.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Good you say? Marvelous! I'm no military man, but I'll take your word for it! I shall invest in Hektar. A remarkable chat, good fellow. Say, do me a service and take this worthless assistant of mine off of my hands. I think one of Hektar's lizard people will serve me better."</text>
					<achievement>ACH_EVENT_COUNT</achievement>
					<crewMember amount="1" class="engi"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="HEKTAR_MODULAR_WEAPONS" blue="false">
				<text>They're awful.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Oh, well that's certainly not good. I'm no military man, but I'll take your word for it! I shall not invest in Hektar. Here, you can have this worthless piece of junk, considering I certainly won't want it."</text>
					<achievement>ACH_EVENT_COUNT</achievement>
					<weapon name="SHOP_ITEM_HEKTAR_BASE"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Don't have any.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Well, then you are worthless to me. Imagine being so poor. Thanks for the chat, gotta go!" The man sprints back to his ship, dropping several piles of scrap from his pockets as he goes.</text>
					<autoReward level="LOW">scrap_only</autoReward>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="HEKTAR_INVESTOR_QUESTIONS_MET"> <!--you have met Dinkleman yet-->
	<text>"Strange poor person, we meet again! It is me, Count Dinkleman Reichster Von Applebuzz Tri Tri the Fourth! What a coincidence we happen upon each other on this occasion. I have taken a long venture to these lands to see what treasures Hektar might have to offer me and my immense wealth. Tell me, good sir or madam, what are your opinions on Hektar?"</text>
	<variable name="loc_dinkleman" op="set" val="1"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>They're tricking people into being trapped in this sector.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Good heavens, what a genius idea! Forcing people into paying off an imaginary debt by trapping them in a massive market place, then hiding it in a nebula where the Federation will never find it? Delightful! I'm sure you think it's horrible though, because you aren't disgustingly rich. Anyways, thanks for the chat, gotta go!" The man sprints back to his ship, dropping several piles of scrap from his pockets as he goes.</text>
			<autoReward level="LOW">scrap_only</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>They're literally enslaving people.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Oh, well you know what they say in 'the business.' Actually, I don't. I'm not in 'the business.' But somewhere, I'm sure they have some justfiable reasons for slavery. Clearly, you wouldn't know, because you aren't disgustingly rich. Anyways, thanks for the chat, gotta go!" The man sprints back to his ship, dropping several piles of scrap from his pockets as he goes.</text>
			<autoReward level="LOW">scrap_only</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Meh, they're alright.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Just alright, eh? Well, what about their products? You have a large military vessel at your disposal. Do you enjoy the use of Hektar's signature modular weaponry?"</text>
			<choice hidden="true" req="HEKTAR_MODULAR_WEAPONS" blue="false">
				<text>They're pretty good.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Good you say? Marvelous! I'm no military man, but I'll take your word for it! I shall invest in Hektar. A remarkable chat, good fellow. Say, do me a service and take this worthless assistant of mine off of my hands. I think one of Hektar's lizard people will serve me better."</text>
					<achievement>ACH_EVENT_COUNT</achievement>
					<crewMember amount="1" class="engi"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="HEKTAR_MODULAR_WEAPONS" blue="false">
				<text>They're awful.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Oh, well that's certainly not good. I'm no military man, but I'll take your word for it! I shall not invest in Hektar. Here, you can have this worthless piece of junk, considering I certainly won't want it."</text>
					<achievement>ACH_EVENT_COUNT</achievement>
					<weapon name="SHOP_ITEM_HEKTAR_BASE"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Don't have any.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Well, then you are worthless to me. Imagine being so poor. Thanks for the chat, gotta go!" The man sprints back to his ship, dropping several piles of scrap from his pockets as he goes.</text>
					<autoReward level="LOW">scrap_only</autoReward>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DISTRESS_HEKTAR_GHETTO" unique="true">
	<text>The nearby planet boasts both a bustling ghetto full of lizards - and a pirate ship firing upon them! There's a good chance Hektar knows about this but doesn't care to intervene, so you might be their only hope!</text>
	<img planet="PLANET_POPULATED"/>
	<distressBeacon/>
	<ship load="SHIP_HEKTAR_PIRATE_GHETTO" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Rescue the lizards.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You prepare to fight the pirate ship.</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore the ghetto.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The lives of these lizards are nothing to you. Bah, let them all die for all you care.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Check the storage.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="HEKTAR_UNION" unique="true">
	<text>You're surprised to find a band of lizards aboard a nearby Hektar ship, unaccompanied by any Slugs. They hail you. "You are a military ship, right? I think you could be of assistance to us. Will you help?"</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Listen to their offer.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"We have begun the steps towards establishing a union that might finally make this place less of a hell to work at. Unfortunately, our boss refuses to even acknowledge our efforts. Will you help 'encourage' him for us? Just make sure you don't kill him, otherwise this will all have been pointless!"</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Agree.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The lizards show you where their boss is located and reinforce that you must not kill him.</text>
					<ship load="SHIP_HEKTAR_UNION" hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Reveal their plan to their manager.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The Slug laughs when he learns about the lizards' plan. "Hah, thossse idiotss don't even know how to wear a ssshirt the right way. Thanksss for telling me though, a good whippin' will do them good!" The greedy Slug doesn't even give you anything in return, but the lizards are furious and storm your ship!</text>
					<boarders min="3" max="4" class="lizard"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Decline.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>No thanks.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The lizards make no further comment and go back to talking amongst themselves.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Check the storage.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="HEKTAR_SUZERAIN" unique="true">
	<text>You really can't say you expected to find a Suzerain ship so far out here, and you heavily doubt they're victims to Hektar. For what reasons might they have come?</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_SUZERAIN_FIGHT" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Hail them.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Suzerain responds, flailing his arms in several grand motions. "Greetings! You are hearing of the great Billy Hektar, yes? He is man of fewest ethics, leader of greatest and most morally bankrupt corporation in WHOLE Multiverse! I come to learn from him and master ways of becoming living scum myself! Have you heard his teachings?"</text>
			<choice hidden="true" req="slug">
				<text>(Slug Crew) We have.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"I see you are having Slug one aboard your ship! Squishy men, but most natural commers of retched living! Honored I am, and giving you things."</text>
					<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="slug_clansman">
				<text>(Clansman Crew) We have.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"I see you are having Guild man aboard your ship! Hunter and poacher of sentient things, skinner of the living! Oh how I envy your nerves of steel and torturous methods of mutilation! Honored I am, and giving you things."</text>
					<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="slug_saboteur">
				<text>(Saboteur Crew) We have.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"I see you are having stealthy cloaking Slug aboard your ship! Cunning master of silent assassinations and devilish trickery! Oh, oh, how I hoping to learn! Yes, I coming with to learn from you!"</text>
					<autoReward level="LOW">standard</autoReward>
					<crewMember amount="1" class="mantis_suzerain"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="slug_ranger">
				<text>(Ranger Crew) We have.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"I see you are having evilest taxidermy man aboard your ship! Master of sniping and knowledgeable in all forms of unethical biological weapons! Oh, oh, how I hoping to learn! Yes, I coming with to learn from you!"</text>
					<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
					<crewMember amount="1" class="mantis_suzerain"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_VARIANT_HEKTAR">
				<text>(Hektar Crew) We have.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"You are having one of Billy's own disciples! You are seeing oh great Billy in the flesh! I honored, truly! Please, allowing me to come and learn!"</text>
					<crewMember amount="1" class="mantis_suzerain"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_VARIANT_BILLY">
				<text>(Billy) Introduce him to Billy.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"EEK! It is you! Most ungraceful one, Billy himself! I not knowing what to say, overcome with excitement! Please, allowing me to come with you, it would be biggest of honors!"</text>
					<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
					<crewMember amount="1" all_skills="2" class="mantis_suzerain"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>We haven't.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Hah! Then you are stupid idiot! Biggest of fools, ethically driven and morally abundant! Hahahahah! The galaxy needing less of you, so I doing that."</text>
					<ship hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore the Suzerains.</text>
		<event>
			<text>There's no sane reason to go interacting with Suzerains unless you want to risk having your head removed. You put a large distance between your ships just in case.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Check the storage.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
		NEBULA EVENTS!!!!!
		NEBULA EVENTS!!!!!
		NEBULA EVENTS!!!!!
-->

<!--
		DISTRESS!!!
	Events that can call a fight
-->
<eventList name="NEBULA_DISTRESS_HEKTAR">
	<event load="NEBULA_DISTRESS_HEKTAR_CHILDREN"/>
	<event load="NEBULA_DISTRESS_HEKTAR_DEBTORS"/>
	<event load="NEBULA_DISTRESS_HEKTAR_CRISIS"/>
</eventList>

<event name="NEBULA_DISTRESS_HEKTAR_FEMALE" unique="true"> <!--this one always spawns-->
	<text>Seems a Hektar transport nearby is broadcasing the distress signal. Upon hailing, the frustrated captain appears to be wiping blood from his face. "A Renegade? Not really what I wassss looking for, but whatever. Our shipment isss in revolt and it'sss ssscrewing up our time ssschedule. Do usss a favor and calm it down, would you?"</text>
	<environment type="nebula"/>
	<distressBeacon/>
	<ship load="SHIP_HEKTAR_FEMALE" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Your shipment?</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Yeah. We're bringing in more lizardsss. Billy had ssssome dumb rule againsssst 'breeding them' but I don't know how he expectssss usss to get more workersss then. Luckily that idiot is bussssy, ssso HQ'ssss having usss bring ssssome more in under the radar ssso we don't have to pay them more. Uhm... maybe I sssshouldn't have told you that."</text>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CHECK_ANY_CREW" lvl="1" blue="false">
				<text>Help try to put down the revolt.</text>
				<event load="HEKTAR_FEMALE_ASSIST"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CHECK_ANY_CREW" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
				<text>We have no crew to assist with.</text>
				<event load="OPTION_INVALID"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Help the lizards.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Man jussst our luck, I ran into the ONE Renegade who givesss a damn about sssslavery. Fine, guesss I'll take care of thisss revolt later."</text>
					<ship hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="unique_billy">
				<text>(Billy) "Hey, I didn't authorize thisss!"</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Oohhhh. Oohhhhhh. Sssshit. You have... the bossss on your ssship. Well I guesssss I'm fired, huh?" Billy nods his head. "Welp. Off to the unemployment line I go." The Slug hangs up and an escape pod soon after ejects from the ship. Seems that was a rather quick way of handling that.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Check on the lizards.</text>
						<event load="HEKTAR_FEMALE_SAVE"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>You disgust me.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Oh, and the hired killer sssuddenly hasss a moral compasss? Get a grip. Fine, if you won't help then get losssst."</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Check the storage.</text>
						<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Do nothing.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="HEKTAR_FEMALE_ASSIST">
	<event>
		<text>It's no wonder the Slugs needed help - the "shipment" of lizards put up quite the fight. In the end you make it out without any casualties on your end, though several lizards die. The Slugs are frustrated but reluctantly offer you a reward.</text>
		<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>It's no wonder the Slugs needed help - the "shipment" of lizards put up quite the fight. One of your crew doesn't make it out in the end but the lizards are otherwise contained. The Slug laughs upon hearing the news of your crew, but when you slap him and threaten to blow up his ship he relents and offers a reward.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">item</autoReward>
		<removeCrew>
			<clone>true</clone>
			<text>Though you make no mention of it to the Slugs, fortunately your crew member is able to be revived by the Clone Bay.</text>
		</removeCrew>
	</event>
</eventList>
<event name="HEKTAR_FEMALE_SAVE">
	<text>With the Slugs all gone, you board the transport to see what remains. Some of the lizards are wounded, dead, or dying, but a number still live. You go one by one freeing them until you stumble upon a giant creature in the very back of the cargo bay! It's a lizard for sure, but twice the size as all the others, and much more lethargic."</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Are you one of them?</text>
		<event>
			<text>As the giant lizard speaks, its deep voice seems to reverberate with wisdom and age. "There is no need to be rude. I, am Vunk. A lizard I mostly certainly am, yes. But not of the kind you have seen thus far. We females of the species are much older, much wiser, and much larger. It seems though the Slugs have not yet stooped to the levels of systematic breeding, they are hoping we might reproduce naturally within their work camps."</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>That's awful.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"It is, isn't it. But for what use would Hektar have with morals? Come, would you please free me? These poor souls are without a leader, and it seems it is my natural duty now to guide them back to our home."</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Free Vunk.</text>
						<event>
							<text>As you start to free Vunk from her cage, you inquire how come you've never seen any other female lizards. "Our species naturally breeds fewer females. Not to speak so... lowly of the others, but the gap in our intelligence is often paramount. Nevertheless, it is the matriarchy that used to thrive on our homeworlds. But poaching from the EHG, slavers even before the time of Hektar, and ancient wars within our species have reduced our numbers greatly. With so few of us left on the homeworlds, it is vital that I return. Thank you, strange but kind soul. I am forever indebted to you. I will send with you the most able of fighters among us to assist you. They will be loyal to your cause." Vunk motions with her giant leg to one of the younger lizards. "Go now, little one. This is your new duty."</text>
							<variable name="door_female" op="set" val="1"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event load="DOOR_OPEN_SONG"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="NEBULA_DISTRESS_HEKTAR_CRISIS" unique="true">
	<text>You see the distress call at this beacon, but you see no ship in distress. Instead, a lizard piloting a cargo ship hails you.</text>
	<environment type="nebula"/>
	<distressBeacon/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>What's with the distress beacon?</text>
		<event>
			<text>"I am in distress! Oh, horrible horrible. Not the kind of distress you are thinking of, no. I am in despair! I think I am having a mental breakdown! What is life? All I know is work. All I do is work. I know nothing but work. Is there more to life but an endless cycle of work?"</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>No. You either work, or you become obsolete.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Oh, then let me choose obsoletion! I quit!" The Lizard opens all of the airlocks aboard his ship, venting him, the rest of the crew, and the entire cargo. It's quite morbid, but it won't stop you from swooping in and stealing some of the crates.</text>
					<autoReward level="HIGH">stuff</autoReward>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Yes. Work hard enough and eventually you'll be free from the cycle.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"You mean there is freedom? The metaphorical pot of gold at the end of the metaphorical rainbow? Then I shall seek that gold! You have given me hope! Thank you captain!" The Lizard offers you a drone from the cargo.</text>
					<drone name="RANDOM"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_MONK">
				<text>(Monk Crew) "Life is a cycle yes - but which cycle you follow is up to you."</text>
				<event>
					<text>"I have a choice? I thought Hektar was all there was. That's what they told me - the rest of the galaxy was a barren wasteland and this was the last sector alive. But wait... you're from out there! I must come with you and taste freedom at long last!"</text>
					<variable name="door_crisis" op="set" val="1"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="DOOR_OPEN_SONG"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_FREEMAN">
				<text>(Free Mantis Crew) "Status Quo is only what big man upstair wanting you to follow!"</text>
				<event>
					<text>"I have a choice? I thought Hektar was all there was. That's what they told me - the rest of the galaxy was a barren wasteland and this was the last sector alive. But wait... you're from out there! I must come with you and taste freedom at long last!"</text>
					<variable name="door_crisis" op="set" val="1"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="DOOR_OPEN_SONG"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>I'm not a philosopher.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The lizard has already broken out into full on sobbing and barely hears your lame excuse to leave.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Check the storage.</text>
						<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Do nothing.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="NEBULA_DISTRESS_HEKTAR_DEBTORS" unique="true">
	<text>The distress call appears to originate from a ship, lost in the clouds. "Please, help us! We are in debt to Hektar, but our chances of paying it off are hopeless! Is there anything you can spare us?"</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_GENERIC" hostile="false"/>
	<environment type="nebula"/>
	<distressBeacon/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Give them a small amount of scrap. [-15~]</text>
		<event>
			<text>With such a small amount, you'd expect the ship to take it as an insult. Instead, they seem grateful. "Thank you so much! It is so little, yes, but any amount of generosity increases our chances of getting out of here." The civilians cannot pay you in scrap, so they offer you an upgrade to your life support instead.</text>
			<upgrade amount="1" system="oxygen"/>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="-15" max="-15"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Give them a large amount of scrap. [-50~]</text>
		<event>
			<text>The civilians are shocked you'd offer them so much money. "T-thank you so much! This will help tremendously." Obviously, the civilians cannot reward you with a donation of scrap, so they repay you with detailed sector mappings they've collected from their extensive time here, as well as a reactor upgrade and some fuel.</text>
			<autoReward level="MED">fuel_only</autoReward>
			<upgrade amount="1" system="reactor"/>
			<reveal_map/>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="-50" max="-50"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>These guys are a good target. Attack!</text>
		<event>
			<text>You raise your weapons and attack the ship.</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="MORALITY_UPDATE_GENERAL_FIGHT"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>We can't help, sorry.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Unfortunately, these civilians will have to rely on other means to save themselves. Knowing how this sector is a giant trap, it's unlikely they'll find any other vessel willing to help.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Check the storage.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="NEBULA_DISTRESS_HEKTAR_CHILDREN" unique="true">
	<text>A Hektar distress beacon is coming from this beacon. From the looks of it, it appears a crowd of Slugs has gathered at a Hektar factory.</text>
	<environment type="nebula"/>
	<distressBeacon/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Contact the factory owners.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The factory owner appears to be a frustrated and middle-aged Slug. In the background, hundreds of Slug children toil away working the machines. "Ugh, for years we've been running Hektar with thossse lizard freakssss. But when I decccide I want to ssstart ussssing children to run my facccilitiessss, NOW people freak out? Jeez, what issss wrong with people..."</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Assist the factory owners and disperse the protestors.</text>
				<event load="HEKTAR_CHILDREN_DISPERSE"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Assist the protestors and liberate the children.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You power up your weapons and attack the Hektar factory. A ship arrives to stop you.</text>
					<ship load="SHIP_HEKTAR_CHILDREN" hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="false">
				<text>Pay the factory owner to free the children.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The Slug is reluctant to turn over his workers, but he seems to see the logic in your offer and accepts it. The children are set free and the jubilant protestors reward you.</text>
					<item_modify>
						<item type="scrap" min="-20" max="-30"/>
					</item_modify>
					<choice hidden="false">
						<text>Accept their gift.</text>
						<event>
							<weapon name="RANDOM"/>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="false">
						<text>Ignore their gift, take one of the children, and quickly leave.</text>
						<event>
							<crewMember amount="1" class="slug">Timmy</crewMember>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Leave.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore the factory.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Looks like things could turn ugly fast. Better if you don't get involved.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Check the storage.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="HEKTAR_CHILDREN_DISPERSE">
	<event>
		<text>The crowd is put down easily. Not willing to reinforce their thoughts with a counter attack, the Slugs leave and the factory owner pays you. You are now an official supporter of forced child labor, congratulations!</text>
		<autoReward level="LOW">scrap_only</autoReward>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>Looks like the protestors are more willing to defend their thoughts than you expected. A few shots dent your hull, but fortunately it's not too bad. Seeing their attacks were mostly ineffective, the protestors give up and the factory owner pays you. You are now an official supporter of forced child labor, congratulations!</text>
		<autoReward level="LOW">scrap_only</autoReward>
		<damage amount="3"/>
	</event>
</eventList>

<!--
		ITEMS!!!
	Events that can call a fight
-->
<eventList name="NEBULA_ITEMS_HEKTAR">
	<event load="NEBULA_HEKTAR_HOPE"/>
	<event load="NEBULA_HEKTAR_TOYS"/>
	<event load="NEBULA_HEKTAR_SYLVAN"/>
	<event load="NEBULA_HEKTAR_RAIN"/>
</eventList>

<event name="NEBULA_HEKTAR_RAIN" unique="true">
	<text>On the small nearby planet through the clearing you observe a small Hektar facility. It turns out to be some agricultural center, but the planet is otherwise barren and devoid of life. Scans show the facility is mostly being run by lizards.</text>
	<img back="BACK_EVENT_LIGHTNEBULA" planet="PLANET_UNPOPULATED"/>
	<status type="loss" target="player" system="sensors" amount="1"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Check it out.</text>
		<event>
			<text>As you approach the facility, your video feed shows a strange scene. A band of lizards are rotating around a small planter of unsprouted seeds, chanting a song. Their leader appears to be wearing a crudely made cardboard mask.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Inquire what they're doing.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"We sing the rain song, and hope the rain comes! Hektar has put us here, in this desolate place, and expects seeds to grow and make great bounty! But there is no water here!" The lizard grumbles. "I will sing the rain song till creation dies. But if rain does not come, I die first!"</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Join them.</text>
						<event>
							<text>You dismount from the ship with your crew and join the lizards in chanting. Of course, the 'rain' never comes, but they seem happy you offered your help. After a while the lizards give up, but offer to upgrade your ship afterwards.</text>
							<modifyPursuit amount="1"/>
							<upgrade amount="1" system="oxygen"/>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="unique_guntput">
						<text>(Guntput) Send Guntput down there with them.</text>
						<event>
							<text>The lizards seem shocked to see Guntput. "Oh great Shaman! I ashamed! We should have listened, your advice was most wise. Now, we are trapped, and there is no rain! What will become of us?" Guntput frowns and smacks the lizard with his shield. "There is no point in shame. What is done is done. Our people will live, the homeworlds are in shambles but we live. The rain will not come you fool. Come with us, we will make better use of you than rotting in Hektar's communes."</text>
							<variable name="door_rain" op="set" val="1"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event load="DOOR_OPEN_SONG"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="unique_billy">
						<text>(Billy) Send Billy down there with them.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Upon seeing Billy the lizards all bow, but he seems mostly confused. "Why... why are you guysss down here? Aren't you sssupposssed to be packing boxesss or running the cargo ssships?" The lizards shake their heads. "Box shipping full! Cargo ships all piloted! Still, more slaves come in. Too many workers, so we are placed here." Billy shudders upon hearing the word slave. "Mhm... I... Okay maybe I made a little missstake here. Uh... you guyssss are formally disssmissed. Go back to your homesss or whatever." The lizards are confused. "We... have no homes. You abducted us." Billy winces again. "Uhm... then you're working for usss now."</text>
							<variable name="door_rain" op="set" val="1"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event load="DOOR_OPEN_SONG"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="BLUELIST_WEAPONS_FIRE_ALL">
						<text>(Fire Weapon) Start a fire to turn on the sprinklers.</text>
						<event>
							<text>The lizards shriek as your weapons set the facility ablaze. Indeed, the sprinklers do come on, but are useless at stopping the blaze. Soon the whole building goes up in smoke and the lizards are forced to evacuate. "You are stupidest being! What did you expect to happen? Go, shoo! Hektar will be furious."</text>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Try to get them to give up.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"Did not hear me? I said I sing the rain song till the day creation dies or rain comes!" The lizard shakes his head in annoyance and goes back to chanting.</text>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore the facility.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You doubt there's going to be anything of value to find at an agriculture facility.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Check the storage.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="NEBULA_HEKTAR_SYLVAN" unique="true">
	<text>"Sssstranger, welcome to my beacon!" You jump, thinking you've somehow found Sylvan yet again, but instead it seems this is just another Hektar employee, not the infamous traveling merchant.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_HEKTAR_TRANSPORT_LOOT" hostile="false"/>
	<environment type="nebula"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Why are you pretending to be Sylvan?</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Well, Sssylvan isss my hero! He'ssss sso cool. And hot. I wisssh I wasss that cool and hot... Pardon the oxymoron."</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do you sell things too?</text>
				<event>
					<text>The Slug perks up. "In fact, I do!" He resumes his impersonation from before. "Come on in sssstranger, and take a look at my goodssss!"</text>
					<store>STORE_HEKTAR_DEFAULT</store>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>You're not quite up to his level, shield and weaponry wise.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Yeah... I'm not even sssure how he managed thisss! Every time I try to inssstall that many ssshields I jussst get an obnoxious beep like I've hit a hardcoded limit or sssomething."</text>
					<choice>
						<text>Offer him some scrap to spruce up his ship.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"That'ssss quite generoussss, ssstranger! Uh, I mean, thankssss."</text>
							<item_modify>
								<item type="scrap" min="-90" max="-90"/>
							</item_modify>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event>
									<text>"Oh man, I don't have anything to give... wait, no! I do! Thissss isss very valuable to me, but I'm sssure you'll get a lot more ussse out of it than me. Pleasssse take good care of it though."</text>
									<weapon name="LASER_CHAINGUN_GOLD"/>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Do you sell things too?</text>
						<event>
							<text>The Slug perks up. "In fact, I do!" He resumes his impersonation from before. "Come on in sssstranger, and take a look at my goodssss!"</text>
							<store>STORE_HEKTAR_DEFAULT</store>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="unique_sylvan">
				<text>(Sylvan) "Well hello, ssstranger!"</text>
				<event>
					<text>"OH GOD! IT'SSS YOU! OH MY OH MY OH MY OH MY OH MY!" The Slug practically demands that you allow him on the ship so that he can work alongside Sylvan.</text>
					<crewMember amount="1" combat="2" class="slug_hektar"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore the pretender.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You aren't sure why someone would try to immitate Sylvan, but it's nothing more than a nuisance to you.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Check the storage.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="NEBULA_HEKTAR_TOYS" unique="true">
	<text>A small Hektar run gift-shop is nearby. It's highly unlikely it's carrying any military goods, but maybe you'll find something interesting inside?</text>
	<environment type="nebula"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Check it out.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You're welcomed by an overweight Slug. "Visssitorssss! Come on in! I have ssssomething to ssshow you! I've created a new line of pull-ssstring toysss resssembling variousss racccesss accrosss the galaxy. Come and try them!"</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Pull the Human's string.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The human toy squeaks, and spits out "Glory to the Rebellion!" The Slug notices your shock and tries to calm your nerves. "It'sss okay! A lot humans are Rebelsss, that'sss the point! It'ss relatable for humansss!"</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Right...</text>
						<event>
							<text>The Slug laughs nervously. "I'm guesssing you don't like it then? *Sigh*, okay..." The Slug slithers back to the store counter, defeated. "There'sss a military depot not too far from here. Go there inssstead if you want sssomething wortwhile..."</text>
							<store>STORE_HEKTAR_DEFAULT</store>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Buy the toy for 20 scrap.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"You actually like it? OH BOY! Thank you ssso much! My brother tried to ssstart a plusssshie line in the EHG and thingsss haven't been going well for him, ssso I can't wait to tell him that good newsss! Wait, better yet, I'll come with you, and then I can ssssell my toysss to the whole Multiverssse!"</text>
							<item_modify>
								<item type="scrap" min="-20" max="-20"/>
							</item_modify>
							<crewMember amount="1" class="slug_hektar"/>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_HUMAN">
						<text>(Human Crew) Offer your feedback.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Your crew explains their opinions on the toy. The Slug thoughtfully contemplates this advice, and seems grateful. "Thank you ssso much for your input! Here, have thisss!"</text>
							<autoReward level="MED">stuff</autoReward>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Pull the Mantis's string.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The Mantis toy squeaks, and spits out "Kill all living things!" The Slug notices your shock and tries to calm your nerves. "It'sss okay! Mantisss are jussst like that! It'sss not offensssive if it'ssss true, right?"</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Right...</text>
						<event>
							<text>The Slug laughs nervously. "I'm guesssing you don't like it then? *Sigh*, okay..." The Slug slithers back to the store counter, defeated. "There'sss a military depot not too far from here. Go there inssstead if you want sssomething wortwhile..."</text>
							<store>STORE_HEKTAR_DEFAULT</store>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Buy the toy for 20 scrap.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"You actually like it? OH BOY! Thank you ssso much! My brother tried to ssstart a plusssshie line in the EHG and thingsss haven't been going well for him, ssso I can't wait to tell him that good newsss! Wait, better yet, I'll come with you, and then I can ssssell my toysss to the whole Multiverssse!"</text>
							<item_modify>
								<item type="scrap" min="-20" max="-20"/>
							</item_modify>
							<crewMember amount="1" class="slug_hektar"/>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_MANTIS">
						<text>(Mantis Crew) Offer your feedback.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Your crew explains their opinions on the toy. The Slug thoughtfully contemplates this advice, and seems grateful. "Thank you ssso much for your input! Here, have thisss!"</text>
							<autoReward level="MED">stuff</autoReward>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Pull the Shell's string.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The Shell toy squeaks, and spits out "Racism is good!" The Slug notices your shock and tries to calm your nerves. "It'sss okay! Sssshellsss usssse racccissssm to organize their ssspeciesss! They're sssmart, ssso clearly they've figured sssomething out! It'sss the context that makesss it okay!"</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Right...</text>
						<event>
							<text>The Slug laughs nervously. "I'm guesssing you don't like it then? *Sigh*, okay..." The slug slithers back to the store counter, defeated. "There'sss a military depot not too far from here. Go there inssstead if you want sssomething wortwhile..."</text>
							<store>STORE_HEKTAR_DEFAULT</store>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Buy the toy for 20 scrap.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"You actually like it? OH BOY! Thank you ssso much! My brother tried to ssstart a plusssshie line in the EHG and thingsss haven't been going well for him, ssso I can't wait to tell him that good newsss! Wait, better yet, I'll come with you, and then I can ssssell my toysss to the whole Multiverssse!"</text>
							<item_modify>
								<item type="scrap" min="-20" max="-20"/>
							</item_modify>
							<crewMember amount="1" class="slug_hektar"/>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_SHELL">
						<text>(Shell Crew) Offer your feedback.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Your crew explains their opinions on the toy. The Slug thoughtfully contemplates this advice, and seems grateful. "Thank you ssso much for your input! Here, have thisss!"</text>
							<autoReward level="MED">stuff</autoReward>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore the gift-shop.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You're on an important mission, no time to stop by worthless tourist traps like this.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Check the storage.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="NEBULA_HEKTAR_HOPE" unique="true">
	<text>A civilian ship is here, wandering through the clouds, lost and afraid. Their captain perks up when he sees you. "The Federation has arrived?! I thought we'd be trapped here forever indebted to these Slugs bastards!"</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_CIVILIAN_ALL" hostile="false"/>
	<environment type="nebula"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Confess the truth - the Federation has no idea about this place.</text>
		<event load="HEKTAR_HOPE_TRUTH"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Lie - promise them the Federation has arrived to help.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Then we are saved! This is a glorious day, liberation at last! I cannot offer much, but please, take this fuel!"</text>
			<autoReward level="MED">fuel_only</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="human_soldier">
		<text>(Soldier Crew) We did not come here to stop Hektar - but we will do our best now that we are here.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Wow! So noble! But, for you to do anything you'll have to make it out of here alive. Let me see if I can help you with that!" The civilian ship patches up some of the damage to your hull.</text>
			<damage amount="-30"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="HEKTAR_HOPE_TRUTH">
	<event>
		<text>"So the Federation has abandoned us? What happened to their oath to protect the galaxy? How can they just let these atrocities be commited every day and do nothing? The Federation is worthless..." The civilians jump away.</text>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>"But you ARE a Federation ship, right? That means you can do something! You can tell them about here! But to do that, you'll have to make it out alive. Here, let me see if I can help with that." The civilian ship patches up some of the damage to your hull.</text>
		<damage amount="-15"/>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>"Oh... Well I suppose you're still a good chance for me to get the hell out of here. Please, take me with you, I want to be free from this hell!"</text>
		<crewMember amount="1" shields="1" class="human"/>
	</event>
</eventList>

<!--
		NEUTRAL!!!
	Events that can call a fight
-->
<eventList name="NEBULA_NEUTRAL_HEKTAR">
	<event load="NEBULA_HEKTAR_PATENT"/>
	<event load="NEBULA_HEKTAR_IKEA"/>
	<event load="NEBULA_HEKTAR_REFUEL"/>
	<event load="NEBULA_HEKTAR_POWERPLANT"/>
	<event load="NEBULA_HEKTAR_FANATIC"/>
</eventList>

<event name="NEBULA_HEKTAR_FANATIC" unique="true">
	<text>Looks like a group of civilians, likely victims of Hektar as well, are trapped inside an abandoned warehouse, being guarded by a set of fellow, well armed civilians. Their leader is a bulky human with a bright blue mohawk and the Hektar logo tatooed on both of his arms.</text>
	<environment type="nebula"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>See what's going on.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Before you're allowed to enter the warehouse, you're stopped by the same man you saw earlier. "YOU! YOOUUUUUUUU! ARE YOU LOYAL TO THE ONE, THE ONLY, HEKTAR? DO YOU GROVEL AT THE FEET OF THE GREAT HEKTAR CLAN? YES OR NO?"</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>YES!!!</text>
				<event>
					<text>"YEEEEESSSSS! YEEEEEEESSSSS! ONE OF US, ONE OF US, ONE OF US!!! WOOOOOOOO!" This guy is obviously a massive nutjob and probably has Stockholm syndrome of some sort, but he seems to welcome you amongst his ranks and leads you inside the building where the civilians are trapped.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event>
							<text>"These are the heretics whom I have captured, and shall SACRIFICE IN THE NAME OF HEKTAR! They actually want to LEAVE! There shall be no LEAVING this place. We must stay, and dedicate our lives and our wallets to HEKTAR!"</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>These guys have to be stopped!</text>
								<event>
									<text>Once it becomes clear you've turned on them, the burly man calls for one of his guards to attack you!</text>
									<boarders min="2" max="3" class="human"/>
									<ship load="SHIP_HEKTAR_FANATIC" hostile="true"/>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Continue...</text>
										<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Nod your head and get the hell out.</text>
								<event/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>No.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"THEN BEGONE, SCUM!" The man slams the door to the warehouse on you, locking you out.</text>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore the warehouse.</text>
		<event>
			<text>This looks like chaos, the kind of chaos you don't want to be a part of. You distance yourself from the crazed civilians.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Check the storage.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="NEBULA_HEKTAR_POWERPLANT" unique="true">
	<text>This beacon appears to be covered in an ion storm. However, the lightning here appears to be striking in unusual patterns. An Orchid ship is nearby as well, observing the clouds.</text>
	<environment type="storm"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Hail the Orchids.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Oh, hello. I am professor Ithen, a nebula biologist. You wouldn't believe the kinds of strange creatures these nebulas host! Unfortunately, it looks like Hektar's power generating facilities are manufacturing synthetic ion storms, which is very deadly for these creatures! I've already found 3 or so dead space whales, and this cannot be allowed to continue! Could you try and talk to the manager of the nearby powerplant?"</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Visit the powerplant.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Looks like the facility in question has several massive tesla coils protruding from it, feeding off of the storm. The manager of the facility doesn't seem too receptive to the Orchid's message. "Bah, who caresss about ssssome ssstupid whale. Anaerobesss are lame! Just breathe oxygen, you losssersss."</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Attack the facility!</text>
						<event>
							<text>If this guy won't listen to logic, then he'll have to listen to the sound of your guns!</text>
							<ship load="SHIP_HEKTAR_POWERPLANT_HEKTAR" hostile="true"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Help out the facility and attack the Orchids.</text>
						<event>
							<text>These Orchids are just being nosy, getting involved in business that doesn't concern them. Best you take them out.</text>
							<ship load="SHIP_HEKTAR_POWERPLANT_ORCHIDS" hostile="true"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event load="MORALITY_UPDATE_ORCHID_FIGHT"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Give up.</text>
						<event>
							<text>You return to the Orchid and explain it didn't work. He seems disappointed in your lack of dedication, but thanks you for trying anyways and offers you a small reward.</text>
							<autoReward level="LOW">scrap_only</autoReward>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_ORCHID">
						<text>(Orchid Crew) Explain the importance of not harming ecosystems, regardless of where or what they are.</text>
						<event>
							<text>Your Orchid's speech only seems to confuse the Slug. "I don't underssstand a damn word you jussst sssaid, but it sssure wasss annoying asss hell. If you're sssaying there'sss more weirdosss like you that're going to bug me about thissss, then I'll ssstop jussst to shut you up."</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Return to Ithen.</text>
								<event>
									<text>"Marvelous work! I cannot thank you enough. I guess my work here is done. Unfortunately, I'm kind of stuck here. You know, massive debt and all that. Mind helping escort me out of this place?"</text>
									<crewMember amount="1" class="orchid">Ithen</crewMember>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Refuse.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ion storms suck, just leave.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You don't want to linger any longer than you have to in an ion storm. These Orchids can keep doing whatever it is they're doing, you're out of here.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Check the storage.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="NEBULA_HEKTAR_REFUEL" unique="true">
	<text>Looks like, curiously, a Hektar station is nearby, offering free refuelings to passing ships. Could it be that these Slugs aren't greedy like all the rest of this sector?</text>
	<environment type="nebula"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_HEKTAR_STATION" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Dock.</text>
		<event>
			<text>To your utter shock, the station welcomes you in and actually refuels your ship! You lean back in comfort, impressed by these Slugs.</text>
			<autoReward level="HIGH">fuel_only</autoReward>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event>
					<text>As you attempt to leave, you're stopped by the Slugs. "Sssorry cussstomer, but you can't leave! You appear to be in debt to Hektar Indussstriesss, and thusss the free dissscount on thisss fuel hassss been rendered void. Assss such, your price now totalssss to around... all of your ssscrap. Pay up."</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Hell no!</text>
						<event>
							<text>You aren't paying them all of your scrap! You'll have to fight your way out now.</text>
							<ship hostile="true"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Pay them all of the scrap you have.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"Come again!" The Slugs wave you off as you fly away, empty pocketed.</text>
							<item_modify steal="true">
								<item type="scrap" min="-999999" max="-999999"/>
							</item_modify>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_VARIANT_BILLY">
						<text>(Billy) "There isssn't a debt anymore, moronssss."</text>
						<event>
							<text>The employees are shocked to see their CEO aboard your vessel. Once Billy is done reprimanding each staff member individualy, you're cleared to go, and are even offered supplies to make up for the "misssunderssstanding".</text>
							<autoReward level="MED">stuff</autoReward>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="engines" lvl="5">
						<text>(Upg. Engines) Hightail it out of there.</text>
						<event>
							<text>You power up your engines and fly away as fast as possible before the Slugs can even react.</text>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="cloaking" lvl="2">
						<text>(Upg. Cloaking) Cloak and sneak away.</text>
						<event>
							<text>You activate your cloaking system and sneak away from the Slugs.</text>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore the station.</text>
		<event>
			<text>No - this must be a trap. No way these guys are any different from the rest of this sector's inhabitants.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Check the storage.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="NEBULA_HEKTAR_IKEA" unique="true">
	<text>A brightly colored civilian ship is stealthily hidden away near a Hektar platform. When you jump in, they seem to spot you quickly and hail.</text>
	<environment type="nebula"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Hello, Federation captain! I am Astrid Kamprad. For many centuries my family has run a prominent furniture corporation in the Galactic Union, but to my horror when I heard news of Hektar, it would appear my family business's core idea has been shamelessly STOLEN by these devilish Hektars. I am certain there is proof of this locked away in a vault in that platform, but I need your help to get it. A station protects the vault, and I need it destroyed!"</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Agree.</text>
				<event>
					<text>As Astrid claimed, to access the platform, you'll first have to take out a Hektar station. Get ready to fight!</text>
					<ship load="SHIP_HEKTAR_IKEA" hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Decline.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="HEKTAR_IKEA_WIN">
    <text>"You've done it captain! Now, let's crack open this vault and find the truth!"</text>
    <choice hidden="true">
        <text>Open the vault.</text>
        <event>
            <text>After a little bit of a struggle, you get the vault open and enter. Inside are various documents and messily written letters, signed by a "Carle Hektar". Astrid explains Carle was the original founder of Hektar many many years ago before the Federation had even been founded.</text>
            <choice hidden="true">
                <text>Continue...</text>
                <event>
                    <text>At last, Astrid finds what he is looking for. A journal entry, which reads; "Today I visited Earth! I've always loved human culture. On my trip, I met this lovely gentleman who owned a furniture corporation. When I told him Slugs rarely furnished their homes, he was shocked! And then, the lad gave me a most brillant idea I'll never forget. He said I should start a furniture company myself! I owe everything to that man."</text>
                    <choice hidden="true">
                        <text>Continue...</text>
                        <event>
                            <text>Astrid seems at a loss for words. "I... uh..." He clears his throat. "Well, I guess I better pay you for your help. I'm going to go cry in a bathroom now."</text>
                            <weapon name="RANDOM"/>
                        </event>
                    </choice>
                </event>
            </choice>
        </event>
    </choice>
</event>

<event name="NEBULA_HEKTAR_PATENT" unique="true">
	<text>A Hektar ship and a Zoltan vessel look to be in some kind of standoff, arguing over trademarks. You can't seem to gleam any more insight on their argument, other than it seems very heated.</text>
	<environment type="nebula"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Intervene and help the Hektar ship.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You engage the Zoltan ship.</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_HEKTAR_PATENT_ZOLTAN" hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Intervene and help the Zoltan.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You engage the Hektar ship.</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_HEKTAR_PATENT_HEKTAR" hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore the conflict.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You quickly fly away. Soon, both ships open fire at each other.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Check the storage.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
		HOSTILE!!!
	Events that can call a fight
-->
<eventList name="NEBULA_HOSTILE_HEKTAR">
	<event load="NEBULA_ENCOUNTER_HEKTAR"/>
</eventList>

<event name="NEBULA_ENCOUNTER_HEKTAR">
	<environment type="nebula"/>
	<text load="TEXT_ENCOUNTER_HEKTAR"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_HEKTAR_FIGHT" hostile="true"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_ENCOUNTER_HEKTAR">
	<text>As you're starting to notice, the most prominent trait of all Hektar employees is their extreme greed. One particularly greedy Slug nearby looks to be wanting a piece of your ship and attacks!</text>
	<text>A Hektar ship approaches, weighing their odds of success against you. Apparently they rank them high, because the ship attacks!</text>
	<text>"Let'sss both be real. You're never going to pay off that debt of yoursss. Sssso, why not jussst let usss kill you and sssteal your ssstuff, and then your sssuffering can be over!"</text>
	<text>A Hektar ship is nearby. Their captain hails you, waving cheerfully. Suddenly, a timer goes off. "Ah crap, my break issss over. Sssorry man, now I gotta do my job and rob you."</text>
	<text>"Did you know I get a bonussss for every sssship I rob? Not from Hektar, but from money I get ssselling your garbage. Now, give me your cargo!"</text>
</textList>

<!--
		SYLVAN'S HOME
-->
<event name="NEBULA_SYLVANHOME">
	<loadEventList first="true" generate="true" default="NEBULA_SYLVANHOME_REAL">
		<event name="NEBULA_SYLVANHOME_QUARANTINE" req="quarantine" lvl="1"/>
		<event name="NEBULA_SYLVANHOME_HER" req="prof_opened_nexus" lvl="1"/>
	</loadEventList>
</event>
<event name="NEBULA_SYLVANHOME_QUARANTINE">
	<preventQuest/>
	<text>The clouds here are thicker than usual, and a violent storm rages on. You wander aimlessly hoping to find something, and eventually come across a very small Hektar pod drifting nearby, maybe only as large as two rooms. Its exterior is charred and the door busted open, and inspecting inside of it you find nothing but a small business card with the header "C.E.L." - The phone number on the back is impossible to call.</text>
	<environment type="storm"/>
</event>
<event name="NEBULA_SYLVANHOME_REAL">
	<preventQuest/>
	<text>The clouds here are thicker than usual, and a violent storm rages on. You wander aimlessly hoping to find something, and eventually come across a very small Hektar pod drifting nearby, maybe only as large as two rooms. Your scans cannot penetrate its shell no matter what you do.</text>
	<environment type="storm"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Approach.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You move closer to the pod and find it is protected by a metal door with a passcode. On the bottom is written simply "property of S.H." There's no possible way to break it open without jeopardizing the structural integrity, and the security system is so advanced you doubt you could break through before the Rebel fleet arrived. Whoever built this clearly doesn't want people messing with their stuff.</text>
			<choice hidden="true" req="unique_obyn">
				<text>(Obyn) Obyn knows how to open the door.</text>
				<event load="NEBULA_SYLVANHOME_OPEN_OBYN"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="unique_anurak">
				<text>(Anurak) Anurak knows how to open the door.</text>
				<event load="NEBULA_SYLVANHOME_OPEN_ANURAK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="unique_sylvan">
				<text>(Sylvan) Sylvan seems to have something to say.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Sylvan glances at the pod for a moment but stops himself. "Heh, nevermind sssstranger. My bad. Ignore my rambling..."</text>
					<choice hidden="true" req="unique_obyn">
						<text>(Obyn) Obyn knows how to open the door.</text>
						<event load="NEBULA_SYLVANHOME_OPEN_OBYN"/>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="unique_anurak">
						<text>(Anurak) Anurak knows how to open the door.</text>
						<event load="NEBULA_SYLVANHOME_OPEN_ANURAK"/>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Guess there's nothing to be done.</text>
						<event>
							<text>This is a very strange sighting, and you can't help but wonder if there's something of great significance here. However, today no mystery will be solved. Not here at least.</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Check the storage.</text>
								<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Do nothing.</text>
								<event/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Guess there's nothing to be done.</text>
				<event>
					<text>This is a very strange sighting, and you can't help but wonder if there's something of great significance here. However, today no mystery will be solved. Not here at least.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Check the storage.</text>
						<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Do nothing.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Guess there's nothing to be done.</text>
		<event>
			<text>This is a very strange sighting, and you can't help but wonder if there's something of great significance here. However, today no mystery will be solved. Not here at least.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Check the storage.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="NEBULA_SYLVANHOME_HER">
	<preventQuest/>
	<text>The clouds here are thicker than usual, and a violent storm rages on. You wander aimlessly hoping to find something, and eventually come across a very small Hektar pod drifting nearby, maybe only as large as two rooms. Your scans cannot penetrate its shell no matter what you do.</text>
	<environment type="storm"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Approach.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You move closer to the pod and find it is protected by a metal door with a passcode. On the bottom is written simply "property of S.H." There's no possible way to break it open without jeopardizing the structural integrity, and the security system is so advanced you doubt you could break through before the Rebel fleet arrived. Whoever built this clearly doesn't want people messing with their stuff.
			
			Curiously, a note seems to have been written underneath the passcode. It seems to move with you, always following your gaze, with a faint red and blue glimmer. It reads, "Password: #!XX_sLuggyB0y_789 - You're welcome :)" You aren't sure who left this note, or why it looks the way it does, but it should allow you entry.</text>
			<choice hidden="true" req="unique_obyn">
				<text>(Obyn) Obyn knows how to open the door.</text>
				<event load="NEBULA_SYLVANHOME_OPEN_OBYN"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="unique_anurak">
				<text>(Anurak) Anurak knows how to open the door.</text>
				<event load="NEBULA_SYLVANHOME_OPEN_ANURAK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Use the password to open the door.</text>
				<event load="NEBULA_SYLVANHOME_OPEN_PASSWORD"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="unique_sylvan">
				<text>(Sylvan) Sylvan seems to have something to say.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Sylvan glances at the pod for a moment but stops himself. "Heh, nevermind sssstranger. My bad. Ignore my rambling..."</text>
					<choice hidden="true" req="unique_obyn">
						<text>(Obyn) Obyn knows how to open the door.</text>
						<event load="NEBULA_SYLVANHOME_OPEN_OBYN"/>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="unique_anurak">
						<text>(Anurak) Anurak knows how to open the door.</text>
						<event load="NEBULA_SYLVANHOME_OPEN_ANURAK"/>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Use the password to open the door.</text>
						<event load="NEBULA_SYLVANHOME_OPEN_PASSWORD"/>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Ignore the door and leave.</text>
						<event>
							<text>This is a very strange sighting, and you can't help but wonder if there's something of great significance here. However, today no mystery will be solved. Not here at least.</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Check the storage.</text>
								<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Do nothing.</text>
								<event/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Ignore the door and leave.</text>
				<event>
					<text>This is a very strange sighting, and you can't help but wonder if there's something of great significance here. However, today no mystery will be solved. Not here at least.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Check the storage.</text>
						<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Do nothing.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore the pod and leave.</text>
		<event>
			<text>This is a very strange sighting, and you can't help but wonder if there's something of great significance here. However, today no mystery will be solved. Not here at least.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Check the storage.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="NEBULA_SYLVANHOME_OPEN_OBYN">
	<text>Obyn brushes past you and walks up to the passcode. He types in a string of numbers you don't recognize and to your surprise the pod opens! You glance at Obyn, who shrugs. "S.H.; those are Sylvan's initials. He has a bad habit of using the same password for everything, so I figured I'd try it..."</text>
	<metaVariable name="prof_opened_nexus" op="set" val="1"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Enter.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The interior of the pod is decorated by all kinds of oddities. A messy bed with dark purple sheets conceals an array of stuffed animals with obvious wear from years of friendship. Much of the decorations seem strangely childish, with a few outliers that seem to have been added after the fact. Obyn kneels and picks up a small trinket, a necklace with a symbol of the great eye, engraved with the name 'Anurak'.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>What's that?</text>
				<event>
					<text>Obyn places the necklace back where it was carefully. "A gift, from an old friend of ours." He stops, and looks around the room. "I know what this place is. Sylvan told me about it. Whenever he needed to escape from his parents and later on his brother, he would come here. This became his home away from home: he would continue to visit from time to time. After our showdown with the EHG, he brought me here once." Obyn glances at the bed and a strange hazmat suit tailored for a Slug next to it. "Hmph. Good memories."</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event>
							<text>You walk around the room, looking for nothing in particular, until you find a compartment with a map in it, showing a star system unlike anything you've ever seen. All kinds of strange labels are scattered around, and a single sticky-note carries coordinates which you mark on your own map. Nothing else here seems to be of any use to you, so you do one more once over and close the door behind you.</text>
							<quest event="NEXUS_PORTAL"/>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="NEBULA_SYLVANHOME_OPEN_ANURAK">
	<text>Anurak rambles on a bit about what he thinks this is and how he knows how to open it. "You see Shellskenbry, the initials S.H., I believe they are short for Sylvan Hektar! Sylvan being the traveling merchant - because he's a merchant who uh.. travels. And well, I knew Sylvan back in the day. He took refuge in my monastery while on the run from the EHG (that's the Exotic Hunter's Guild, Shellskenbry. I know, these acronyms are so confusing!) and set me up with a nice little spot on some lizard planet in the Ministry Capital! And while I was with that unusually nice Slug I learned his password! Apparently according to his boyfriend, he always uses the same one for everything! They were always arguing about it. They were arguing about everything, actually. Ah, young love. If only I was young..."
	
You motion for Anurak to hurry up and try the password. He does, and to your surprise it actually works!</text>
	<metaVariable name="prof_opened_nexus" op="set" val="1"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Enter.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The interior of the pod is decorated by all kinds of oddities. A messy bed with dark purple sheets conceals an array of stuffed animals with obvious wear from years of friendship. Much of the decorations seem strangely childish, with a few outliers that seem to have been added after the fact. Anurak looks around with a mixture of wonder, eventually eying a necklace with a symbol of the great eye, engraved with his name. "Sylvan kept this? Why, it's been years! I didn't think our friendship meant that much to him!"</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>What is this place?</text>
				<event>
					<text>Anurak spins around, trying to locate himself in the space time continuum. "Well, Shellskenbry, my memory isn't very good. I think so much cloning during my years as a Duskbringer have worn down my memory processor. But from what I can remember, I think Sylvan told us about this place once. It was a sanctuary, away from his parents and his brother! Terribly sad upbringing, it always pained me to hear about it. The poor Slug, he was so nice and yet so troubled... This place was his home away from home, or something like that! I think he wanted to bring his boyfriend here, but I'm no third wheel. Their secrets are my secrets too, so don't ask! I keep tight lips, nothing gets out." Anurak lifts a finger to his lips and pretends to seal a zipper with them.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event>
							<text>You walk around the room, looking for nothing in particular, until you find a compartment with a map in it, showing a star system unlike anything you've ever seen. All kinds of strange labels are scattered around, and a single sticky-note carries coordinates which you mark on your own map. Nothing else here seems to be of any use to you, so you do one more once over and close the door behind you.</text>
							<quest event="NEXUS_PORTAL"/>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="NEBULA_SYLVANHOME_OPEN_PASSWORD">
	<text>You punch the code into the keypad and the door buzzes a green light.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Enter.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The interior of the pod is decorated by all kinds of oddities. A messy bed with dark purple sheets conceals an array of stuffed animals with obvious wear from years of friendship. Much of the decorations seem strangely childish, with a few outliers that seem to have been added after the fact. You aren't quite sure what this place it, but based on the surroundings it seems like it belongs to Sylvan.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event>
					<text>You walk around the room, looking for nothing in particular, until you find a compartment with a map in it, showing a star system unlike anything you've ever seen. All kinds of strange labels are scattered around, and a single sticky-note carries coordinates which you mark on your own map. Nothing else here seems to be of any use to you, so you do one more once over and close the door behind you.</text>
					<quest event="NEXUS_PORTAL"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
</FTL>