<FTL>
<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					MINISTRY SECTOR
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					EXIT BEACON
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->
<event name="FINISH_BEACON_ZOLTAN">
	<text id="finish_beacon"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Explore.</text>
		<event load="EXIT_FILLER_LIST"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
		<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Do nothing.</text>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					ITEM EVENTS ()
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<eventList name="ITEMS_ZOLTAN_MV">
	<event load="ZOLTAN_FASCISM"/>
	<event load="ZOLTAN_FREE_AUGMENT_MV"/>
	<event load="ZOLTAN_FREE_MAP_MV"/>
	<event load="ZOLTAN_TRADE_HUB_MV"/>
	<event load="ZOLTAN_FIGHTER_MONK"/>
	<event load="ZOLTAN_ODD_MOON_MV"/>
</eventList>

<event name="ZOLTAN_FASCISM" unique="true">
	<text>A few smouldering wrecks nearby are being observed by a Zoltan vessel, whose captain is speaking on open comms. At first you think he's blindly talking to himself until you realize he's speaking to you. "Damn Duskbringers, so much pointless bloodshed. This is all the fault of humanity, infecting this galaxy with their diseased ideologies like fascism. If it wasn't for the Rebellion, never would such sinister thoughts have reached our peaceful race."</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>That... doesn't sound right.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Oh but it is! It's an ideology born out of the stomach, used by jingoists and fake patriots alike to line pockets with war-time economy and supress free speech. It is a mockery of intellectualism and a cog in the eugenics machine." This guy isn't wrong, but the way he speaks makes you realize he may be a bit delusional.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>If you hate fascists, maybe you can help us with the Rebels?</text>
				<event>
					<text>The Zoltan mumbles something to himself. "Fighting the Rebellion is a futile effort. The disease of fascism has already infected the galaxy, and there's no cure. But you seem young and hopeful. Perhaps a new generation of right-minded individuals can rectify the course of our politics." The Zoltan sends some equipment your way. "I've been holding onto this since the Civil War. I'm not a soldier anymore, I don't need it. Take it, and send the fascists packing!"</text>
					<weapon name="RANDOM"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_MEDICAL">
				<text>(Medical Crew) Examine his mental state.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Your crew starts asking the Zoltan various questions, trying to probe for tell-tale signs of mental instability. The conclusion seems to be he's experiencing early cognitive decay, a rare malfunction in Zoltan chassis that can cause erratic thought patterns and irregular speech. However, trying to convince him to find a hospital only seems to confuse him more. Strangely, he thinks you're asking him for a reactor tune-up, and agrees.</text>
					<upgrade amount="1" system="reactor"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Leave the Zoltan alone.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice req="LIST_CREW_HUMAN" hidden="true">
		<text>(Human Crew) Apologise for being solely responsible for inventing fascism.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Zoltan nods. "Humanity is a species of nothing but pestilent ideas, fermented with political turmoil and selfishness. You have forever ruined this galaxy with partisan concepts like 'democracy' and 'feminism'. It disgusts me. We were once a pure race, until we came into contact with yours. It is known that humans are a warlike race who can only be controlled by manipulating their even greater greed. Take this, and never return." It's clear this guy is delusional, but you don't mind free scrap.</text>
			<autoReward level="HIGH">scrap_only</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="ZOLTAN_FREE_AUGMENT_MV" unique="true">
	<text>A Zoltan academy sits docked just outside the beacon perimeter. They're happy to show you the fruits of their labor, and offer something to take home with you.</text>
	<autoReward level="LOW">augment</autoReward>
	<choice>
		<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
		<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Do nothing.</text>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="ZOLTAN_FREE_MAP_MV" unique="true">
	<text>The Zoltans stationed near this beacon are happy to receive you. As they give you the formal tour of their ship you spy some local star charts and mentally log the details.</text>
	<reveal_map/>
	<ship load="SHIP_ZOLTAN_GENERIC" hostile="false"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
		<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Do nothing.</text>
		<event/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Attack them.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Their crew is astonished by your sudden attitude shift, but they won't back down from this aggression.</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="MORALITY_UPDATE_ZOLTAN_FIGHT"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="ZOLTAN_TRADE_HUB_MV" unique="true">
	<text>You come to a Zoltan trade and supply hub - everything the weary traveler needs, provided they have the right documentation.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Try to talk your way in.</text>
		<event load="ZOLTAN_TRADE_HUB_MV_TALK"/>
	</choice>	
	<choice hidden="true" req="teleporter" lvl="1">
		<text>(Teleporter) Beam directly to the civilian deck.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You re-materialize in a dark corner of the main concourse and are able to conduct your investigations in peace.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="ZOLTAN_TRADE_HUB_MV_SUCCESS"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="LOCKED_GLOBAL_TELEPORT">
		<text>(Central Teleport) Beam directly to the civilian deck.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You re-materialize in a dark corner of the main concourse and are able to conduct your investigations in peace.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="ZOLTAN_TRADE_HUB_MV_SUCCESS"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice req="LIST_CREW_ZOLTAN_CAPITAL">
		<text>(Ministry Crew) Present official documentation and pay the entry fee.</text>
		<event>
			<text>They scan ID that declares your crewmember an official citizen, collect their fee, and let you pass.</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="-10" max="-10"/>
			</item_modify> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="ZOLTAN_TRADE_HUB_MV_SUCCESS"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Leave.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You don't have the papers - well, the neuro-laced identity bracelets - to get in, so best not to try.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="ZOLTAN_TRADE_HUB_MV_TALK">
	<event>
		<text>They don't see many of your species in these parts, and you stick out like a Casvagarian Sea Slug in a Plutonian Shrimp Stew. You make it back to the ship with a gang of Zoltan guards in tow!</text>
		<ship load="SHIP_ZOLTAN_FIGHT" hostile="true"/>
		<boarders min="2" max="4" class="zoltan"/>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>You pose as traders and succeed in bypassing airlock security - however, it's only a matter of time before someone realizes your ID cards are counterfeit!</text>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="ZOLTAN_TRADE_HUB_MV_SUCCESS"/>
		</choice>
	</event>
</eventList>
<eventList name="ZOLTAN_TRADE_HUB_MV_SUCCESS">
	<event>
		<text>You head into a ship supply store. It is a well-equipped, self-service affair. An order is dialled into a terminal, scrap is deposited, and the item is dispatched from a nearby chute.</text>
		<store>STORE_ZOLTAN</store>
	</event>
</eventList>

<event name="ZOLTAN_FIGHTER_MONK" unique="true">
    <text>It's risky business being a slaver in Zoltan space, but it appears one soul is daring enough to run his trade here. Not exactly commendable, but still a rare sight.</text>
    <ship load="SHIP_SLAVER_MINISTRY" hostile="false"/>
    <choice hidden="true">
        <text>See who they might have on sale.</text>
        <event>
            <text>"Feds, eh? You look like a fellow who could use a fighter with a little extra bit'a... umph, if you get me. For quite the modest fee, how does a masterful Zoltan warrior sounds to join the ranks of your crew?"</text>
            <choice>
                <text>Purchase the Zoltan.</text>
                <event>
                    <text>You hand over your scrap to the slavers, but they don't return with the slave promised. You begin to suspect something might be wrong, until they inevitably stumble out carting with them a Zoltan wrapped in a brown robe.</text>
                    <item_modify>
                        <item type="scrap" min="-35" max="-35"/>
                    </item_modify>
                    <choice hidden="true">
                        <text>Continue...</text>
                        <event>
                            <text>They violently toss the Zoltan onto your floor and apologize, then walk off. You inspect the Zoltan, only to realize they're a pacifist monk! The Zoltan explains their situation, "I was once a trained Zoltan warrior, but I eventually saw the light and joined the Monks, but not long after I was abducted by these men. You have saved me from slavery, and I shall now serve you. As ironic as that sounds."</text>
                            <crewMember amount="1" combat="2" class="zoltan_monk"/>
                            <choice hidden="true">
                                <text>Continue...</text>
                                <event load="REPUTATION_UPDATE_SLAVER"/>
                            </choice>
                        </event>
                    </choice>
                </event>
            </choice>
            <choice hidden="true">
                <text>Decline.</text>
                <event/>
            </choice>
        </event>
    </choice>
    <choice hidden="true">
        <text>Attack the slavers.</text>
        <event>
            <text>The Ministry would not appreciate the presence of slavers within their territory. You arm your weapons and approach with hostile intent.</text>
            <ship hostile="true"/>
            <choice hidden="true">
                <text>Continue...</text>
                <event load="REPUTATION_DECREASE_SLAVER_COMBAT"/>
            </choice>
        </event>
    </choice>
    <choice hidden="true">
        <text>Ignore them.</text>
        <event>
            <text>Eventually, the slavers jump away. They surely can't afford to set up their business without getting caught by the Ministry's enforcers.</text>
            <choice>
                <text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
                <event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
            </choice>
            <choice>
                <text>Do nothing.</text>
                <event/>
            </choice>
        </event>
    </choice>
</event>
<eventList name="ZOLTAN_FIGHTER_MONK_RESCUE_ATTEMPT">
    <event>
        <text>As you investigate their hold, you realize that the Zoltans are freshly dead - it appears that they must have perished in the fighting. It doesn't take much imagination to find out why - the conditions of their hold are nearly inhospitable. Looks like there's nothing more to gain here.</text>
        <choice hidden="true">
            <text>Continue...</text>
            <event load="MORALITY_REMOVE_ZOLTAN"/>
        </choice>
    </event>
    <event>
        <text>You search their ship and discover the slave hold. The slaves are barely hanging on - it appears that the conditions of the hold are surprisingly careless for Slavers. Nonetheless, you are able to rescue them. Among the survivors, a Zoltan monk bows to you. "I thank you for rescuing us from the slavers. I used to be a fighter like you until I found my faith with the Illesctrian order."</text>
        <crewMember amount="1" combat="2" class="zoltan_monk"/>
        <choice hidden="true">
            <text>Continue...</text>
            <event load="MORALITY_REMOVE_ZOLTAN"/>
        </choice>
    </event>
</eventList>
	
<event name="ZOLTAN_ODD_MOON_MV" unique="true">
	<text>Something strikes you as odd about a moon in the distance.</text>
	<img planet="PLANET_MOONS"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Check it out.</text>
		<event load="ZOLTAN_ODD_MOON_MV_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Leave it be.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You try not to fixate on the moon in the aft scanner as you set the coordinates for the next jump.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="DRONE_CONTROL_BOARDING">
		<text>(Boarding Drone) Send a drone to probe the surface.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Initial scans indicate a network of caves not far underground. You launch a boarding drone and it breaks through the surface into the cavern below.</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="drones" min="-1" max="-1"/>
			</item_modify>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event>
					<text>Your drone discovers a vast cave network and evidence of excavation. Buried deep below you find a Zoltan scientist, still hard at work. He tells you that all his colleagues are long dead. You decide not to ask questions and offer to let him join your crew.</text>
					<crewMember amount="1" class="zoltan"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="ZOLTAN_ODD_MOON_MV_CHECK">
	<event>
		<text>A closer inspection reveals signs of habitation on the surface, but nothing else particularly interesting.</text>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>Sending a shuttle to explore a beckoning cave system you discover signs of a battle - and a still-functioning weapon!</text>
		<autoReward level="LOW">weapon</autoReward>	
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>A deep scan of the surface reveals a cave system that runs for miles, and what looks like a scrap heap left over from some heavy-duty construction.</text>
		<autoReward level="MED">scrap_only</autoReward>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>It looks as if a team could break through the fragile layer of the moon's surface into a hidden cavern.</text>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Attempt to detonate an explosive to break through the surface. [-1}]</text>
			<event load="ZOLTAN_ODD_MOON_MV_EXPLOSION"/>
		</choice>
		<choice>
			<text>Explosives are too valuable to waste on excavation work. Let's get out of here.</text>
			<event/>
		</choice>
	</event>
</eventList>
<eventList name="ZOLTAN_ODD_MOON_MV_EXPLOSION">
	<event>
		<text>A portion of the surface layer is destroyed in an impressive display, revealing miles of caves. You don't have time to fully explore them, but you find some remains of an old subterranean base that could be useful.</text>
		<item_modify>
			<item type="missiles" min="-1" max="-1"/>
		</item_modify>
		<autoReward level="RANDOM">scrap_only</autoReward>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>The explosives are set remotely, but the detonation achieves nothing. What a waste.</text>
		<item_modify>
			<item type="missiles" min="-1" max="-1"/>
		</item_modify>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>Your explosives reveal the 'cave' is actually a secret base, located in a network of bunkers just under the surface. Everyone inside is dead; some Mantis clearly came through here recently. It looks like the Zoltans were researching advanced ship weaponry. You take one of their better examples back to your ship.</text>
		<autoReward level="RANDOM">weapon</autoReward>
		<item_modify>
			<item type="missiles" min="-1" max="-1"/>
		</item_modify>
	</event>
</eventList>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					NEUTRAL EVENTS ()
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->	
<eventList name="NEUTRAL_ZOLTAN_MV">
	<event load="ZOLTAN_CREW_SCAN_MV"/>
	<event load="ZOLTAN_SCIENCE_DOCK_MV"/>
	<event load="ZOLTAN_LIFERAFT_MV"/>
	<event load="ZOLTAN_TOURIST"/>
	<event load="ZOLTAN_TICKET"/>
	
	<event load="DUSK_YOUNG"/>
</eventList>

<event name="ZOLTAN_CREW_SCAN_MV" unique="true">
	<text>You arrive at a Zoltan security checkpoint set up in a perimeter around the beacon. "Travelling vessel, you will submit to crew profiling to identify fugitives of the empire."</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>You don't have time for this nonsense. Attack!</text>
		<event>
			<text>Expecting resistance, their Energy Shield is raised and ready for combat.</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_ZOLTAN_CREW_SCAN" hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="MORALITY_UPDATE_ZOLTAN_FIGHT"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CHECK_ANY_CREW" lvl="1" blue="false">
		<text>Submit to profiling.</text>
		<event load="ZOLTAN_CREW_SCAN_LIST_MV"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CHECK_ANY_CREW" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
		<text>Submit to profiling.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The process turns out to be really quick, considering you have no one aboard. So quick infact, that you still have time to do something onboard.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_SLUG">
		<text>(Slug Crew) Have your Slug talk them into letting you go.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You give the guards permission to dock with the ship, but before they come on board your crewmember slowly advances to meet them. As far as you can tell no words were exchanged, but the guards offer you some supplies and say the ship checks out. Best to not ask questions.</text>
			<autoReward level="MED">fuel_only</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_ZOLTAN_CAPITAL">
		<text>(Zoltan Crew) Have your Zoltan talk them into letting you go.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Your Zoltan talks to the guards in great lengths about the majesty of the Zoltan empire. Convinced that you're nothing more than do-gooders, they let you past.</text>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="mind">
		<text>(Mind Control) Make the guards believe they have already checked your crew today.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The captain of the guard appears on the vid screen "Back so soon friend! Well, no need to waste your time further. Here, take these spare fuel canisters and get on with your mission." Your ship is cleared to pass.</text>
			<autoReward level="MED">fuel_only</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>		
	<choice hidden="true" req="BLUELIST_WEAPONS_MIND_CONTROL">
		<text>(Mind Control Weapon) Make the guards believe they have already checked your crew today.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The captain of the guard appears on the vid screen "Back so soon friend! Well, no need to waste your time further. Here, take these spare fuel canisters and get on with your mission." Your ship is cleared to pass.</text>
			<autoReward level="MED">fuel_only</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>		
</event>
<eventList name="ZOLTAN_CREW_SCAN_LIST_MV">
	<event>
		<text>The Zoltan security staff board your ship and scan the crew's faces into a computer. After a few tense moments of uncertainty they allow your ship to pass.</text>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>The Zoltan security staff board your ship and begin scanning the crew's faces into a computer. Suddenly alarms go off and the Zoltans leap on one of your crew! "This person is wanted on five charges of Utter Villainy! Surrender them to us!"</text>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Give up your crewmember.</text>
			<event>
				<text>It's a tough call, but Zoltan law holds sway here. Besides, that one always seemed a bit shifty.</text>
				<removeCrew>
					<clone>false</clone>
					<text>Unfortunately your crewmember was taken away unharmed so your Clone Bay was unable to retrieve them.</text>
				</removeCrew>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Refuse and fight.</text>
			<event>
				<text>You're not going to leave anyone behind. You pull away from the station with the enemy guards on board. Unfortunately, they are able to sabotage your weapon system in the chaos. It's time to leave!</text>
				<ship load="SHIP_ZOLTAN_CREW_SCAN" hostile="true"/>
				<boarders min="2" max="4" class="zoltan"/>
				<status type="divide" target="player" system="weapons" amount="2"/>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event load="MORALITY_UPDATE_ZOLTAN_FIGHT"/>
				</choice>
				<choice hidden="true" req="ANTI_VIRUS">
					<text>(Anti-Virus) Restore your weapons.</text>
					<event>
						<text>Your weapon system is restored to full power.</text>
						<status type="clear" target="player" system="weapons" amount="100"/>
						<choice hidden="true">
							<text>Continue...</text>
							<event load="MORALITY_UPDATE_ZOLTAN_FIGHT"/>
						</choice>
					</event>
				</choice>
			</event>
		</choice>
	</event>
</eventList>

<event name="ZOLTAN_SCIENCE_DOCK_MV" unique="true">
	<text>What appears to be a Zoltan science ship requests permission to dock.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Dock with them.</text>
		<event load="ZOLTAN_SCIENCE_DOCK_LIST_MV"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Have them keep their distance.</text>
		<event>
			<text>They leave without a word.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>	
<eventList name="ZOLTAN_SCIENCE_DOCK_LIST_MV">
	<event>
		<text>You allow them to approach, but are caught unaware when they open fire!</text>
		<ship load="SHIP_ZOLTAN_SCIENCE_DOCK" hostile="true"/>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>"We have been studying the relationships between the species and have determined that the 'Federation' still has potential to be a net positive for the galaxy. Please accept this gift to aid your journey."</text>
		<autoReward level="MED">stuff</autoReward>
	</event>
</eventList>

<event name="ZOLTAN_LIFERAFT_MV" unique="true">
	<text>You pick up a Zoltan life raft floating in space. Its inhabitant asks you to retake his ship from the pirates who recently commandeered it. "I'm certain it is clear," he concludes, "that you must not destroy my vessel in the process."</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_ZOLTAN_LIFERAFT" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Engage the pirates.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You focus your fire on the pirates.</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Leave.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You refuse to get his ship back, but still offer to drop him off at the next station. The Zoltan is displeased, but directs you to a nearby starbase just the same.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="ZOLTAN_LIFERAFT_HIRE_MV">
	<event>
		<text>He responds haughtily, "You would presume I would work under your command after such a display of... prowess? No, I must decline."</text>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>He responds defeated, "I suppose I have nowhere else to go without a ship. I accept your offer."</text>
		<item_modify>
			<item type="scrap" min="-40" max="-40"/>
		</item_modify>
		<crewMember amount="1" class="zoltan"/>
	</event>
</eventList>

<event name="ZOLTAN_TOURIST" unique="true">
	<text>It appears a civilian ship is under attack by a Zoltan ship! You aren't sure why, but it looks like they need help.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_ZOLTAN_RESCUE" hostile="false"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Rescue the civilians.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You give the Zoltan ship no choice but to fight you as you fly towards it full speed.</text> 
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="MORALITY_UPDATE_ZOLTAN_FIGHT"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="zoltan_peacekeeper">
		<text>(Peacekeeper Crew) Demand the Zoltans back down.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Your Peacekeeper cites Ministry law C-T-55 from the Ministry codex, saying that they have no right to attack civilian ships without sufficient reason or permission from a higher authority. As no Zoltan, dead or alive, is said to have full knowledge of the entire codex, the other ship has no grounds to deny the existance of said law. They back down and jump away.</text>
			<instantEscape/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="SAVE_CIVILIAN_LIST"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore them.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Eventually the civilians are chased out of range, and you are left alone.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="ZOLTAN_TICKET" unique="true"> <!--technically hostile??? we just need more neutral...-->
	<text>Not long after you jump in a Zoltan Automated vessel hails you. "You are in direct violation of protocol-S36-T by exceeding the weight limit for Cruiser class vehicles in this zone. Your fine equates to: 10 scrap."</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_ZOLTAN_AUTO" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Hell no, fight past the ship.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Hostile actions registered. Preparing to defend."</text> 
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice req="unique_mafan">
		<text>(Mafan) Debate the fine with the Auto.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Protocol-S36-T doesn't apply here, this ship has an MV drive! You'd use an S36-T-MV form to calculate the ship's new weight limits, then add a deduction factor for the personal carrying allotment of each crew member. Then factor in the fee waivers for our sub-category as a science vessel due to my presence..." You're reasonably certain Mafan could go on all day, but a circuit blows somewhere in the Zoltan ship while it tries to follow Mafan's logic, causing the ship to explode violently!</text> 
			<enemyDamage amount="50" system="random" effect="eff"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Whatever, just pay the fine.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Fine has been paid. Have a nice day."</text> 
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="-10" max="-10"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<eventList name="NEUTRAL_ZOLTAN_UNIQUE">
	<event load="ZOLTAN_FREEMANTIS_FRIENDLY"/>
	<event load="ZOLTAN_REVOLT"/>

	<event load="ZOLTAN_CREW_SCAN_MV"/>
	<event load="ZOLTAN_SCIENCE_DOCK_MV"/>
	<event load="ZOLTAN_LIFERAFT_MV"/>
	<event load="ZOLTAN_TOURIST"/>
	<event load="ZOLTAN_TICKET"/>
	
	<event load="DUSK_YOUNG"/>
</eventList>

<event name="ZOLTAN_FREEMANTIS_FRIENDLY" unique="true">
	<text>The Free Mantis and Zoltan don't get along well, so it's concerning to see a Free Mantis ship so far into Zoltan space. A ship from the peacekeeper border police has docked with a massive Free Mantis ship, which can't mean anything good.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_ZOLTAN_FREEMANTIS_FRIENDLY" hostile="false"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Board as well and see what's happening.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You step into the ship only to find a Peacekeeper violently kicking a defenseless Free Mantis warlord on the ground, who is desperately screaming "Stop, stop! I not wanting violence, only friendlyness!", but the Zoltan won't listen.</text> 
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Pull the Zoltan off of the Free Mantis.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You grab at the Zoltan, pulling them away from the Free Mantis. They shove you away, shouting "What the hell are you doing? All your precious Federation can do now is interfere with foreign matters, isn't that so? I'll put you in your god damn place!" The Zoltan gives orders for his men to attack!</text>
					<ship hostile="true"/> 
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="MORALITY_UPDATE_ZOLTAN_FIGHT"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Try to reason with the Zoltan.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You try to reason with the Peacekeeper, but it only infuriates them further. "The Federation should know their place, instead of always interfering with foreign matters. Maybe the Duskbringers are right, and all of you filth deserve to die." The Peacekeeper gives orders for his men to attack!</text>
					<ship hostile="true"/> 
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="MORALITY_UPDATE_ZOLTAN_FIGHT"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_ZOLTAN_CAPITAL">
				<text>(Ministry Crew) Have your Zoltan reason with them.</text>
				<event load="ZOLTAN_FREEMANTIS_FRIENDLY_REASON_ZOLTAN"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="ZOLTAN_DELETER">
				<text>(Zoltan Deleter) Begone.</text>
				<event>
					<text>It only takes a single shot to erase the peace-keeper from existence. You help the Free Mantis to their feet. "Thanking you very much Federation, we come here only make friends, but Zoltan not trust us. Me coming with you, much friendlier."</text>
					<crewMember amount="1" class="mantis_warlord"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore the ships.</text>
		<event>
			<text>There's no way you're messing with the Zoltan border police in the Zoltan Capital.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="ZOLTAN_FREEMANTIS_FRIENDLY_REASON_ZOLTAN">
	<text>"What are you doing? Is this really keeping the peace? The Ministry stands for lawful justice, and yet here you are attacking a defenseless Mantis! Is this what you signed up to the force for?"
		
The Peacekeeper falters for a moment. "I- don't try and get involved in things that have nothing to do with you, Federation!" The Zoltan begins to say more, but is immediately sliced in twain by the Free Mantis, who crawled off the floor while the Zoltan was distracted. You hurry back to the ship before the Peacekeeper ship notices something is wrong, but it's too late. You escape from the ship, but a team of Zoltans beam aboard your ship!</text>
	<crewMember amount="1" class="mantis_warlord"/>
	<boarders min="2" max="3" class="zoltan_peacekeeper"/>
	<!--<choice>
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="MORALITY_UPDATE_ZOLTAN"/>
	</choice>-->
</event>

<event name="ZOLTAN_REVOLT" unique="true">
	<text>Despite the arrogant nature of the Zoltans regarding their supposedly superior government, many of their kind are dissatisfied with the strict and controlling Zoltan Peace-Keepers instated to, as their name would suggest, 'keep the peace'. It appears a full on riot has started on the nearby planet.</text>
	<img planet="PLANET_POPULATED"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Pull closer to survey the chaos.</text>
		<event>
			<text>It seems the conflict was incited by a Duskbringer soldier giving a rather motivating speech, which inevitably resulted in complete and utter destruction, as civilians overturn Peace-Keeper ground vehicles and orbital satellites open fire on crowds of innocent people trying to flee for their life.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Take part in the battle - help the Zoltan civilians.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You've made up your mind to help the civilians. You attack one of the Peace-Keeper vessels.</text>
					<ship load="SHIP_ZOLTAN_REVOLT_PEACE" hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Take part in the battle - help the Peace-Keepers.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You've made up your mind to help the Peace-Keepers. You attack one of the Duskbringer vessels.</text>
					<ship load="SHIP_ZOLTAN_REVOLT_DUSK" hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="cloaking">
				<text>(Cloaking) Cloak and loot some of the buildings while everyone is distracted.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You swoop down to collect some supplies as quickly as possible before leaving.</text>
					<autoReward level="RANDOM">stuff</autoReward>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Pull away quickly.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>This isn't our business, ignore them.</text>
		<event>
			<text>It's not your duty to get involved in the business of everyone else you encounter. You ignore the chaos below.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="ZOLTAN_REVOLT_CIVILIANS_HELP"> <!--fight the Peace-Keepers-->
	<event>
		<text>The civilians manage to fight back the Peace-Keeper forces, who flee from the scene before more casualties can occur. It appears your efforts did not go unnoticed either, and the civilians bring you a large reward for your assistance.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">item</autoReward>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>The civilians manage to fight back the Peace-Keeper forces, who flee from the scene before more casualties can occur. It appears your efforts did not go unnoticed either, and the civilians bring you a large reward for your assistance.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">item</autoReward>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>Unfortunately, it seems your efforts were in vain. The civilians are defeated and the Peace-Keepers retake the city. You flee before they can chase you off themselves.</text>
	</event>
</eventList>
<eventList name="ZOLTAN_REVOLT_PEACE_HELP"> <!--fight the Duskbringers-->
	<event>
		<text>As you expected, the Peace-Keepers quickly retake the sector from the Duskbringers and begin making arrests. It appears you chose to help the right side, because the Peace-Keepers have taken note of your efforts at assisting them and pay you in scrap.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">scrap_only</autoReward>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>It appears your efforts were in vain, as the Duskbringer forces beat back the Peace-Keepers and slowly take control over the city. As the Capital forces flee, a lone soldier runs to your ship and offers to join you so they can escape.</text>
		<crewMember amount="1" class="zoltan_peacekeeper"/>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>While scrapping the hull of the Duskbringer ship, a massive explosion erupts from one of the nearby buildings! Your ship takes some damage but luckily you pull away in time before it can be compromised. Another series of explosions rocks the city, as buildings crumble to the ground! A squadron of Duskbringer bombs descend from the sky, reducing the city to ashes. You fly away as quickly as possible.</text>
		<damage amount="5"/>
	</event>
</eventList>
<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					DISTRESS EVENTS ()
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->
<eventList name="DISTRESS_ZOLTAN_MV">
	<event load="DISTRESS_ZOLTAN_MANTIS_MV"/>
	<event load="DISTRESS_ZOLTAN_HUSK_MV"/>
	<event load="DISTRESS_REFUGEE_ZOLTAN_MV"/>
</eventList>

<event name="DISTRESS_ZOLTAN_MANTIS_MV" unique="true">
	<text>Your jump interrupts a Zoltan security ship as it follows a Mantis pirate into an asteroid field. They message you, "Your presence here will continue to be tolerated - but please, do not interfere."</text>
	<environment type="asteroid"/>
	<distressBeacon/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Interfere and save the Mantis ship.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Sometimes you have to bet on the underdog - even on the rare occasions that the underdog is a Mantis warship. You set off for the heart of the asteroid field and engage the Zoltan there.</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_ZOLTAN_SAVE_MANTIS1" hostile="true"/>
			<environment type="asteroid"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="MORALITY_UPDATE_ZOLTAN_FIGHT"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Interfere and help the Zoltan ship.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You overtake the Zoltans and catch up with the Mantis ship in the asteroid belt. Time to make some friends.</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_ZOLTAN_SAVE_MANTIS2" hostile="true"/>
			<environment type="asteroid"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Don't interfere.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Zoltans know their business better than most - best to leave them to it. You prepare to jump.</text>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DISTRESS_ZOLTAN_HUSK_MV" unique="true">
	<distressBeacon/>
	<text>You arrive to find a lumbering Zoltan freighter with no one at the helm. It's a mystery what happened to the crew, but it'd be a shame to let the opportunity go to waste.</text>
	<autoReward level="RANDOM">standard</autoReward>
	<choice>
		<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
		<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Do nothing.</text>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DISTRESS_REFUGEE_ZOLTAN_MV" unique="true">
	<distressBeacon/>
	<text>You have encountered a refugee ship drifting in space. It looks as if it was fleeing the Rebel advance and ran out of fuel. Its distress beacon is active, but you're not sure anyone is on board.</text>
	<choice>
		<text>Hail them.</text>
		<event load="REFUGEE_HAIL_LIST_ZOLTAN_MV"/>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Ignore the refugees.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You're wary of the refugees but figure it's safe to do something on the ship.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="REFUGEE_HAIL_LIST_ZOLTAN_MV">
	<event load="REFUGEE_TRADER"/>
	<event>
		<text>As you hail the refugee ship, a Zoltan ship suddenly jumps into the system... it claims the refugees are criminals, and accuses you of escorting fugitives! Before you can respond, it cuts communications, and powers up its weapons!</text>
		<ship load="SHIP_ZOLTAN_REFUGEE" hostile="true"/>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
		</choice>
	</event>
</eventList> 

<eventList name="DISTRESS_ZOLTAN_UNIQUE">
	<event load="DISTRESS_ZOLTAN_ARREST"/>
	<event load="DISTRESS_ZOLTAN_RAID"/>

	<event load="DISTRESS_ZOLTAN_MANTIS_MV"/>
	<event load="DISTRESS_ZOLTAN_HUSK_MV"/>
	<event load="DISTRESS_REFUGEE_ZOLTAN_MV"/>
</eventList>

<event name="DISTRESS_ZOLTAN_ARREST" unique="true">
	<distressBeacon/>
	<text>It appears a pirate ship here is under arrest by a Zoltan ship. They've secretly activated the distress beacon, and have sent you a short message saying "help".</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Assist the pirates and attack the Zoltans.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You arm the weapons and engage the Zoltan vessel.</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_ZOLTAN_CAPITAL_ARREST" hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="MORALITY_UPDATE_ZOLTAN_FIGHT"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Report the pirates to the Zoltans.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Zoltans gruffly thank you and give you some fuel, then go back to dealing with the pirates.</text>
			<autoReward level="LOW">fuel_only</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore the pirates.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The pirates send you no future messages and are all brought aboard the Zoltan ship, which jumps away shortly after.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="DISTRESS_CAPITAL_ARREST_WIN">
	<event>
		<text>It appears the pirates were slavers. Grateful for your assistance, they offer you one of their 'workers' for free.</text>
		<crewMember amount="1"/>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>The pirates appear to be mercenaries, ironically hired to hunt you down by the Rebels. After an awkward silence, you work out a deal, and they promise to lie to the fleet.</text>
		<modifyPursuit amount="-2"/>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>The pirates appear to be smugglers. They explain that their client snitched on them and led to their arrest. Now that you've saved them, they offer to sell to you instead.</text>
		<store>STORE_PIRATE</store>
	</event>
</eventList>

<event name="DISTRESS_ZOLTAN_RAID" unique="true">
	<distressBeacon/>
	<text>A Zoltan Peace Brigade is under heavy fire at this beacon by a battalion of Rebel fighters. The distress beacon comes from the commanding ship. They appear to be too busy to notice you.</text>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_ZOLTBATTLE" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Hail them and offer assistance.</text>
		<event>
			<text>It's hard to hear the Zoltan commander over the sounds of gunfire on their ship. "What?! Oh, you've come to provide assistance? We need all the help we can, there's numerous Rebel ships attacking this system! If you're going to help, be quick about it!"</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Attack one of the smaller Rebel ships.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Several Rebel ships are scattered around the perimeter, swooping in to assist their comrades when necessary. You pick a ship at random and attack.</text>
					<ship load="SHIP_CAPITAL_RAID_BORING" hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Take on one of the Elite ships.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The burden of the attack is being carried out by Elite vessels. You intercept one of them and attack.</text>
					<ship load="SHIP_CAPITAL_RAID_ELITE" hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Take on the ship leading the squadron.</text>
				<event>
					<text>A powerful MFK Ace is leading the Rebels. If you can destroy it, the Zoltans might be able to win this battle.</text>
					<ship load="SHIP_CAPITAL_RAID_ACE" hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>This is chaos, leave.</text>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="CAPITAL_RAID_BORING_WIN">
	<text>You salvage the remains of the Rebel ship while the battle rages on in the distance.</text>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Zoltans are too busy dealing with the conflict to reward you, so you decide it's a good time to leave before another Rebel ship attacks you.</text>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="CAPITAL_RAID_ELITE_WIN">
	<text>You salvage the remains of the Elite Rebel ship while the battle rages on in the distance.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">weapon</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Zoltans are too busy dealing with the conflict to reward you, so you decide it's a good time to leave before another Rebel ship attacks you.</text>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="CAPITAL_RAID_SELITE_WIN">
	<text>The MFK Ace has been neutralized. You salvage the remains of the ship.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">weapon</autoReward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Around you the battle begins to die down. The Rebels, watching you defeat their leader, reconsider and begin to jump away. In a matter of minutes the Zoltan forces go from near defeat to conclusive victory.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Contact the Zoltans.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"You have saved us from a terrible defeat. We are grateful for your assistance. Allow me to repay our debt to you."</text>
					<autoReward level="MED">stuff</autoReward>
					<crewMember amount="1" class="zoltan_peacekeeper"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					QUEST EVENTS ()
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->
<eventList name="QUESTS_ZOLTAN_MV">
	<event load="ZOLTAN_LAWBOOK"/>
	<event load="ZOLTAN_LANIUS_CORE"/>
</eventList>

<event name="ZOLTAN_LAWBOOK" unique="true">
	<text>A Zoltan peacekeeper is straggling behind its assigned fleet at this beacon, looking for something. They hail you quickly, asking if you can do them a favor.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_ZOLTAN_ELITE_FIGHT" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Inquire further.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"I would not normally ask a stranger of this, but we have found ourselves in a very unfortunate position. We have lost our book of law, a utility required for all Zoltan peacekeepers to have on them at all times. We will not be permitted back into our fleet until we find it... or someone else finds it for us. Would you be willing to track it down? We will give the co-ordinates of one of the positions we suspect it may be in."</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Agree.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The Zoltan transmit the suspected location of their lawbook.</text>
					<quest event="ZOLTAN_QUEST_LAWBOOK_LIST"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Decline.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>No thanks, we aren't looking for any side jobs or mercenary work.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Zoltan begin to protest but give up and go back to searching.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="ZOLTAN_QUEST_LAWBOOK_LIST">
	<event load="ZOLTAN_QUEST_LAWBOOK_PIRATE"/>
	<event load="ZOLTAN_QUEST_LAWBOOK_DUSKBRINGER"/>
	<event load="ZOLTAN_QUEST_LAWBOOK_ENGI"/>
</eventList>
<event name="ZOLTAN_QUEST_LAWBOOK_PIRATE" unique="true">
	<beaconType id="map_icon_quest" global="true">
		<color r="69" g="168" b="235" a="1"/>
		<unvisitedTooltip>Presumed location of a lost Zoltan law book.</unvisitedTooltip>
	</beaconType>
	<text>At the suspected location of the lawbook you find a smuggler ship. "Ah, I see you've been sent to collect this little book here. Thing is, we could sell this for a giant price as an artifact on the black market. So, if you want it back, you're gonna have to pay us."</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_SMUGGLER_LAWBOOK" hostile="false"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Pay for the lawbook.</text>
		<event>
			<text>It's one hell of a ripoff, but you're willing to do it if it means you don't have to fight the smugglers.</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="-30" max="-30"/>
			</item_modify>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="ZOLTAN_QUEST_LAWBOOK_OBTAIN"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Just fight them for it.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You aren't paying for the damn book. You'll just take it from them.</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Leave.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Alright, alright! I'll lower the price. But only this once!"</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Pay for the lawbook.</text>
				<event>
					<text>It's one hell of a ripoff, but you're willing to do it if it means you don't have to fight the smugglers.</text>
					<item_modify>
						<item type="scrap" min="-15" max="-15"/>
					</item_modify>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="ZOLTAN_QUEST_LAWBOOK_OBTAIN"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Just fight them for it.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You aren't paying for the damn book. You'll just take it from them.</text>
					<ship hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>No thanks.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The Smugglers don't attempt to negotiate further.</text>
					<choice>
						<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
						<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>Do nothing.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="ZOLTAN_QUEST_LAWBOOK_DUSKBRINGER" unique="true">
	<beaconType id="map_icon_quest" global="true">
		<color r="69" g="168" b="235" a="1"/>
		<unvisitedTooltip>Presumed location of a lost Zoltan law book.</unvisitedTooltip>
	</beaconType>
	<text>You notice a Duskbringer ship collecting the lawbook from a pirate vessel. You'll likely have to fight them for it if you want it back.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_DUSKBRINGER_LAWBOOK" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Take back the law book.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You prepare to engage the Duskbringer ship.</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Leave.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You aren't interested in fighting the Duskbringer ship.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="ZOLTAN_QUEST_LAWBOOK_ENGI" unique="true">
	<beaconType id="map_icon_quest" global="true">
		<color r="69" g="168" b="235" a="1"/>
		<unvisitedTooltip>Presumed location of a lost Zoltan law book.</unvisitedTooltip>
	</beaconType>
	<text>An Engi ship at this beacon is sitting dormant. You hail it, asking if it has seen the lost law book. "Bound paper object of conduction code has been found. Intentions: keep book safe until owner returns."</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_ENGI_LAWBOOK" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true"> <!--maybe add a chance?-->
		<text>Tell the Engi that the Zoltans sent you.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Likelihood of Zoltans sending Federation ship to retrieve Law Book... favorable." They send over the book.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="ZOLTAN_QUEST_LAWBOOK_OBTAIN"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Just fight them for it.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You prepare to engage the Engi ship.</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="MORALITY_UPDATE_ENGI_FIGHT"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Leave.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The law book is likely safe with the Engi. Hopefully, the Zoltans return here to find the Engi and get the book back.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="ZOLTAN_QUEST_LAWBOOK_OBTAIN">
	<text>Now that you have the lawbook, you can head back to the location of the Zoltan ship.</text>
	<quest event="ZOLTAN_QUEST_LAWBOOK_RETURN"/>
</event>
<event name="ZOLTAN_QUEST_LAWBOOK_RETURN">
	<beaconType id="map_icon_quest" global="true">
		<color r="69" g="168" b="235" a="1"/>
		<unvisitedTooltip>Return the lost law book here.</unvisitedTooltip>
	</beaconType>
	<text>You've found the Zoltan ship again. You send over the law book, for which they are extremely grateful. They give you an augment and some supplies.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">stuff</autoReward>
	<augment name="RANDOM"/>
</event>

<event name="ZOLTAN_LANIUS_CORE" unique="true">
	<text>To your surprise, this beacon is inhabited by a Lanius vessel! They don't attack, but instead send you a message.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_LANIUS_GENERIC" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Respond.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Offer asking. Green! Force want. Core Zoltan collect, bring us." It's hard to understand, but after further discussion it seems the Lanius are interested in the Zoltan shields on this sector's inhabitants, and are asking you for a favor. Capture a Zoltan ship and bring to the Lanius their shield's core, and they will pay you.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Agree.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Greater. Location sending." The Lanius attach the co-ordinates of the ship they are wanting the core from.</text>
					<quest event="QUEST_ZOLTAN_LANIUS_CORE_LIST"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Decline.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Attack!</text>
		<event>
			<text>If the Lanius aren't going to attack, then you will!</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>	
		<text>Ignore the Lanius.</text>
		<event load="QUEST_ZOLTAN_LANIUS_CORE_IGNORE"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="QUEST_ZOLTAN_LANIUS_CORE_IGNORE">
	<event>
		<text>The Lanius eventually jump away after realizing you don't intend on responding.</text>
		<choice>
			<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
			<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
		</choice>
		<choice>
			<text>Do nothing.</text>
			<event/>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>The Lanius aren't pleased by being ignored... they arm their weapons and attack!</text>
		<ship hostile="true"/>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
		</choice>
	</event>
</eventList>
<eventList name="QUEST_ZOLTAN_LANIUS_CORE_LIST">
	<event load="QUEST_ZOLTAN_LANIUS_CORE_REGULAR"/>
	<event load="QUEST_ZOLTAN_LANIUS_CORE_STATION"/>
	<event load="QUEST_ZOLTAN_LANIUS_CORE_DUSKBRINGER"/>
	<event load="QUEST_ZOLTAN_LANIUS_CORE_MONK"/>
	<event load="QUEST_ZOLTAN_LANIUS_CORE_AUTO"/>
</eventList>
<event name="QUEST_ZOLTAN_LANIUS_CORE_REGULAR">
	<beaconType id="map_icon_quest" global="true">
		<color r="69" g="168" b="235" a="1"/>
		<unvisitedTooltip>Tracked location of a Zoltan shield core.</unvisitedTooltip>
	</beaconType>
	<text>The co-ordinates have led you to a regular Zoltan ship. If you want the core, you'll have to clear them of inhabitants first.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_ZOLTAN_CORE_REGULAR" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Attack!</text>
		<event>
			<text>You arm the weapons and approach the Zoltan ship.</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>These Zoltans haven't done anything to us, leave them alone.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You decide not to fight the Zoltans.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="QUEST_ZOLTAN_LANIUS_CORE_STATION">
	<beaconType id="map_icon_quest" global="true">
		<color r="69" g="168" b="235" a="1"/>
		<unvisitedTooltip>Tracked location of a Zoltan shield core.</unvisitedTooltip>
	</beaconType>
	<text>The co-ordinates have led you to a regular Zoltan station. If you want the core, you'll have to clear them of inhabitants first.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_ZOLTAN_CORE_STATION" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Attack!</text>
		<event>
			<text>You arm the weapons and approach the Zoltan station.</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>These Zoltans haven't done anything to us, leave them alone.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You decide not to fight the Zoltans.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="QUEST_ZOLTAN_LANIUS_CORE_DUSKBRINGER">
	<beaconType id="map_icon_quest" global="true">
		<color r="69" g="168" b="235" a="1"/>
		<unvisitedTooltip>Tracked location of a Zoltan shield core.</unvisitedTooltip>
	</beaconType>
	<text>The co-ordinates have led you to a Duskbringer vessel! They immediately detect that you are a Federation ship and attack. You'll have to fight them either way, but if you want the core you'll have to kill their crew.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_ZOLTAN_CORE_DUSKBRINGER" hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="QUEST_ZOLTAN_LANIUS_CORE_MONK">
	<beaconType id="map_icon_quest" global="true">
		<color r="69" g="168" b="235" a="1"/>
		<unvisitedTooltip>Tracked location of a Zoltan shield core.</unvisitedTooltip>
	</beaconType>
	<text>The co-ordinates have led you to a Zoltan Monk! They hail you: "The stars have told us you would come here, in search of the heart that powers our ship. If you wish to take it, you must test your mind."</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_ZOLTAN_CORE_MONK" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Agree to "test your mind".</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Monks lead you to a room shrouded in complete darkness, and lock the door. You wait inside for several hours completely alone. Right when you think you are about to go insane, you drift into a deep sleep. When you awake, you are back on the ship with a monk and the core!</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="zoltan_monk"/>
			<modifyPursuit amount="1"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="QUEST_ZOLTAN_LANIUS_CORE_OBTAIN"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_MONK">
		<text>(Monk Crew) Negotiate with them for the core.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Your Monk crew member seems to have been able to convince the others to give you their core.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="QUEST_ZOLTAN_LANIUS_CORE_OBTAIN"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Screw the riddle, attack them.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You arm the weapons and approach the Monk ship. However, it seems the Monks are trying to escape!</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="QUEST_ZOLTAN_LANIUS_CORE_AUTO">
	<beaconType id="map_icon_quest" global="true">
		<color r="69" g="168" b="235" a="1"/>
		<unvisitedTooltip>Tracked location of a Zoltan shield core.</unvisitedTooltip>
	</beaconType>
	<text>The co-ordinates have led you to an automated Zoltan ship. It seems to be in rest mode, so maybe you can stealthily extract the core?</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_ZOLTAN_CORE_AUTO" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Attempt to salvage the core.</text>
		<event load="QUEST_ZOLTAN_LANIUS_CORE_AUTO_SALVAGE"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="hacking">
		<text>(Hacking) Hack the Auto-ship to keep it offline.</text>
		<event>
			<text>It appears you are successful! The Auto-ship remains offline.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Inspect the core.</text>
				<event load="QUEST_ZOLTAN_LANIUS_CORE_OBTAIN"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<!--<choice hidden="true" req="BLUELIST_WEAPONS_HACK">
		<text>(Hacking Weapon) Disable the Auto-ship activation sequence.</text>
		<event>
			<text>It appears you are successful! The Auto-ship remains offline.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Inspect the core.</text>
				<event load="QUEST_ZOLTAN_LANIUS_CORE_OBTAIN"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>-->
	<choice hidden="true" req="cloaking">
		<text>(Cloaking) Cloak the ship while extracting the core.</text>
		<event>
			<text>It appears you are successful! The Auto-ship remains offline.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Inspect the core.</text>
				<event load="QUEST_ZOLTAN_LANIUS_CORE_OBTAIN"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Ignore the Auto-ship.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You decide not to attempt to extract the core from the Zoltan Auto-ship.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="QUEST_ZOLTAN_LANIUS_CORE_AUTO_SALVAGE">
	<event>
		<text>It appears you are successful! The Auto-ship remains offline.</text>
		<choice>
			<text>Inspect the core.</text>
			<event load="QUEST_ZOLTAN_LANIUS_CORE_OBTAIN"/>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>Your attempt was unsuccessful. The Auto-ship recognizes you and attacks!</text>
		<ship hostile="true"/>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
		</choice>
	</event>
</eventList>
<event name="QUEST_ZOLTAN_LANIUS_CORE_OBTAIN">
	<text>You observe the core. Now that it has been removed from the ship you can't seem to tell how to reverse engineer it, but you assume the Lanius are aware of that and know how to fix it. However... you might be able to use this to upgrade your regular shields.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Bring the core to the Lanius for your reward.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You contact the Lanius and get their new co-ordinates.</text>
			<quest event="QUEST_ZOLTAN_LANIUS_CORE_FINISH"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="shields" lvl="1" max_lvl="7" blue="false">
		<text>Dismantle the core and use it to upgrade your shields.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You won't be able to get your reward now, but your shield system is running better than ever.</text>
			<upgrade amount="1" system="shields"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="QUEST_ZOLTAN_LANIUS_CORE_FINISH">
	<beaconType id="map_icon_quest" global="true">
		<color r="69" g="168" b="235" a="1"/>
		<unvisitedTooltip>Location of the Lanius ship awaiting the shield core you retrieved.</unvisitedTooltip>
	</beaconType>
	<text>You deliver the core to the Lanius ship. "Favor am glad. Bits are belonging you." They transfer over some supplies and offer to trade further.</text>
	<autoReward level="MED">stuff</autoReward>
	<store>STORE_LANIUS</store>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					HOSTILE EVENTS ()
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->
<eventList name="HOSTILE_ZOLTAN_MV">
	<event load="ENCOUNTER_ZOLTAN"/>
	<event load="ENCOUNTER_ZOLTAN_AUTO"/>
	
	<event load="ENCOUNTER_PIRATE_ZOLTAN"/>
	<event load="ENCOUNTER_MANTIS_ZOLTAN"/>
	<!--<event load="ENCOUNTER_ENGI_ZOLTAN"/>-->
	
	<event load="ENCOUNTER_REBEL"/>
	<event load="ENCOUNTER_AUTO"/>

	<event load="ZOLTAN_MALFUNCTION_INTERROGATE"/>
</eventList>

<event name="ENCOUNTER_ZOLTAN">
	<loadEventList first="false" generate="true">
		<event name="ENCOUNTER_ZOLTAN_REGULAR"/>
		<event name="ENCOUNTER_ZOLTAN_ASTEROID"/>
		<event name="ENCOUNTER_ZOLTAN_PULSAR"/>
	</loadEventList>
</event>
<!--regular-->
<event name="ENCOUNTER_ZOLTAN_REGULAR">
	<text load="TEXT_ENCOUNTER_ZOLTAN"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_ZOLTAN_FIGHT" hostile="true"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="ZOLTAN_DELETER">
		<text>(Zoltan Deleter) Threaten the Zoltans.</text>
		<event load="ENCOUNTER_ZOLTAN_THREATEN"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_ENCOUNTER_ZOLTAN">
	<text>A Zoltan ship makes contact. "The nature of the day is rotational. The fever is emaciated. The reason is-" They've caught some nasty deep space dementia. Before you can consider finding help for them, they open fire.</text>
	<text>You're surprised when a stationary Zoltan ship opens fire. It appears there are aggressive pugilists even among the 'enlightened'.</text>
	<text>You receive a message, "This area is off limits. Submit your ship to processing." It's only one guard ship in a lonely beacon. You decide to fight your way out.</text>
	<text>You discover a number of Zoltan civilian ships fighting off pirates. Unfortunately one ship mistakes your purpose and moves in to attack! They are refusing all communication; you have no choice but to fight.</text>
	<text>Like many areas in Zoltan space, the residents of this sector prepared well for Galactic war. The military here seem to have given up reasoning with foreigners, preferring instead to attack on sight!</text>
	<text>A Zoltan ship is waiting at this beacon. They request your identification, but radiation from the sun in this system is disrupting your communications. They take your silence for aggression and move in to attack.</text>
	<text>The Zoltan ship patrolling this area hails you: "This area is off limits. Secrecy is vital." They power their weapons.</text>
</textList>
<eventList name="ENCOUNTER_ZOLTAN_THREATEN">
	<event>
		<text>The Zoltans are not threatened by you. With your attempt at scaring them foiled, you prepare to fight.</text>
		<ship hostile="true"/>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>The Zoltans are not threatened by you. With your attempt at scaring them foiled, you prepare to fight.</text>
		<ship hostile="true"/>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>The Zoltans are not threatened by you. With your attempt at scaring them foiled, you prepare to fight.</text>
		<ship hostile="true"/>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>To your surprise, the Zoltans are actually frightened by your weapon. They offer some supplies.</text>
		<ship hostile="false"/>
		<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
	</event>
</eventList>
<event name="ENCOUNTER_ZOLTAN_ASTEROID" unique="true">
	<text>You arrive in an asteroid field and are greeted by a Zoltan guard. "By attempting to access these closed mining fields, you are in violation of the Natural Mineral Protection Act. Your weaponry will be confiscated for processing." You don't have time for this.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_ZOLTAN_FIGHT" hostile="true"/>
	<environment type="asteroid"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="ZOLTAN_DELETER">
		<text>(Zoltan Deleter) Threaten the Zoltans.</text>
		<event load="ENCOUNTER_ZOLTAN_THREATEN"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="ENCOUNTER_ZOLTAN_PULSAR" unique="true">
	<text load="TEXT_ENCOUNTER_ZOLTAN_PULSAR"/>
	<environment type="pulsar"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_ZOLTAN_FIGHT" hostile="true"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="ZOLTAN_DELETER">
		<text>(Zoltan Deleter) Threaten the Zoltans.</text>
		<event load="ENCOUNTER_ZOLTAN_THREATEN"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_ENCOUNTER_ZOLTAN_PULSAR">
	<text>"The end is upon us. The eye casts its madness upon the sector - electromagnetism!" A stream of incoherent babble floods your speakers as a Zoltan ship attacks!</text>
	<text>A Ministry research station has been constructed near the pulsar here to study it. Your presence, for some reason, is recognized as a violation of boundaries and they send a ship to ward you off!</text>
	<text>Most species would tend to avoid locations such as these, but the Zoltans don't seem to particularly mind the hazards. They do mind, however, military vessels like yours wandering through their territory!</text>
</textList>

<event name="ENCOUNTER_ZOLTAN_AUTO">
	<loadEventList first="false" generate="true">
		<event name="ENCOUNTER_ZOLTAN_AUTO_REGULAR"/>
		<event name="ENCOUNTER_ZOLTAN_AUTO_SUN"/>
	</loadEventList>
</event>
<event name="ENCOUNTER_ZOLTAN_AUTO_REGULAR">
	<text load="TEXT_ENCOUNTER_ZOLTAN_AUTO"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_ZOLTAN_AUTO" hostile="true"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_ENCOUNTER_ZOLTAN_AUTO">
	<text>The Zoltans are one of the few races who've invested in automated drone tech. Unfortunately, these ships are unpredictable at best and often attack random passers-by, such as yourself.</text>
	<text>"Combat mode engaged... looking for targets... target found!" An automated Zoltan vessel moves in to attack.</text>
	<text>It appears the automated Zoltan vessel here is malfunctioning... and has falsely decided that you are a threat!</text>
</textList>
<event name="ENCOUNTER_ZOLTAN_AUTO_SUN" unique="true">
	<text>A Zoltan Automated ship appears to be in charging mode near this sun, probably harvesting the solar energy! However, it appears you arrive just in time for it to re-activate, and the ship somehow identifies you as a threat.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_ZOLTAN_AUTO" hostile="true"/> 
	<environment type="sun"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="ENCOUNTER_PIRATE_ZOLTAN">
	<text load="TEXT_ENCOUNTER_PIRATE_ZOLTAN"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_PIRATE_ZOLTAN" hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_ENCOUNTER_PIRATE_ZOLTAN">
	<text>"Emergency, all ships in range, we are under attack!" The frequency matches a nearby Zoltan ship; you move in on their pursuer. They take your intervention as a cue to jump away. Cowards.</text>
	<text>You jump just in time to witness a Zoltan ship's FTL drive overload. In his final moments their captain implores you not to get involved, but it's too late - their attacker is already upon you!</text>
	<text>Despite their precautions, pirates have begun to harass the local Zoltan settlements across this sector. One such pirate spots your ship and moves in to attack.</text>
	<text>A ship with pirate markings demands your surrender. These are sad times when even Zoltan space is beset by pirates. You doubt these fools will be missed.</text>
	<text>You spot a pirate ship looting a small Zoltan cruiser. They spot you and move in to attack before your FTL drive has a chance to recharge.</text>
</textList>

<event name="ENCOUNTER_MANTIS_ZOLTAN" unique="true">
	<text>You pick up the last broadcast from a rupturing Zoltan freighter: "The Mantis, they're here, please-" You're interrupted by fire off the port bow!</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MANTIS_FIGHT" hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="ENCOUNTER_ENGI_ZOLTAN" unique="true">
	<text>You jump into a debris field that used to be a Zoltan cruiser. Unfortunately, its Engi escort takes you for the attacker and retaliates! They refuse all hails.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_ENGI_FIGHT" hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="ZOLTAN_MALFUNCTION_INTERROGATE" unique="true">
    <text>As you arrive at this beacon, the nearby Ministry Auto-ship sparks. "Warning - this space is off limits - ERROR - explanation not found. Sabotage suspected. Engaging self-defense."</text>
    <ship load="SHIP_ZOLTAN_AUTO_INTERROGATION" hostile="true"/>
    <choice hidden="true">
        <text>Continue...</text>
        <event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
    </choice>
</event>
<event name="ZOLTAN_MALFUNCTION_INTERROGATE_SELF_DEFENSE">
    <text>"Aha! I knew it. You did something bad, didn't you? Don't try to deny it. You did something bad and it caught you, so you had to blow it up." No matter how you try to explain, the Zoltan doesn't accept your other explanations. It's likely that this incident will be reported.</text>
    <choice>
        <text>Continue...</text>
        <event load="MORALITY_UPDATE_ZOLTAN"/>
    </choice>
</event>
<event name="ZOLTAN_MALFUNCTION_INTERROGATE_MALFUNCTION">
    <text>"Oh really? And where is your proof of this? It seems that all evidence has been conveniently destroyed."</text>
    <choice hidden="true" req="sensors" lvl="2">
        <text>(Upg. Sensors) Our ship's sensors have a log of the incident.</text>
        <event>
            <text>The Zoltan looks intently at the logs. "This checks out. Well, in that case, I guess what you did was justified. We'll patch up your ship to offset whatever damage might have been caused."</text>
            <damage amount="-5"/>
        </event>
    </choice>
    <choice req="LIST_CREW_ZOLTAN_CAPITAL">
        <text>(Ministry Crew) "The ship was experiencing error 632. It must not have received the most recent firmware update."</text>
        <event>
            <text>The Zoltan thinks about it for a moment. "That explanation is reasonable, I don't think we did update the firmware. In that case, I guess what you did was justified. We'll patch up your ship to offset whatever damage might have been caused."</text>
            <damage amount="-5"/>
        </event>
    </choice>
    <choice>
        <text>We don't have evidence.</text>
        <event>
            <text>"I didn't think so. I'll let you go for now, but don't think we'll forget this."</text>
            <choice>
                <text>Continue...</text>
                <event load="MORALITY_UPDATE_ZOLTAN"/>
            </choice>
        </event>
    </choice>
</event>
<event name="ZOLTAN_MALFUNCTION_INTERROGATE_ATTACKED">
    <text>"Ah, now we're getting somewhere. So you expect us to believe it attacked you for no reason? That doesn't make any sense."</text>
    <choice hidden="true">
        <text>It must have been malfunctioning or something.</text>
        <event load="ZOLTAN_MALFUNCTION_INTERROGATE_MALFUNCTION"/>
    </choice>
    <choice hidden="true">
        <text>If anyone has been wronged here, it's us. We should be interrogating you!</text>
        <event>
            <text>"So it's our word against yours, then? Well, I don't think we're getting anywhere, so I'll let you off. Maybe it was a malfunction or something. The thing didn't always work right anyway."</text>
            <choice hidden="true">
                <text>Continue...</text>
                <event/>
            </choice>
        </event>
    </choice>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					NEBULA EVENTS ()
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->
<eventList name="NEBULA_ZOLTAN_MV">
	<event load="NEBULA_ZOLTAN_BATTLEFIELD"/>
	<event load="NEBULA_ZOLTAN_STUDY"/>
	<event load="NEBULA_ZOLTAN_ROCK"/>
	<event load="NEBULA_STORM_ZOLTAN_SUPPLY"/>
</eventList>

<event name="NEBULA_ZOLTAN_BATTLEFIELD" unique="true">
	<text>This nebula looks like it's recently seen two ships exchange fire... with mutually-assured destructive results. Wreckage drifts by your screens and tumbles into the depths of the nebula to be lost to sight. It's hard to determine who the combatants were without closer investigation.</text>
	<environment type="nebula"/>
	<choice req="LIST_CREW_SLUG" hidden="true">
		<text>(Slug Crew) Ask your Slug crew to scan for survivors.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Despite the destruction filling the system, your crewman is able to pick up the faint thoughts of a life form in the debris - it looks like they won't last much longer without help.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Assist the survivor.</text>
				<event load="BATTLEFIELD_SURVIVOR"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Leave the battlefield before other ships arrive.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You take leave from the battlefield.</text>
					<choice>
						<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
						<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>Do nothing.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice req="BLUELIST_CREW_SNAIL" hidden="true">
		<text>(Telepathic Shell) Ask your Shell crew to scan for survivors.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Despite the destruction filling the system, your crewman is able to pick up the faint thoughts of a life form in the debris - it looks like they won't last much longer without help.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Assist the survivor.</text>
				<event load="BATTLEFIELD_SURVIVOR"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Leave the battlefield before other ships arrive.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You take leave from the battlefield.</text>
					<choice>
						<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
						<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>Do nothing.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Investigate the battlefield.</text>
		<event load="BATTLEFIELD_INVESTIGATE"/>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Leave the battlefield before other ships arrive.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You take leave from the battlefield.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="BATTLEFIELD_INVESTIGATE">
	<event>
		<text>As you investigate the battlefield, your ship is pummeled by drifting wreckage - unable to detect anything of interest, you decide not to risk any further damage to your hull and prepare to jump.</text>
		<damage amount="4"/>
		<damage amount="1" system="room" effect="fire"/>  <!--DLC-->
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>The wreckage is drifting faster than it first appeared. You barely avoid being pummeled by drifting wreckage - unable to detect anything of interest, you decide not to risk your ship and prepare to jump.</text>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>The wreckage is drifting faster than it first appeared. You barely avoid being pummeled by drifting wreckage - unable to detect anything of interest, you decide not to risk your ship and prepare to jump.</text>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>The wreckage is drifting faster than it first appeared. You barely avoid being pummeled by drifting wreckage - unable to detect anything of interest, you decide not to risk your ship and prepare to jump.</text>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>You spot a life form floating within the wreckage.</text>
		<choice>
			<text>Assist the survivor.</text>
			<event load="BATTLEFIELD_SURVIVOR"/>
		</choice>
		<choice>
			<text>Leave the battlefield before other ships arrive.</text>
			<event>
				<text>You take leave from the battlefield.</text>
				<choice>
					<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
					<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
				</choice>
				<choice>
					<text>Do nothing.</text>
					<event/>
				</choice>
			</event>
		</choice>
	</event>
</eventList>
<event name="BATTLEFIELD_SURVIVOR">
	<text>Your bring the survivor aboard, but discover their wounds are severe. They won't live much longer.</text>
	<choice>
		<text>Make them comfortable for their final moments.</text>
		<event>
			<text>On their death bed, they croak out a series of coordinates and beg you to go there - when you attempt to ask them why, the survivor simply says, "ABADOTH" and perishes.</text>
			<quest event="SECRET_WORD_ABADOTH_MV"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice req="medbay" lvl="2" hidden="true">
		<text>(Upg. Medbay) Get them into the medbay!</text>
		<event>
			<text>Using your upgraded medical bay, you are able to heal the survivor's wounds and they recover quickly. Grateful to be saved, they offer to join your crew and help however they can.</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="zoltan_monk"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice req="clonebay" hidden="true">
		<text>(Clone Bay) Try to clone them before it's too late.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You clone the individual and let the host pass away. The clone decides to join you - although it has little choice in the matter.</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="zoltan_monk"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice req="LIST_CREW_MEDICAL" hidden="true">
		<text>(Medical Crew) Have your crew treat them.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You have your crewmember treat the survivor, and after a tense few moments they successfully nurse them back to good health. Grateful to be saved, they offer to join your crew and help however they can.</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="zoltan_monk"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice req="BLUELIST_DRONES_MEDICAL" hidden="true">
		<text>(Medical Drone) Have your drone treat them.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You have your drone treat the survivor, and it quickly helps them recover. Grateful to be saved, they offer to join your crew and help however they can.</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="zoltan_monk"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice req="BLUELIST_BOMBS_HEAL" hidden="true">
		<text>(Healing Bomb) Use your Heal Bomb on them. [-1}]</text>
		<event>
			<text>Your bomb proves effective at healing the survivor's wounds, and they recover quickly. Grateful to be saved, they offer to join your crew and help however they can.</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="zoltan_monk"/>
			<item_modify>    
				<item type="missiles" min="-1" max="-1"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="SECRET_WORD_ABADOTH_MV">
	<beaconType id="map_icon_quest" global="true">
		<color r="69" g="168" b="235" a="1"/>
		<unvisitedTooltip>Mysterious coordinates provided by a deceased crewman.</unvisitedTooltip>
	</beaconType>
	<text>You have arrived at the coordinates given to you by the dead crewman you attempted to save. There doesn't seem to be anything here - no planets, no vessels, and no clue as to what he meant by sending you here.</text>
	<img planet="NONE"/>
	<choice req="LIST_CREW_SLUG" hidden="true">
		<text>(Slug Crew) Ask your Slug crewmember to scan for life forms.</text>
		<event load="SECRET_WORD_ABADOTH_CONCLUSION_MV"/>
	</choice>
	<choice req="BLUELIST_CREW_SNAIL" hidden="true">
		<text>(Telepathic Shell) Ask your Shell crewmember to scan for life forms.</text>
		<event load="SECRET_WORD_ABADOTH_CONCLUSION_MV"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Do a full system scan - though you're sure to lose some of your lead with the Rebels.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You start the arduous task of a full system scan. This better be worth it.</text>
			<modifyPursuit amount="1"/>
			<choice>
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="SECRET_WORD_ABADOTH_CONCLUSION_MV"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Leave this mystery behind.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You have no clue what this was all about, but you decide to not waste any further time to it.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="SECRET_WORD_ABADOTH_CONCLUSION_MV">
	<text>Suddenly, a Zoltan ship appears seemingly from out of nowhere! "We insist you provide the reason for being here, or face grave consequences."</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_ZOLTAN_FIGHT" hostile="false"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Explain about finding the dead crewman.</text>
		<event>
			<text>There is a moment of silence, and suddenly the Zoltan ship powers weapons - must have been the wrong word to use... now you've got a fight on your hands!</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice req="LIST_CREW_ENGI" hidden="true">
		<text>(Engi Crew) Say ABADOTH.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Your Engi crewman easily recalls the phrase the deadman used from its memory banks. There is a moment of silence, and the ship's captain solemnly thanks you for the information. He wishes you well on your journey, and he offers several upgrades to assist you in exchange for your service to the Zoltan race.</text>
			<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
			<choice>
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="MORALITY_REMOVE_ZOLTAN"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice req="LIST_CREW_COGNITIVE" hidden="true">
		<text>(Cognitive Crew) Say ABADOTH.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Your Cognitive easily recalls the phrase the deadman used from its memory banks. There is a moment of silence, and the ship's captain solemnly thanks you for the information. He wishes you well on your journey, and he offers several upgrades to assist you in exchange for your service to the Zoltan race.</text>
			<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward> 
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Say ANODYNE.</text>
		<event>
			<text>There is a moment of silence, and suddenly the Zoltan ship powers weapons - must have been the wrong word to use... now you've got a fight on your hands!</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Say ABADOTH.</text>
		<event>
			<text>There is a moment of silence, and the ship's captain solemnly thanks you for the information. He wishes you well on your journey, and he offers several upgrades to assist you in exchange for your service to the Zoltan race.</text>
			<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
			<choice>
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="MORALITY_REMOVE_ZOLTAN"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Say ABATODH.</text>
		<event>
			<text>There is a moment of silence, and suddenly the Zoltan ship powers weapons - must have been the wrong word to use... now you've got a fight on your hands!</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="NEBULA_ZOLTAN_STUDY" unique="true">
	<text>You arrive at a Zoltan research facility. They say they are researching genetic distortion due to stasis sleep and prolonged FTL travel. They ask if your crew has the time to undergo a few scans.</text>
	<environment type="nebula"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Participate in their study.</text>
		<event load="ZOLTAN_CREW_STUDY_LIST_MV"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Decline.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Alright. Fly safe." You prepare to leave.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="medbay" lvl="3">
		<text>(Adv. Medbay) Give them your medical records.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Thank you! We didn't expect to receive such a significant amount of data regarding your crew's health during FTL travel. Please, accept this for your trouble."</text>
			<drone name="RANDOM"/>
			<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_SHELL">
		<text>(Shell Crew) Request an exchange with the Zoltan science team.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Overjoyed to come across this opportunity after having remained in Shell space for so long, your Shell has many subjects to discuss, most of which are beyond your understanding. Following a long debate and brainstorming sessions with the Zoltans, they finally are able to return to you, and offer a drone schematic in thanks.</text>
			<drone name="RANDOM"/>
			<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="ANCIENT_CONSTRUCTOR"> <!--thought this would be interesting to add as well-->
		<text>(Hibernating Alien) Ask if they know what to do with this.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Interesting... I have never seen a creature like this. I'm afraid there's not much we can do with it; its current state is unrelated to stasis sleep. However, with a catalyst, such as quantum fuel, you may be able to awaken it again?"</text>
			<restartEvent/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="ZOLTAN_CREW_STUDY_LIST_MV">
	<event>
		<text>Your crew calmly lines up for the Zoltans to take their readings. After a short time, the process is done. They contact you, "Thank you for your participation in our study. Please accept these small cakes made from stiff dough as well as some scrap."</text>
		<autoReward level="LOW">scrap_only</autoReward>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>Your crew calmly lines up for the Zoltans to take their readings. After a short time, the process is done. They contact you, "Thank you for your participation in our study. Please accept these small cakes made from stiff dough as well as some scrap."</text>
		<autoReward level="LOW">scrap_only</autoReward>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>As soon as you dock, pirates burst on board and a hostile ship appears on the radar. You hear the Zoltans yell in the distance, "We're being held hostage!"</text>
		<ship load="SHIP_PIRATE_ZOLTAN_CREW_STUDY" hostile="true"/>
		<boarders min="2" max="2" class="random"/>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
		</choice>
	</event>
</eventList>

<event name="NEBULA_ZOLTAN_ROCK" unique="true">
	<text>This nebula turns out to be the hiding place of a terrified Rock crew taking refuge from the Zoltan border police. They don't seem prepared to risk your leaving with their co-ordinates, and open fire!</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_ROCK_GENERIC" hostile="true"/>
	<environment type="nebula"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="NEBULA_STORM_ZOLTAN_SUPPLY" unique="true">
	<text>You spy two pirate ships lurking in the nebula here. They remain unaware of your presence; you're able to get your scanners to at least identify their cargo: one is carrying the fuel supplies, the other the ammunition. They begin to drift away from each other in the storm.</text>
	<environment type="storm"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Secure the fuel supply.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You jet toward the pirate with the fuel supplies and engage - hopefully you can leave the ship in one piece!</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_STORM_PIRATE_SUPPLY_FUEL" hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Secure the ammunition.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You jet toward the pirate with the ammunition and engage - hopefully you can leave the ship in one piece!</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_STORM_PIRATE_SUPPLY_AMMO" hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Let them leave.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Sometimes discretion is the better part of valor.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					UNIQUE EVENTS
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->

<event name="ENCOUNTER_ZOLTAN_ELITE" unique="true">
	<text>Though not all Zoltans choose to align with the extreme views of the Duskbringers, that doesn't mean they all appreciate the Federation. A particularly annoyed Zoltan Elite appears to be fed up with tolerating Federation ships and has decided to attack.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_ZOLTAN_ELITE_FIGHT" hostile="true"/> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					SPECIAL EVENTS
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->
<event name="CAPITAL_OSMIA_RAID" unique="true">
	<text>At first, you assume the nearby planet isn't anything important - until your Atlas informs you this is actually the location of the Zoltan Capital! Usually these places are better marked, but Ministry government buildings are rarely seen as tourist attractions. You expected the capital to be on the Zoltan Homeworlds, Osmia, but this most certainly isn't any such place.</text>
	<preventQuest/>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_ZOLTHUB" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Visit the capital.</text>
		<event>
			<text>As soon as you approach, it's clear something is eerily wrong. There is barely any activity on the streets near the massive capitol building, and you swear you see several armed patrols stationed outside. Your descent is met with a warning; "Unregistered foreign vessel - desist at once and leave this zone. This is not a time for complacent intervention from reckless third parties."</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>We aren't a reckless third party - we're Federation.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"I understand that. My statement still stands. This is a matter of importance for the Ministry and the Ministry alone. Now beat it."</text>
					<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_ZOLTAN_CAPITAL">
						<text>(Ministry Crew) Talk them into allowing you to assist.</text>
						<event load="OSMIA_RAID_ASSIST"/>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_HARMONY">
						<text>(Harmony Crew) Talk them into allowing you to assist.</text>
						<event load="OSMIA_RAID_ASSIST"/>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="ENERGY_SHIELD">
						<text>(Zoltan Shield) Convince them you are a Zoltan ship.</text>
						<event load="OSMIA_RAID_ASSIST"/>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Insist on helping anyways.</text>
						<event>
							<text>The Zoltan doesn't bother speaking to you, instead calling on his radio for backup in dispersing you!</text>
							<ship load="SHIP_ZOLTAN_ELITE_FIGHT" hostile="true"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue...</text>
								<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>It seems there's no convincing these guys.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Abide that warning and leave.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>	
		<text>There's no point in visiting.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You have no interest in bothering the Zoltan citizens or sight seeing.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="OSMIA_RAID_ASSIST">
	<text>"It seems I have misevaluated your aptitude. I am Allta Foleck, regent and speaker on behalf of Minister Lumei who is not present at this time. As you perhaps have noticed, the capitol has been evacuated, and the city is under lockdown in face of an impending terrorist attack."</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Terrorists? Is it the Duskbringers?</text>
		<event>
			<text>Allta hesitates, but eventually responds: "Not quite. We believe they are a more radical, religious sect of the Duskbringers, almost cult like. They have donned masks of hideous three-eyed beasts and wear sacrificial robes, and their only goal is the total annihilation of the Ministry. We have received news that their forces will be arriving soon and they must be apprehended. Death is the only suitable consequence for these acts of terror."</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Agree to stay and help fight the terrorists.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Not too long later, you catch sight of the first of the terrorist vessels approaching. A decently sized cruiser vessel and very well armed, it looks like this is your chance to earn the Ministry's favor.</text>
					<ship load="SHIP_OSMIAN_CRUISER" hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Yeah uh, have fun dealing with those guys. We're out of here.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<ship name="SHIP_OSMIAN_CRUISER" auto_blueprint="MU_OSMIAN_CRUISER">
	<triggeredEvent name="OSMIA_ESCAPE_TRIGGER" event="OSMIA_RAID_ESCAPE" enemyCrew="3" thisFight="true"/>
	<gotaway load="OSMIA_GOTAWAY"/>
	<destroyed>
		<text>The strange Zoltan vessel has been vanquished. It causes some damage to the infastructure below when it crashes into the ground, but the Zoltan officials tell you not to worry.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="OSMIA_RAID_WIN"/>    
		</choice>
	</destroyed>
	<deadCrew>
		<text>The strange Zoltan vessel has been vanquished. It causes some damage to the infastructure below when it crashes into the ground, but the Zoltan officials tell you not to worry.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="OSMIA_RAID_WIN"/>    
		</choice>
	</deadCrew>
</ship>
<event name="OSMIA_RAID_ESCAPE">
	<text>It seems that, having gotten so low on crew, the ship is now attempting to flee. You don't see this kind of behavior often, but you receive word from Allta. "Do not let that ship escape! We must ensure the terrorists cannot regroup!"</text>
	<clearTriggeredEvent name="OSMIA_ESCAPE_TRIGGER"/> 
	<escape/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Keep fighting.</text>
		<event/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="FTL_JUMPER">
		<text>(Adv. Navigation) Suggest allowing the ship to escape and track its movements.</text>
		<event load="OSMIA_RAID_ESCAPE_OFFER"/>  
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="ADV_SCANNERS">
		<text>(Long-Ranged Scanners) Suggest allowing the ship to escape and track its movements.</text>
		<event load="OSMIA_RAID_ESCAPE_OFFER"/>  
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="sensors" lvl="3">
		<text>(Adv. Sensors) Suggest allowing the ship to escape and track its movements.</text>
		<event load="OSMIA_RAID_ESCAPE_OFFER"/>  
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="OSMIA_RAID_ESCAPE_OFFER">
	<text>"Absolutely not! You are under direct orders to keep firing on that ship until they are dead! Do NOT attempt to follow them, they are dangerous and must be stopped!"</text>
	<variable name="loc_evidence_os_escape_offer" op="set" val="1"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Keep fighting.</text>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="OSMIA_GOTAWAY">
	<text>The terrorist ship jumps away. You can tell Allta is mad, but he manages to maintain his professional composure despite his wavering voice. "Very well then. This is not the most optimal outcome, but... we can make do with this. The capital has been saved, thanks to your efforts. Heheh..."</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="OSMIA_RAID_WIN"/>   
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="loc_evidence_os_escape_offer">
		<text>Grab the coordinates of the terrorist ship's new location first.</text>
		<event>
			<text>While you speak further with Allta, you proceed to discreetly download the trajectory and coordinates of the strange Zoltan ship. You aren't sure where this will lead, but clearly there's something there the Ministry doesn't want anyone near.</text>
			<quest event="OSMIA_UNLOCK_QUEST"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="OSMIA_RAID_WIN"/>   
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="OSMIA_RAID_WIN">
	<text>You can't help but notice no other ships were present during the attack, and the Zoltan military forces were... very reserved in that they refused to assist you in the fight. Strange, but Allta appears once again to commemorate you. "I think it goes without saying that without your help, we would not have been able to survive that attack. Allow me to show my generosity to both you and the Federation. Now, feel free to carry on with your mission. I would hate to steal any more of your time." You aren't sure where this sudden attitude shift came from, but as promised Allta does deliver a rather large reward, including ship blueprints for a Zoltan cruiser!</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">droneparts</autoReward>
	<drone name="DRONE_SHIELD_POWERLESS"/>
	<unlockCustomShip silent="false">PLAYER_SHIP_ZOLTAN</unlockCustomShip>
	<variable name="ach_boss_osmian" op="set" val="1"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Accept the gift and leave.</text>
		<event/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>We have some questions left to ask.</text>
		<event load="OSMIA_RAID_QUESTIONS"/>   
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="OSMIA_RAID_QUESTIONS">
	<text>"Oh? Questions? I'm a very busy man I'm afraid. I'll try to entertain your thoughts, but I cannot stick around for long."</text>
	<choice hidden="true" req="loc_evidence_os_question_help" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
		<text>Why did none of the other ships help us?</text>
		<event>
			<text>"We could see that you had the situation under control. With ships as deadly as theirs, we were not willing to risk our more valuable security teams unless necessary. Many citizens and ground patrols were not given full information on the events that were to transpire to ensure there would be no hysteria. That is all, I hope you were not offended."</text>
			<variable name="loc_evidence_os_question_help" op="set" val="1"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>OSMIA_RAID_QUESTIONS</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="loc_evidence_os_question_attack" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
		<text>Why were there no other ships attacking?</text>
		<event>
			<text>"It would seem that we were largely misinformed on the scale of the attack. You see, informants can't get everything right all of the time... With this vessel dealt with, I am certain the terrorists will hesitate before making future attacks, but should we ever need help in the future, I suppose we know who to call... Heheh..."</text>
			<variable name="loc_evidence_os_question_attack" op="set" val="1"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>OSMIA_RAID_QUESTIONS</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="loc_evidence_os_question_mask" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
		<text>Why were those terrorists' masks so realistic?</text>
		<event>
			<text>"What reasonable man could try and justify the absurd efforts of mentally unstable zealots? Their dedication to their craft is, as some would say, remarkable, but I would sooner call it disturbing. Never fear though, those ghastly creatures are just the same as any Zoltan, and thank goodness for it!"</text>
			<variable name="loc_evidence_os_question_mask" op="set" val="1"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event>
					<loadEvent>OSMIA_RAID_QUESTIONS</loadEvent>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>That's all of our questions.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Good, good. You are a very curious individual I see. I appreciate your drive to know more about the galaxy around you, but I must warn you. Try not to go sticking your nose into business you have no part in the future, okay? Bye bye!" Allta immediately hangs up from the call, and an escort is dispatched to ensure you have a 'safe flight' as you leave the capital.</text>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<ship name="SHIP_OSMIAN_CRUISER_COLONY" auto_blueprint="MU_OSMIAN_CRUISER">
	<destroyed>
		<text>You've defeated the ship of so-called Osmians. There wasn't much point - the Ministry isn't exactly going to give you a second reward - but at least this mystery is over. Right?</text>
		<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
	</destroyed>
	<deadCrew>
		<text>You've defeated the ship of so-called Osmians. There wasn't much point - the Ministry isn't exactly going to give you a second reward - but at least this mystery is over. Right?</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	</deadCrew>
</ship>
<event name="OSMIA_UNLOCK_QUEST">
	<beaconType id="map_icon_osmia" global="true">
		<color r="255" g="85" b="75" a="1.0"/>
		<unvisitedTooltip>Location of the terrorists.</unvisitedTooltip>
		<visitedTooltip>Explored location. Nothing left of interest.</visitedTooltip>
	</beaconType>
	<preventQuest/>
	<preventFleet/>
	<quest>
		<nebulaBeacon>false</nebulaBeacon>
		<aggressive>2</aggressive>
	</quest>
	<img back="BACK_EVENT_OSMIA" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<text>As soon as you arrive at the location of the terrorists you're taken aback by the location on your Atlas. THIS is Osmia, homeworld of the Zoltan race. Unlike the capital, which at least had a minor indicator of importance upon arrival, Osmia has no such fanfare. How has the Ministry kept an entire planet hidden from the rest of the Federation - and more importantly, why?</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>As you follow the coordinates closer to the surface you can see the planet has seen much better days. Similar to most of the homeworlds of galactic empires, it lays in a state of mass disarray, but this is much different. Vegetation is completely absent from almost half of the planet, and that where it can be found it grows erratically. Ancient craters decorate the surface and near them is large amounts of radioactivity. You steer clear of the dead-zones and approach a massive elevated city suspended by several large towers. This is no ruin however - it's bustling with activity.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event>
					<text>Suddenly, you're stopped by the same ship as before. Their dialect is strange, though close enough to modern Zoltan that your translator fills in the gaps easily. "Please tell us you have not come to finish us off! Whatever the Ministry has told you is a lie! Please, you must understand, we aren't a threat!"</text>
					<ship load="SHIP_OSMIAN_CRUISER_COLONY" hostile="false"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>You attacked the capital - that seems pretty threatening.</text>
						<event>
							<text>"Look, let me explain! I am Malki, and we are the Osmians. We are not terrorists, I can promise you. We are the last of the few non-transformants that the Ministry could not reach. If you care, I can start from the beginning and explain everything. But I believe you might be of a great help to my people, if you're willing."</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Listen to his explanation.</text>
								<event load="OSMIA_UNLOCK_EXPLANATION"/>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>We're in a bit of a hurry here.</text>
								<event load="OSMIA_UNLOCK_QUESTION"/>
							</choice>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Don't trust these guys - attack!</text>
								<event>
									<text>You ignore the protests of Malki and silence the ship before moving in to attack.</text>
									<ship hostile="true"/>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Continue...</text>
										<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="OSMIA_UNLOCK_EXPLANATION">
	<text>"Okay, okay. Look, why don't we both power down our weapons and meet face to face? If you came this far, you're certainly looking for answers." Reluctantly, you agree and you land your ship near a frozen lake. Malki dismounts from his vessel, revealing himself to look the same as the creatures from before.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>The Ministry said you were disguised Duskbringers.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"I'm afraid that's a lie. One of many. As you can see, we are not Zoltans in the same sense that you know. Long long before the Federation, all of us Zoltans looked this way. Back then, we were steaming ahead full force into the interstellar era, driven to be the first of many competing nations. But this competition turned to travesty, and nuclear holocaust became imminent. Osmia was annihilated, and the survivors were forced to flee the planet. For almost centuries Osmia was out of our reach, a solemn reminder of our failure."</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event>
					<text>"The lost explorers roamed the surrounding nebula, unable to settle for long without devolving into war once again. However, in those mysterious clouds they found something. At the center of the infamous Great Eye nebula was a monolith that held immense, god-like power. The Zoltans came to worship it, and so it brought them unity. This gave birth to the Illesctrian faith and the Ministry who sought to uphold this new peace. The Ministry, however, was brutal with its enforcement, and to justify its cruelty the leadership constructed an ever-large and rapidly expanding codex of laws no man nor army could ever memorize. Through force they assimilated every last Zoltan colony."</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>But what happened? Why are the Zoltans hard-light now?</text>
						<event>
							<text>"Yes, see, the Great Eye also brought with it the discovery of other, similar tech. Aether, a highly conductive and resistant metal alloy used to forge the ruins around the Eye could be used to create sustainable hard-light generators. This tech enticed the Ministry's top scientists, who saw it as a solution for the Osmia crisis alongside various other tech. Though Aether was used to construct most of Zoltan kind's most infamous technology like our special shields, we also used it to create new part-organic part-mechanical forms to explore Osmia with. This was a success and the explorers were revered as heroes, and many flocked back to recolonize the planet. The current Minister at the time only lived for a little longer until he succumbed to a natural death and was replaced by the new Minister, Lumei."</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Wait, but wasn't this centuries ago? How is Lumei still in charge?</text>
								<event>
									<text>"This was indeed long ago, but we'll get to the answer for your question soon enough. Under Lumei's leadership the codex was almost doubled in size and enforcement became even stricter. The Osmian explorers, still held high in reverency by the public, were given seats in the Ministry so Lumei could keep them close to him as pawns. Because of the connection between Aether and the Great Eye, these hard-light forms took on a religious significance as well, and so Lumei himself underwent transformation to secure his power. As the technology became better researched soon the wealthy elite, priests, and eventually even the common people were able to afford such procedures. Supremacy of the transformants took hold and, fearful that this divide might create a split between the Zoltans, the Ministry began to normalize and enforce transformancy."</text>
									<choice hidden="true">
										<text>Continue...</text>
										<event>
											<text>"Most adamant non-transformants died of natural causes and the newer more 'progressive' mindset took hold. All Zoltans over the age of 7 were to be immediately transitioned into hard-light chassis. The only place the Ministry struggled to touch was, ironically, Osmia itself. A group of non-transformants had taken hold there, seizing control of the territory between the wastelands that had survived the initial holocaust. Eventually the Ministry gave up and spent their effort erasing the importance of Osmia from the rest of the Zoltans - something made easier by the recent discovery of other sapient life. And so, that is how the first of we Osmians came to be. The Ministry wants nothing more than for the galaxy to forget we exist and for us to die out naturally."</text>
											<choice hidden="true">
												<text>So, what is it that you needed of us?</text>
												<event load="OSMIA_UNLOCK_QUESTION"/>
											</choice>
										</event>
									</choice>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="OSMIA_UNLOCK_QUESTION">
	<text>"Yes, well I suppose it's best I explain why we were there at the capital then, before I ask of you anything... You see, there are a few of our kind left which have not taken refuge on Osmia. They were captured by the Ministry and kept locked away in a secret laboratory under 'protocol 3', in the case of an unforeseen cataclysmic failure of the hard-light forms. We estimate there's likely several hundred of them locked away from centuries ago - each of them an innocent life, as well as a time capsule for ancient forgotten history. We hoped to storm the Capital and force them to release the captives, but as you can see that didn't work out as planned."</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Whoops. Sorry about that.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Don't be. We understand your alliance with the Ministry as part of the Federation took precedence. But now, I'm afraid I must ask of you a favor that is not in the interest of that alliance. Our military is not strong enough to take on the vessel guarding the lab, and our only ship capable, you caused quite the damage to. We cannot offer you the same as the Ministry might, so I expect nothing more than your refusal. But if you accept this plea out of the kindness of your heart, then you will forever have the Osmian people's gratitude."</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Agree to rescue the captives.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Really? I cannot believe this. But I haven't time to thank you any further. I must encourage you to hurry, I cannot say if the Ministry will take action to further protect the specimens in the face of our actions or not. I'll transfer the coordinates immediately. Our transports will be on the way shortly after you arrive. Best of luck. Our people are counting on you."</text>
					<quest event="OSMIA_LAB"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Decline.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Understandable. At least I can thank you for allowing us to continue to exist as we were. Best of luck on your travels."</text>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<ship name="SHIP_ZOLTAN_LAB" auto_blueprint="MU_ZOLTAN_LAB">
	<triggeredEvent name="TRIGGER_OSMIAN_ARRIVAL" event="OSMIAN_ARRIVAL" enemyDamage="10" enemyDeaths="4"/>
	<destroyed>
		<text>The peacekeepers have been defeated. You expect more reinforcements, but it seems the lab just intends to surrender instead. The Ministry is desperate to hide this truth, but apparently not enough to risk a full-scale war.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="OSMIA_LAB_WIN"/>    
		</choice>
	</destroyed>
	<deadCrew>
		<text>The peacekeepers have been defeated. You expect more reinforcements, but it seems the lab just intends to surrender instead. The Ministry is desperate to hide this truth, but apparently not enough to risk a full-scale war.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="OSMIA_LAB_WIN"/>    
		</choice>
	</deadCrew>
</ship>
<event name="OSMIA_LAB">
	<beaconType id="map_icon_secretlab" global="true">
		<color r="255" g="85" b="75" a="1.0"/>
		<unvisitedTooltip>Location of the secret Ministry Lab.</unvisitedTooltip>
		<visitedTooltip>Explored location. Nothing left of interest.</visitedTooltip>
	</beaconType>
	<preventQuest/>
	<preventFleet/>
	<quest>
		<nebulaBeacon>true</nebulaBeacon>
		<createNebula>true</createNebula>
		<nextSector>true</nextSector>
		<aggressive>1</aggressive>
	</quest>
	<img back="BACK_EVENT_SECRETLAB" planet="PLANET_INVISIBLE"/>
	<text>There is zero doubt in your mind this is the place. Just from the immediate sinister appearance, it's clear this is not an ordinary secret base - if there ever was one. According to the Osmians, the security must be tight, and getting any closer without being detected is impossible.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Pull closer.</text>
		<event>
			<text>As soon as you cross a certain threshold, a Peace-keeper vessel activates. It's a cruiser, and therefore no idle threat. "Entrance to Zone E17 is forbidden. How did you find this place?"</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_ZOLTAN_LAB" hostile="false"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>No question - time to fight.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You're done being told what to do by the Ministry. Time to finally give them what they've had coming for a long time.</text>
					<ship hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="MORALITY_UPDATE_ZOLTAN_FIGHT"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Oops sorry, we're lost. We'll leave!</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Leave.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You've bitten off more than you can chew this time. The Osmians will need to find someone else to help them.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="OSMIAN_ARRIVAL">
	<clearTriggeredEvent name="TRIGGER_OSMIAN_ARRIVAL"/>
	<text>Your radar immediately picks up several more pings. You're afraid this means the Zoltans have received reinforcements - but this isn't the case. In fact, it's quite the opposite. The Osmians have arrived, and unlike most of your "allies" in conflicts like this, they're actually providing firepower from the sidelines!</text>
	<environment type="PDS" target="enemy"/>
</event>
<event name="OSMIA_LAB_WIN">
	<text>The Osmian troops, though limited in ships, are plentiful in manpower and storm the lab. The Zoltan scientists surrender. You take note of assorted Engi and even a few workers in Federation garb in the crowd, but you're distracted by Malki. "Thank you for your help. Though material offers I cannot extend, I can provide your Federation blueprints for our finest warship. We-" Suddenly, an alarm blares. Something bad is happening!</text>
	<unlockCustomShip silent="false">PLAYER_SHIP_OSMIA</unlockCustomShip>
	<variable name="ach_boss_zone" op="set" val="1"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Shortly after the alarm, another warning plays over the stereo. You might be getting tired of all these warnings, but this isn't one to be ignored. "Evacuate the premises immediately. Nuclear strike imminent." Panic immediately breaks out, and your radar detects an approaching warhead. Apparently, in case of emergency, the Ministry rigged this place to destroy itself. If your holopad's estimation is correct, you have 10 minutes before the impact.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Assist the Osmians in moving the stasis pods.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Your crew rush over to help, disengaging the pods from their holding compartments and carrying them over to the awaiting Osmian transport vessels. As the timer continues to tick down, you realize there's a much greater issue than the time limit - there isn't enough space for all of the specimens. Malki notices too and is dismayed. "What will we do now? There isn't enough time for multiple trips!"</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>We have to leave them behind!</text>
						<event load="OSMIAN_LEAVE"/>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true" req="BLUELIST_CREW_STRONG">
						<text>(Strong Crew) Haul some of the pods onto your ship.</text>
						<event>
							<text>With the other transports full, the only option is to load the chambers onto your own ship. You bring as many back as possible, but you can't help but notice Malki is still rushing around fruitlessly trying to fit more containers on the other ships.</text>
							<augment name="ZOLTAN_SPAWNER"/>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Urge him to leave.</text>
								<event load="OSMIAN_LEAVE"/>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>We've done our part - leave!</text>
				<event>
					<text>You apologize to Malki, but he hardly notices as he's already run off to help move as many stasis chambers as possible. You hurry back to your ship and prepare to leave.</text>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="OSMIAN_LEAVE">
	<text>"Are you insane? We didn't come this far just to leave them behind! We- we have to rescue as many as we can!" You try to explain there isn't possibly enough time to move them all, but Malki won't listen. Eventually, through force, you manage to drag him back to your ship as the rest of the Osmians flee. Though you weren't able to save all of the specimens and the scientists are doomed, at least all of the Osmians and your crew were able to make it away safely.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>From the distance as you leave the planet behind you can see the flash of the detonation. In grim silence Malki watches, unresponsive. "I have failed my people. But... I should have known. The Ministry would sooner destroy its heritage than allow its people to see the truth. It's not like it matters to them. If they ever need new specimens they know they can just attack Osmia again. That lab was merely a formality. If news of our raid gets out at all, I'm sure it'll be spun as an accident, though even that is doubtful."</text>
			<changeBackground>BACKGROUND</changeBackground>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>There were Federation scientists there too. Why?</text>
				<event>
					<text>"You think the Federation didn't know about us? I'm sure they've briefed all the rest that we're some dangerous threat. That way, if we ever tried to start another civil war, the Federation wouldn't hesitate to side with the Ministry. But that's besides the point... I shouldn't be so grim. We didn't save everyone - we couldn't have. But we still saved dozens of our people, and we may finally recover some of our lost history. But, as the leader of my people, I have failed to prepare us for such outcomes: I cannot return to Osmia. I humbly request that you accept my services, captain."</text>
					<crewMember amount="1" all_skills="2" class="zoltan_osmian">Malki</crewMember>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
</FTL>
