<FTL>
<eventList name="STORAGE_CHECK_JOB_SALVAGE_DEFAULT">
	<event load="SALVAGE_DEFAULT_LOW"/>
	<event load="SALVAGE_DEFAULT_LOW"/>
	<event load="SALVAGE_DEFAULT_MED"/>
	<event load="SALVAGE_DEFAULT_MED"/>
	<event load="SALVAGE_DEFAULT_HIGH"/>
	<event load="SALVAGE_DEFAULT_FUEL"/>
	<event load="SALVAGE_DEFAULT_MINEFIELD"/>
	<event load="SALVAGE_DEFAULT_DRONE"/>
	<event load="SALVAGE_DEFAULT_PIRATES"/>
	<event load="SALVAGE_FAIL"/>
</eventList>
<eventList name="STORAGE_CHECK_JOB_SALVAGE_ARM">
	<event load="SALVAGE_ARM_LOW"/>
</eventList>

<event name="SALVAGE_FAIL">
	<text>Your crew find little of value; disappointed, they return to the ship.</text>
	<variable name="loc_has_salvaged" op="set" val="1"/>
</event>

<!--ARM-->
<event name="SALVAGE_ARM_LOW">
	<text>You wait a reasonable amount of time in hopes the arm will attract any close range junk, then retract it and observe your haul.</text>
	<item_modify>
		<item type="scrap" min="0" max="4"/>
		<item type="missiles" min="0" max="2"/>
		<item type="drones" min="0" max="2"/>
	</item_modify>
</event>

<!--STANDARD-->
<event name="SALVAGE_DEFAULT_LOW">
	<text>Your crew find little, but it's still something. They return back to the ship with their haul.</text>
	<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
	<variable name="loc_has_salvaged" op="set" val="1"/>
</event>
<event name="SALVAGE_DEFAULT_MED">
	<text>Your crew find a decent amount of salvage. They return back to the ship with their haul.</text>
	<autoReward level="MED">stuff</autoReward>
	<variable name="loc_has_salvaged" op="set" val="1"/>
</event>
<event name="SALVAGE_DEFAULT_HIGH">
	<text>Your crew find a large amount of salvage. They return back to the ship with their haul.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">stuff</autoReward>
	<variable name="loc_has_salvaged" op="set" val="1"/>
</event>

<event name="SALVAGE_DEFAULT_FUEL">
	<text>Your crew find a ton of fuel cells, though their origin is uncertain. They return back to the ship with their haul.</text>
	<autoReward level="MED">fuel_only</autoReward>
	<variable name="loc_has_salvaged" op="set" val="1"/>
</event>

<event name="SALVAGE_DEFAULT_MINEFIELD">
	<text>Your crew stumble across an abandoned minefield. Certainly dubious, but also a potential source of a large amount of ammo and scrap. However, it's risky for the crew.</text>
	<variable name="loc_has_salvaged" op="set" val="1"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CHECK_ANY_CREW" lvl="1" blue="false">
		<text>Take the risk.</text>
		<event load="SALVAGE_DEFAULT_MINEFIELD_RISK"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CHECK_ANY_CREW" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
		<text>You have no sacrificial crew to send in the minefield.</text>
		<event load="OPTION_INVALID"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="rock_crusader">
		<text>Your Crusader knows a lot about explosives, and can also take a hit.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Though your Crusader knows quite a lot about explosives, the real reason he's a good choice is his thick skin. With little danger to their well-being, they return with an impressive haul, though it's not as good as you might have gotten with a larger team.</text>
			<autoReward level="MED">missiles</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="rock_paladin"> <!-- same outcome as crusader, but alt text -->
		<text>Your Paladin knows a lot about explosives, and can also take a hit.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Though your Paladin knows quite a lot about explosives, the real reason he's a good choice is because of his impressive resilience. With little danger to their well-being, they return with an impressive haul, although their slow speed prevents them from gathering more without letting the Rebel fleet gain time.</text>
			<autoReward level="MED">missiles</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>	
	<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_LANIUS">
		<text>Your Lanius can melt down some mines for scrap.</text>
		<event>
			<text>It won't yield any functional ammo, but it's low risk for some reward. You send out your Lanius to liquify as many mines as they can.</text>
			<autoReward level="LOW">scrap_only</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="false">
		<text>Don't risk it, just bring back a few of the outliers.</text>
		<event>
			<autoReward level="LOW">missiles_only</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="SALVAGE_DEFAULT_MINEFIELD_RISK">
	<event>
		<text>With some amount of grace, your crew manage to drift through the field without setting off any explosives. Disarming as many as they can, they bring back an impressive haul.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">missiles</autoReward>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>Your crew are less than graceful navigating the field, almost setting the entire thing off twice. At last, they push their luck for the final time, and one of your crew is blown into chunks! You can hear the rest of the team screaming in terror through the radio, but you silence them and order them back to the ship immediately with however much they've already collected.</text>
		<autoReward level="MED">missiles</autoReward>
		<removeCrew>
			<clone>true</clone>
			<text>Fortunately your crew has been revived by the Clone Bay, though they request they get a pass from the next salvaging mission.</text>
		</removeCrew>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>Your crew manage to disarm a lot of mines before they return, but spot something in the center. It's a Mine Launcher, the tool used to lay the field! Now that there's less mines, you can pilot closer and grab it, but risk setting off the remainders of the field with your ship.</text>
		<autoReward level="MED">missiles</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="false">
			<text>Get the Mine Launcher!</text>
			<event>
				<text>You grab the Mine Launcher and leave the field, only to accidentally trip one of them on the way out! Luckily the resulting explosion isn't too catastrophic, but it still hurts.</text>
				<weapon name="GIFTLIST_MINELAUNCHERS_TRAPPER"/>
				<damage amount="3"/>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="false">
			<text>Leave it.</text>
			<event/>
		</choice>
	</event>
</eventList>

<event name="SALVAGE_DEFAULT_DRONE">
	<text>Oddly enough, it appears a pair of Boarding Drones have been abandoned here in the abyss. You can break them down for parts easily, but if you scanned them for the schematics you might risk activating one.</text>
	<variable name="loc_has_salvaged" op="set" val="1"/>
	<choice hidden="false">
		<text>Break them down for parts.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The schematic isn't worth the risk. You salvage the drones.</text>
			<autoReward level="LOW">droneparts_only</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Scan them.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You attempt scanning, but due to your distance you're unable to get a read. You pull closer, but accidentally move a little too close, triggering the drones! Fortunately you still recover the schematic, but now they're onboard!</text>
			<boarders min="2" max="2" class="drone_battle"/>
			<damage amount="0" system="random" effect="breach"/>
			<damage amount="0" system="random" effect="breach"/>
			<drone name="BATTLETOG_DEFEND"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CHECK_ENERGY_SHIELD">
		<text>(Energy Shield) Approach without any fear of intruders.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Fortunately, your Energy Shield greatly simplify the process. You retrieve the schematic without having to deal with any resistance.</text>
			<drone name="BATTLETOG_DEFEND"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_ENGI">
		<text>(Engi Crew) Disable the drones first.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Fortunately, your Engi is able to disable the drones before scanning them.</text>
			<drone name="BATTLETOG_DEFEND"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
		<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_ENGINEER">
		<text>(Engineer Crew) Disable the drones first.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Fortunately, your Engineer is able to disable the drones before scanning them.</text>
			<drone name="BATTLETOG_DEFEND"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="SALVAGE_DEFAULT_PIRATES">
	<text>The immediate area around the beacon yields little, but after diving much deeper into the system you stumble across an inactive pirate ship scans didn't turn up before.</text>
	<variable name="loc_has_salvaged" op="set" val="1"/>
	<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CHECK_ANY_CREW" lvl="1" blue="false">
		<text>Send a team to see what loot might be inside.</text>
		<event load="SALVAGE_DEFAULT_PIRATES_LOOT"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CHECK_ANY_CREW" lvl="0" max_lvl="0" blue="false">
		<text>You cannot send a team, since you lack one.</text>
		<event load="OPTION_INVALID"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Scrap the hull.</text>
		<event load="SALVAGE_DEFAULT_PIRATES_SCRAP"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="false">
		<text>Ignore the ship.</text>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="SALVAGE_DEFAULT_PIRATES_LOOT">
	<event>
		<text>Your crew dig around the ship, but find all of the crew dead and anything of value gone. You resort to scrapping the hull instead.</text>
		<autoReward level="LOW">standard</autoReward>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>While exploring the interior, your crew find a lone survivor. Though they might have once been a pirate, they're more than willing to work for you.</text>
		<crewMember amount="1"/>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>Your crew find an entire functional weapon left behind in the ship's storage! They haul it back to the ship in triumph.</text>
		<weapon name="RANDOM"/>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>It looks like most of the ship has been stripped bare. However, the cargo bay is still locked, and it doesn't look like anyone's broken in yet. It wouldn't be too hard for you to do so, do you wish to proceed?</text>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Open their cargo.</text>
			<event>
				<text>You delicately cut your way through the door, but the second you step inside a trap is triggered! "Screw you, thieves!" shouts an automated message, followed by an explosion that rips one of your crew apart. Though the loss is terrible, it doesn't seem to be followed by any further repercussions, leaving you to take all that remains.</text>
				<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
				<removeCrew>
					<clone>true</clone>
					<text>Fortunately, your Clone Bay is already in the process of reviving your crew.</text>
				</removeCrew>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true" req="BLUELIST_CREW_NODOORS">
			<text>(Phasing Crew) Sneak inside.</text>
			<event>
				<text>Your crew is able to slip easily past the door and get inside, where they find a trap that they quickly defuse. Now that it's safe to enter, the rest of the crew follow and take all that they can.</text>
				<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_ROCK">
			<text>(Rock Crew) Send in your Rock first.</text>
			<event>
				<text>Your crew is able to easily bash the door open and get inside, but the second they step inside a trap is triggered! "Screw you, thieves!" shouts an automated message, followed by an explosion. Your crew member fortunately appears to only have flinched and is still whole. Now that it's safe to enter, the rest of the crew follow and take all that they can.</text>
				<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Leave it.</text>
			<event/>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>Your crew board the ship, but find it mostly empty. However, there's a very unpleasant stench in the air. Your crew open one of the storage cabinets only to find the rotting corpse in there, as well as what look to be... giant alien spiders?!</text>
		<boarders min="1" max="2" class="spider"/>
	</event>
</eventList>
<eventList name="SALVAGE_DEFAULT_PIRATES_SCRAP">
	<event>
		<text>You are undisturbed as you scrap the ship.</text>
		<autoReward level="LOW">standard</autoReward>
	</event>
</eventList>

</FTL>