<FTL>
<!--
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
					ABANDONDED SECTOR 
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\
-->

<!--
		ITEMS!!!
	Events that give stuff
-->
<eventList name="ITEMS_ABANDONED">
	<event load="ABANDONED_CRYSTAL_TOURIST"/>
	<event load="ABANDONED_COLONY"/>
	<event load="ABANDONED_SLAVER_MOON"/>
	
	<event load="TRADER_CIV"/>
	<event load="PIRATE_SALESMAN"/>
	<event load="ENGINEER_BUY_DRONES"/>
	<event load="TRADER_UPGRADES_EXCHANGE"/>
</eventList>

<event name="ABANDONED_CRYSTAL_TOURIST" unique="true">
	<text>A Crystal ship skitters between various burnt out wrecks and the withered skeletons of long-forgotten stations. They don't seem to notice you.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_CRYSTAL_GENERIC" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Contact them.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Oh, hello there! I didn't see you, I thought you were just part of the scenery. What a fine sector this is! Such interesting design choices for their ships, whoever lives here has excellent taste!"</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Explain that this sector has been abandoned.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Oh heavens. This shows just how ignorant I am. I should explore more, I've been roaming around this sector for months now! Perhaps I should come with you, you look like you've been to other places before."</text>
					<crewMember amount="1" class="crystal"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Ask if they have anything that can help with your mission.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Oh, certainly. I've been collecting relics from these fascinating structures... I hope the owners don't mind, but no one was ever home to argue... maybe you'll find use in them."</text>
					<autoReward level="LOW">augment</autoReward>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_CRYSTAL">
				<text>(Crystal Crew) Request access to their data storage.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Our maps? Why of course! These should be of use to you. Happy travels!"</text>
					<reveal_map/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="INFO_MACHINE_HACKING">
				<text>(Analyzer + Hacking) Remotely access their data storage.</text>
				<event>
					<text>While you make small talk with the Crystals, you configure the Hacking system to get a read of their data storage while the Analyzer downloads their map data. Once the download is complete, you bid farewell and the Crystals even offer a small reward for being so pleasant.</text>
					<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
					<reveal_map/>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Ignore them.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You have no interest in the strange Crystal ship.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="ABANDONED_SLAVER_MOON" unique="true">
	<text>A very faint signal from an unidentified ship is emitting from a small moon in the local system. It's a little choppy, but you manage to make out the words "workers - great price - stop by."</text>
	<img planet="PLANET_MOONS"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Pull closer.</text>
		<event>
			<text>It seems a slave trader is selling their 'goods' on the nearby moon, knowing it's far away from the eye of the Federation out here in this sector.</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_SLAVER_ALL" hostile="false"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Check out the slaves being offered.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The slavers notice your interest and show you several offers.</text>
					<choice> <!--currently just uses the oddshop slave lists... probably fine...-->
						<text>Buy a slave.</text>
						<event load="PIRATE_ODDSHOP_SLAVE"/>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>Buy a slave.</text>
						<event load="PIRATE_ODDSHOP_SLAVE"/>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>Buy an elite slave.</text>
						<event load="PIRATE_ODDSHOP_SLAVE_ELITE"/>
					</choice>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Nevermind.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Attack the slavers!</text>
				<event>
					<text>The Slavers might have thought they were safe here, but you've arrived and you aren't going to let their business carry on for any longer.</text>
					<ship hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Leave.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Ignore the moon and signal.</text>
		<event>
			<text>It's more than clear this is some sort of slave trade, and you have no interest.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="ABANDONED_COLONY" unique="true">
	<text>An abandoned colony lies on the nearby planet; its surface borne defense turrets appear to be disabled due to a lack of power, but you can't be certain. You don't see any ships lurking about, but that doesn't mean they aren't hiding.</text>
	<img planet="PLANET_POPULATED"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Explore.</text>
		<event load="ABANDONED_COLONY_EXPLORE"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="PDS_DISABLE">
		<text>(Signal Diluter) Make certain the defense turrets are offline.</text>
		<event load="ABANDONED_COLONY_EXPLORE_NOTURRETS"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="FLARE_DISTRACTION">
		<text>(Flares) Launch some flares to distract the defense turrets while you explore.</text>
		<event load="ABANDONED_COLONY_EXPLORE_NOTURRETS"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="sensors" lvl="3">
		<text>(Upg. Sensors) Run some heavier scans on the colony.</text>
		<event load="ABANDONED_COLONY_EXPLORE_SCANS"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="ADV_SCANNERS">
		<text>(LRS) Run some heavier scans on the colony.</text>
		<event load="ABANDONED_COLONY_EXPLORE_SCANS"/>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Ignore the colony.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You don't have time to explore every abandoned colony you come across.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="ABANDONED_COLONY_EXPLORE">
	<event>
		<text>It seems the turrets still had some juice in them after all. They lock onto your ship, pelting your defenses and causing some minor damage. You pull away before they can do anything worse.</text>
		<damage amount="3"/>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>It turns out the colony was harbouring a pirate fugitive. Now that their cover has been blown, they protect themselves and attack you.</text>
		<ship load="SHIP_PIRATE_ALL" hostile="true"/>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>Luckily the turrets remain offline and no ships rise to meet you. You take all that you can gather from the wreckage of the colony.</text>
		<autoReward level="MED">item</autoReward>
	</event>
</eventList>
<eventList name="ABANDONED_COLONY_EXPLORE_NOTURRETS">
	<event>
		<text>It turns out the colony was harbouring a pirate fugitive. Now that their cover has been blown, they protect themselves and attack you.</text>
		<ship load="SHIP_PIRATE_ALL" hostile="true"/>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>Luckily the turrets remain offline and no ships rise to meet you. You take all that you can gather from the wreckage of the colony.</text>
		<autoReward level="MED">item</autoReward>
	</event>
</eventList>
<eventList name="ABANDONED_COLONY_EXPLORE_SCANS">
	<event>
		<text>Scans show the turrets are still connected to a functioning backup generator. It's too risky to approach while they're active.</text>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>Seems a known pirate fugitive is hiding in the colony, but they haven't seen you yet.</text>
		<ship load="SHIP_PIRATE_ALL" hostile="false"/>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Engage the pirate.</text>
			<event>
				<text>Realizing that their cover has been blown, the pirates protect themselves and attack you.</text>
				<ship hostile="true"/>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
				</choice>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice>
			<text>Avoid the pirate and scrap some of the debris.</text>
			<event>
				<autoReward level="MED">stuff</autoReward>
			</event>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>Scans show no ships detected and confirm the turrets are offline. You take all that you can gather from the wreckage of the colony.</text>
		<autoReward level="MED">item</autoReward>
	</event>
</eventList>

<!--
		HOSTILE!!!
	Events that always have a fight
-->
<eventList name="HOSTILE_ABANDONED">
	<event load="ENCOUNTER_LANIUS_ABANDONED"/>
	<event load="ENCOUNTER_PIRATE_ABANDONED"/>
	<event load="ENCOUNTER_GHOST_ABANDONED"/>
	<event load="ENCOUNTER_REBEL_ABANDONED"/>
	<event load="ENCOUNTER_MILITIA_ABANDONED"/>
	
	<event load="HAZARD_ABANDONED"/>
</eventList>

<event name="ENCOUNTER_LANIUS_ABANDONED">
	<text load="TEXT_ENCOUNTER_LANIUS_ABANDONED"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_LANIUS_FIGHT" hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_ENCOUNTER_LANIUS_ABANDONED">
	<text>A Lanius vessel stops repurposing an abandoned satellite as soon as you jump in. It blocks all hails and powers its weapons.</text>
	<text>You arrive to see a well-armed Lanius craft preparing to salvage a badly damaged Rebel patrol ship. Noticing your arrival, the Lanius greedily moves in to intercept its second target of the day.</text>
	<text>The Lanius don't pick and choose when it comes to their targets. If you've got scrap, they'll gladly take it from you. Unfortunately, you've been detected by a nearby Lanius ship that swoops in to attack.</text>
	<text>Lanius aren't exactly known for friendliness, but an unusually aggressive military vessel has locked onto your ship and is readying its weapons.</text>
	<text>You stumble across a Lanius vessel melting down the last few remains of a heavily armed Zoltan peace-keeping fighter. Wanting to defend their latest score, they don't give you any opportunities and attack immediately.</text>
	<text>A Lanius ship looking for easy salvage spots you and moves in to intercept.</text>
</textList>

<event name="ENCOUNTER_PIRATE_ABANDONED">
	<text load="TEXT_ENCOUNTER_PIRATE_ABANDONED"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_PIRATE_ALL" hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_ENCOUNTER_PIRATE_ABANDONED">
	<text>If there's one thing pirates like more than anything, it's scrap. Though most come here to salvage empty ships, the one here has chosen to attack you instead.</text>
	<text>A nearby pirate ship notices you. It abandons the wreck it's currently salvaging, hoping you'll be carrying a greater bounty.</text>
	<text>This sector has proven to be a magnet for pirates, an unfortunate fact that has led to the confrontation awaiting you at this beacon.</text>
	<text>Few pirates can resist the temptation of a large bounty regardless of the risk, and it seems the pirate barreling towards you has given in.</text>
	<text>It seems a pirate has found their way to this beacon already, and is eager for a fight.</text>
	<text>Surprisingly, a pirate ship scavenging an old Militia Transport abandons its latest prey in favor of fighting you instead.</text>
</textList>

<event name="ENCOUNTER_GHOST_ABANDONED">
	<text load="TEXT_ENCOUNTER_GHOST_ABANDONED"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_GHOST_ALL" hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_ENCOUNTER_GHOST_ABANDONED">
    <text>Ghosts love getting their hands on new ships, and usually they go for easier pickings. Despite this, the Vagabond ship here seems ready to migrate and they've chosen your ship as their target.</text>
    <text>It's beyond you why most Ghosts choose to populate barely functional wreckage, but it seems the hostile ship here has slightly higher standards and have chosen to take yours next.</text>
    <text>You receive a hail from a dysfunctional and heavily damaged ship, but the only audible noise is static. You attempt to respond but somehow seem to have angered the populates of the ship, a clan of Ghosts.</text>
    <text>The range of ships you see here keeps growing, and it seems 'wreck full of mad gas beings' can be added to the list.</text>
    <text>Ghosts aren't known for being super confrontational, but when they find a ship that piques their interest, they aren't shy to try and take it. Clearly, you've made quite the impression out here.</text>
    <text>You nearly make the mistake of attempting to salvage the wreckage at this beacon before realizing it's populated by Ghosts, but it's already too late. They've noticed you now and move in to attack.</text>
</textList>

<event name="ENCOUNTER_REBEL_ABANDONED">
	<text load="TEXT_ENCOUNTER_REBEL_ABANDONED"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_REBEL_FIGHT" hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="TEXT_ENCOUNTER_REBEL_ABANDONED">
	<text>Though the fighting in this sector has long since ended, it seems a Rebel ship still lingers, and is ready to fight you.</text>
	<text>A Rebel captain hails you: "Do you see now the cost of your war? Give up and let the Rebellion take over, it is best for everyone this way."</text>
	<text>The Rebel ship that rests here is not willing to let you go without a fight. Prepare for battle!</text>
	<text>You thought most of the Rebel forces had left this sector after the evacuations, but it seems a few ships remain and are just as ready for battle as ever.</text>
	<text>"Haha! You were expecting another empty colony, but it was me all along!" The nearby Rebel ship locks onto your hull and attacks.</text>
	<text>It seems a Rebel ship here was lying in wait, ready to ambush any Federation ships that may be passing through. A fight is inevitable.</text>
</textList>

<event name="ENCOUNTER_MILITIA_ABANDONED" unique="true">
	<text>It seems a nearby Militia ship trying desperately to protect this sector has made a mistake and identified you as a scavenger. You don't have time to explain because they've muted comms and are moving in quickly.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_MILITIA_FIGHT" hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
		ENVIRONMENT!!!
	Events with unique environments
-->
<eventList name="HAZARD_ABANDONED">
	<event load="ENCOUNTER_GHOST_ABANDONED_ASTEROID"/>
	<event load="ENCOUNTER_LANIUS_ABANDONED_SUN"/>
</eventList>

<event name="ENCOUNTER_GHOST_ABANDONED_ASTEROID" unique="true">
	<text>A Ghost ship has come to this asteroid field looking for a new ship to acquire. It seems they're willing to settle with yours, despite the hazard here.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_GHOST_ALL" hostile="true"/>
	<environment type="asteroid"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="ENCOUNTER_LANIUS_ABANDONED_SUN" unique="true">
	<text>A Lanius ship hails you, spouting nonsense about the nearby star. "Heat... die, must not stay!" You think they're trying to warn you, but they're attacking as well. You're confused on their motives but you have no choice but to defend your ship.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_LANIUS_GENERIC" hostile="true"/>
	<environment type="sun"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
		NEUTRAL!!!
	Events that could have a fight
-->
<eventList name="NEUTRAL_ABANDONED">
	<event load="ABANDONED_FUELING_STATION"/>
	<event load="ABANDONED_PIRATE_CIVILIAN"/>
	<event load="ABANDONED_LANIUS_AUTO_REBEL"/>
	<event load="ABANDONED_LANIUS_GROUP_AUTO"/>
	<event load="LANIUS_CIVILIAN"/>
	
	<event load="ABANDONED_WRECK"/>
	<event load="ABANDONED_REBEL_DELUSIONAL"/>
	<event load="ABANDONED_GHOST_LANIUS_DUEL"/>
	<event load="ABANDONED_CIVILIAN_LOST_ITEMS"/>
</eventList>

<event name="ABANDONED_CIVILIAN_LOST_ITEMS" unique="true">
	<text>A civilian ship hails you, requesting you do them a favor. "You're operating on Federation comms, so we hope you support what the Federation stands for. We were some of the civilians forced to evacuate this sector, but we left some important personal items behind. This ship isn't designed for combat, and it is dangerous for us to be here. Could you grab our belongings? We'll pay you of course."</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Agree to grab their things.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You approach the colony; a hostile Vagabond ship comes flying out to meet you!</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_GHOST_LOST_ITEMS" hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_VAGABOND">
				<text>(Vagabond Crew) Reason with the aggressive ship.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Your Vagabond convinces the other Ghosts to stand down. They might be loose-cannon scavengers, but it seems they're more interested in protecting themselves than actually fighting you.</text>
					<ship hostile="false"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="ABANDONED_CIVILIAN_LOST_ITEMS_WIN"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>We can't help.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The civilians are disappointed but say they understand.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="ABANDONED_CIVILIAN_LOST_ITEMS_WIN">
	<text>You dig through the withering settlements until you find the items in question, a few family photos, a box of children's toys, and a replica sword of some obscure Mantis warlord. The civilians are pleased and pay you.</text>
	<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
</event>

<event name="ABANDONED_PIRATE_CIVILIAN">
	<text load="ABANDONED_PIRATE_CIVILIAN_TEXT"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_PIRATE_CIVILIAN_LANIUS" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Attack the pirate.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You charge your weapons, which quickly gets the pirate ship's attention.</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice req="FLARE_DISTRACTION" hidden="true">
		<text>(Flares) Use the flares to make a distraction so the Civilian ship can escape.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The pirate is startled by the sudden barrage of flares but quickly realizes he isn't alone. Uncertain where the flares are coming from, the pirate flees rather than take the risk of fighting a bigger ship.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="SAVE_CIVILIAN_LIST"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Avoid the conflict.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Unfortunately it is not your mission to save every person affected by this war or the Lanius invasion.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="ABANDONED_PIRATE_CIVILIAN_TEXT">
	<text>You discover an abandoned mining facility in the process of being 'acquired' by pirate scavengers. However, you immediately receive a call from a civilian transport vessel, "Help! We were trying to escape only to be caught by pirates!" You see a lone pirate ship boarding the civilian craft.</text>
	<text>A pirate ship emerges from hiding after you and another ship jump into the area. Sensors show the pirates ran a quick scan of your ship's weapon system before flying off to pursue the unarmed civilian ship.</text>
	<text>A pirate ship is firing on the small ships docked at a refueling station. They are broadcasting on a wide band channel. You catch the captain's rant mid-speed, "...saw you trading with those damned scavengers. I'll show you what happens when you try and undercut the Red Giant gang!"</text>
</textList>

<event name="ABANDONED_LANIUS_AUTO_REBEL" unique="true">
	<text>You come across a Lanius ship in the process of absorbing a Rebel automated scout. If you scare off the Lanius you could probably make use of it.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_LANIUS_AUTO" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Fight the ship.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You power up your weapons, which quickly gets the attention of the ship.</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice req="LIST_CREW_LANIUS" hidden="true">
		<text>(Lanius Crew) Request access to the Auto-ship first.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The other Lanius at first become territorial, refusing to give up the Auto, but when you explain you only intend to download the data stores, the Lanius oblige. You find the Auto-ship still has a fully functional system to warn the fleet on your location, so you feed it false data and download the map information.</text>
			<modifyPursuit amount="-1"/>
			<reveal_map/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice req="FLARE_DISTRACTION" hidden="true">
		<text>(Flares) Use the flares to guide the Lanius away from the auto.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You've heard stories the Lanius have poor eyesight and poor attention spans, and where that's true or not, this lanius certainly is drawn to your flares. It moves away from the auto temporarily to chase the disc, giving you just enough time to move in closer.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="LANIUS_AUTO_REBEL_LIST"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Leave them alone.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Whatever assistance the disabled scout could provide is not worth the risk of fighting another Lanius. You prepare to move on.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="LANIUS_AUTO_REBEL_LIST">
	<event>	
		<text>You are able to retrieve a significant amount of data about the surrounding beacons from the scout before you scrap it.</text> 
		<autoReward level="LOW">scrap_only</autoReward>
		<reveal_map/>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>You find the ship has a built-in method of warning the Rebel fleet of contact with your ship. You feed it some false data about your ship's whereabouts that should keep the fleet off your tail for a time.</text>
		<autoReward level="LOW">scrap_only</autoReward>
		<modifyPursuit amount="-1"/>
	</event>
</eventList>

<event name="ABANDONED_LANIUS_GROUP_AUTO" unique="true">
	<text>You notice a number of Lanius ships absorbing a forward Rebel base and its automated scouts. They don't seem to be aggressive. Perhaps their desire for metal could prove to be useful?</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Try to use them to delay the Rebels.</text>
		<event load="LANIUS_GROUP_AUTO_OUTCOME"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Leave them alone.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You decide it would be better to leave them be.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_LANIUS">
		<text>(Lanius Crew) Try to use them to delay the Rebels.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Your crewmember tells them of the approaching fleet and the number of automated ships they use to scout ahead. They thank you for the tip and prepare to jump in the direction you came. That will hopefully delay the fleet. You scrap what remains of the Rebel station.</text>
			<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
			<modifyPursuit amount="-1"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="LANIUS_GROUP_AUTO_OUTCOME">
	<event>
		<text>You try your best to convey the notion that the approaching Rebel fleet has countless automated ships scouting for them. However, either the translation device has failed or they're simply not interested. They cut the channel and continue to absorb the ships.</text>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>You try your best to convey the notion that the approaching Rebel fleet has countless automated ships scouting for them. You're not certain if you were misunderstood but they appear to scoff at your suggestion. Most ships continue what they were doing but a single ship moves to fight you.</text>
		<ship load="SHIP_LANIUS_FIGHT" hostile="true"/>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>You try your best to convey the notion that the approaching Rebel fleet has countless automated ships scouting for them. They thank you for the tip and prepare to jump in the direction you came. That will hopefully delay the fleet. You scrap what remains of the Rebel station.</text>
		<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
		<modifyPursuit amount="-1"/>
	</event>
</eventList>

<event name="ABANDONED_FUELING_STATION" unique="true">
	<text>You detect a refueling platform near the beacon, although its broadcast signal is garbled, and you can't make out the message.</text>
	<choice>
		<text>Hail the platform and attempt to communicate.</text>
		<event>
			<text>There is a screech from your comm system, and the broadcast suddenly cuts off. The platform suddenly begins to move, revealing itself to be a Lanius ship!</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_LANIUS_FUELING_STATION" hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Dock with the platform.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Your ship enters one of the refueling station berths, grateful for a rest.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Signal for a refuel.</text>
				<event load="ABANDONED_FUELING_STATION_LIST"/>
			</choice>
			<choice req="doors" lvl="2" hidden="true">
				<text>(Blast Doors) Secure your blast doors - best to be safe when docked.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Your reinforced doors save you from an attempted ambush by the Lanius, who cluster around the doors and hull, attempting to consume your ship. Coldly, you wipe them out one by one with your weapon array, then take control of the station and take its fuel reserves.</text>
					<item_modify>
						<item type="fuel" min="5" max="5"/>
					</item_modify>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Ignore the platform.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You leave the platform alone, and prepare to jump.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="ABANDONED_FUELING_STATION_LIST">
	<event>
		<text>Your ship's dashboard suddenly lights up with warnings - a hull breach! Lanius were on board the platform and are now on board your ship. A hidden cruiser comes into view!</text>
		<ship load="SHIP_LANIUS_FUELING_STATION" hostile="true"/>
		<boarders breach="true" min="1" max="1" class="lanius"/>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>What seemed to be a brief respite turns into a Lanius trap... the first warning is an explosion from your engine room, followed moments later by detection of a Lanius ship at sensor range!</text>
		<ship load="SHIP_LANIUS_FUELING_STATION" hostile="true"/>
		<damage amount="3" system="engines"/>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>No one answers your hails. You run some scans and discover that the station has been recently abandoned, no doubt due to the threat of the Lanius. You empty their fuel reserves before leaving.</text> 
		<item_modify>
			<item type="fuel" min="3" max="5"/>
		</item_modify>
		<choice>
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event/>
		</choice>
		<choice req="sensors" lvl="2" hidden="true" max_group="0">
			<text>(Improved Sensors) Run another scan at maximum sensitivity.</text>
			<event>
				<text>You run an additional more focused scan and find one of the auxiliary refueling platforms has some unclaimed fuel.</text>
				<item_modify>
					<item type="fuel" min="1" max="3"/>
				</item_modify>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice req="sensors" lvl="3" hidden="true" max_group="0">
			<text>(Advanced Sensors) Run another scan at maximum sensitivity.</text>
			<event>
				<text>You run an additional more focused scan and find one of the auxiliary refueling platforms has some unclaimed fuel and drone parts.</text>
				<item_modify>
					<item type="fuel" min="2" max="3"/>
					<item type="drones" min="1" max="3"/>
				</item_modify>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice req="ADV_SCANNERS" lvl="3" hidden="true" max_group="0">
			<text>(Advanced Sensors) Run another scan at maximum sensitivity.</text>
			<event>
				<text>You run an additional more focused scan and find one of the auxiliary refueling platforms has some unclaimed fuel and drone parts.</text>
				<item_modify>
					<item type="fuel" min="2" max="3"/>
					<item type="drones" min="1" max="3"/>
				</item_modify>
			</event>
		</choice>
	</event>
</eventList>
<event name="ABANDONED_FUELING_STATION_END">
	<text>It looks as if the Lanius were uninterested in the fuel reserves on the station, and there is a good amount of fuel left. You take what your ship can hold and prepare to jump to the next beacon.</text>
	<item_modify>
		<item type="fuel" min="3" max="5"/>
	</item_modify>
</event>

<event name="ABANDONED_WRECK" unique="true">
	<text>The wreckage of an old ship drifts nearby, but it's possible that the ship may still contain some supplies.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Scrap the wreck.</text>
		<event load="ABANDONED_WRECK_SALVAGE"/>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Ignore it.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You have higher standards than the filthy Lanius, Ghosts, and pirates that swarm this sector.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="ABANDONED_WRECK_SALVAGE">
	<event>
		<text>Before you can reach the wreck, a Militia ship comes swooping in to stop you. If you want to continue with your salvage mission you'll have to take care of them first.</text>
		<ship load="SHIP_MILITIA_WRECK" hostile="true"/>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>It seems you've made a miscalculation. The wreckage is still populated, not by its original crew but rather a bunch of angry Ghosts who aren't pleased by your attempts at breaking apart their ship.</text>
		<ship load="SHIP_GHOST_ALL" hostile="true"/>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>You are undisturbed as you scrap the wreckage.</text>
		<autoReward level="MED">stuff</autoReward>
	</event>
</eventList>

<event name="ABANDONED_REBEL_DELUSIONAL" unique="true">
	<text>A Rebel ship, presumably a straggler from the Rebel fleet hails you. "The battles, the horrors! You have wrought this battle upon us, and now you have come to finish the job? Around us civilians are dying and the planets burn, and you would rather fight us than help your own people?"</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_REBEL_FIGHT" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Explain to the Rebels the battles ended a long time ago.</text>
		<event load="ABANDONED_REBEL_DELUSIONAL_EXPLAIN"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="REBEL_ID">
		<text>(Forged ID) Claim to be a Rebel ship to comfort them.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Rebels captain is completely delusional but put at ease. It becomes clear they must have PTSD of some sort. Since you can't convince them the battles already ended, you talk the captain into joining your crew instead to 'escape'.</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="human" pilot="1"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_ENGINEER">
		<text>(Engineer Crew) Claim to be a Rebel ship to comfort them.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Rebels captain is completely delusional but put at ease. It becomes clear they must have PTSD of some sort. Since you can't convince them the battles already ended, you talk the captain into joining your crew instead to 'escape'.</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="human" pilot="1"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="mind" lvl="1">
		<text>(Mind Control) Convince him the battles already ended.</text>
		<event>
			<text>It seems these Rebels are further gone than you expected - your mind control struggles to compete with the madness that has infected his mind, and soon instead it drives the Rebel captain into rage!</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="mind" lvl="2">
		<text>(Upg. Mind Control) Convince him the battles already ended.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Your mind control temporarily cancels out the Rebel captain's madness. In this newfound clarity you explain the situation to him - and his reaction surprises you. "I've been wandering this sector for weeks raving out of my mind. This Rebellion is not suited for giving one peace of mind. Perhaps it's time I leave these days behind."</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="human" all_skills="1"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_MEDIC">
		<text>(Medic Crew) Have your medic evaluate the Rebel.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Your medic carefully runs a few checks on the Rebel and helps him through several mental exercises to clear his head. In this newfound clarity you explain the situation to him - and his reaction surprises you. "I've been wandering this sector for weeks raving out of my mind. This Rebellion is not suited for giving one peace of mind. Perhaps it's time I leave these days behind."</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="human" all_skills="1"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Fight the Rebels.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Rebels may be delusional about the 'battles' still raging in this sector, but that doesn't mean they aren't a threat that you need to neutralize.</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>These Rebels are crazy. Avoid them.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Luckily, the Rebels are still busy with their delusional ramblings to notice you sneaking away.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<eventList name="ABANDONED_REBEL_DELUSIONAL_EXPLAIN">
	<event>
		<text>The Rebels are too delusional to listen to you. They won't believe anything you say and eventually become so enraged they decide to attack you.</text>
		<ship hostile="true"/>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>The Rebels are beyond insane, and it's clear they must have PTSD of some sort. They accelerate, oblivious to the fact they're about to collide with you. You try to steer out of the way, but your hulls still collide. The Rebel ship takes the brunt of the hit and is compromised. Your ship still takes damage, but at least you can get some scrap out of it.</text>
		<damage amount="5" effect="breach"/>
		<autoReward level="LOW">standard</autoReward>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>The Rebels can't comprehend anything you say, and it becomes clear they must have PTSD of some sort. Since you can't convince them the battles are long since over, you talk the captain into joining your crew instead to 'escape'.</text>
		<crewMember amount="1" class="human" pilot="1"/>
	</event>
</eventList>

<event name="ABANDONED_GHOST_LANIUS_DUEL" unique="true">
	<text>It seems a Vagabond and Lanius ship are in the midst of a stand-off over a wreck, in a fashion that would put old-earth cowboys to shame.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Assist the Vagabonds and fight the Lanius.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You power up the thrusters and approach the Lanius vessel.</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_LANIUS_DUEL" hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_GHOST">
		<text>(Ghost Crew) Talk the Vagabonds into surrendering.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Though they certainly wouldn't listen to anyone else, your Ghost manages to talk the reason into the Vagabonds. They jump away, and the Lanius hails you. "Impress communication, wandering towards peace conditioning. Further engaging of peace. Will share?" Seems they're offering to share the wreck that started this feud.</text>
			<autoReward level="HIGH">item</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Assist the Lanius and fight the Vagabonds.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You power up the thrusters and approach the Vagabond vessel.</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_GHOST_DUEL" hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_LANIUS">
		<text>(Lanius Crew) Talk the Lanius into surrendering.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Though they certainly wouldn't listen to anyone else, your Lanius manages to reason their peers. They jump away, and the Vagabonds hails you. "Your vernacular does not cease to impress me. How have you managed to talk down the savage metal beasts? Oh, no matter. It seems this is the hour of good deeds, and it is my turn." Seems they're offering to share the wreck that started this feud.</text>
			<autoReward level="HIGH">item</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>These ships deserve each other.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Of all the partially aggressive, mysterious, scavenging alien races in existence, the Ghosts and Lanius are the two who deserve each other the most. You make sure to do several checks around the ship to discourage the crew from betting over which ship will win.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="ABANDONED_GHOST_LANIUS_DUEL_GHOST">
	<text>You aren't sure whether the Ghosts are merely paying you back for your assistance or are afraid of a ship who could so easily take on a formidable Lanius combatant, but the Ghosts avoid you and jump away. You scrap the wreckage that they were fighting over.</text>
	<autoReward level="MED">stuff</autoReward>
</event>
<event name="ABANDONED_GHOST_LANIUS_DUEL_LANIUS">
	<text>It's hard to communicate with the Lanius, but you manage to work out a deal with splitting the wreckage evenly between your two ships.</text>
	<autoReward level="MED">stuff</autoReward>
</event>

<!--
		DISTRESS!!!
	Events that have distress beacons
-->
<eventList name="DISTRESS_ABANDONED">
	<event load="DISTRESS_ABANDONED_GHOST_CONSTRUCTION"/>
	<event load="DISTRESS_ABANDONED_STOLEN_TECH"/>
	<event load="DISTRESS_ABANDONED_ASTEROID_COLONY"/>
</eventList>

<event name="DISTRESS_ABANDONED_GHOST_CONSTRUCTION" unique="true">
	<text>A Federation construction vessel is under attack by a clan of Ghost vagabonds. "Help! These Ghosts have come for our ship! Please, do something!"</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Dock with their ship and draw away the Ghosts.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Ghosts notice you docking and abandon their current target in favor of your much larger ship. The Federation crew are grateful for your assistance and offer pay, which you bring back to the ship after dealing with the Ghost invaders.</text>
			<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
			<boarders min="3" max="4" class="phantom_mare"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="BLUELIST_ANTIBIO">
		<text>(Anti-Bio Weapon) Exterminate the Ghosts.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You erase the Ghosts with ease, making sure not to harm the Federation crew. They're grateful and pay you some supplies.</text>
			<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="BLUELIST_BOMBS_CREWDAMAGE">
		<text>(Crew Damaging Bomb Weapon) Exterminate the Ghosts. [-3}]</text>
		<event>
			<text>You erase the Ghosts with ease, making sure not to harm the Federation crew. They're grateful and pay you some supplies.</text>
			<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="missiles" min="-3" max="-3"/>
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="PROTON_PACK">
		<text>(Proton Pack) Vacuum up the Ghosts.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You connect the Proton Pack to the Federation vessel then get to work capturing the Ghosts one by one. The Feds are so impressed by the efficiency of this they offer double the reward.</text>
			<autoReward level="HIGH">stuff</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Ignore them.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You can't risk your ship dealing with the Ghosts.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DISTRESS_ABANDONED_ASTEROID_COLONY" unique="true">
	<text>An abandoned space colony drifts nearby, a massive hole in its no-longer functional shield generator. It seems the distress signal comes from a band of refugees who've bunkered down in the skeletal remains. "Help us! Our scans show a massive meteor is heading straight for this colony and there's no way for us to evacuate or defend ourselves!"</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Help the refugees.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Your promise to assist is one thing, but you still need a way to stop the asteroid.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>We can tank some damage. Plant the ship in front of the asteroid.</text>
				<event>
					<text>It's not the smartest choice, but hell if it works. You take a pretty big hit but the asteroid shatters upon contact. The refugees are grateful for your help and offer one of the augments left behind by the old settlers, along with some supplies they don't need.</text>
					<damage amount="8"/>
					<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
					<augment name="RANDOM"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="shields" lvl="6">
				<text>(Adv. Shields) Deflect the asteroid with your shields.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Your shields take the blunt of the blow, shattering the asteroid. A few pieces manage to make their way through and scrape up the hull, but you're otherwise unharmed. The refugees are grateful for your help and offer one of the augments left behind by the old settlers, along with some supplies they don't need.</text>
					<damage amount="2"/>
					<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
					<augment name="RANDOM"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="BLUELIST_ARMOR">
				<text>(Hull Armor) Your armor can take a hit. Ricochet the asteroid off of your plating.</text>
				<event>
					<text>An asteroid colliding with the hull is still an asteroid colliding with the hull, and you take some damage regardless of your armor. Still, you resist most of the damage and the asteroid shatters on impact. The refugees are grateful for your help and offer one of the augments left behind by the old settlers, along with some supplies they don't need.</text>
					<damage amount="2"/>
					<autoReward level="LOW">stuff</autoReward>
					<augment name="RANDOM"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Guess we can't help after all.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You mute the comms and fly away.</text>
					<choice>
						<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
						<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>Do nothing.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Can't help, sorry.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You mute the comms and fly away.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="DISTRESS_ABANDONED_STOLEN_TECH" unique="true">
	<text>An Engi vessel, the source of the local distress signal, contacts you. "Assistance required. Job details: Lanius military vessel taken drone technology. Engi ship is poorly equipped, not combat ready. Your ship: adequate for mission. Should Federation accept, payment will be given."</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Agree to hunt down the Lanius.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Turns out the Lanius aren't far, but it seems they've already downloaded the schematic and consumed the original drone. If you want it back, you're going to have to find a way to download it off of their databanks.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Fight the Lanius ship to try and take back the schematic.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You have decided to fight the Lanius ship. If you want the schematic back, you'll have to make sure their computers aren't damaged.</text>
					<ship load="SHIP_LANIUS_STOLEN_DRONE" hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="hacking">
				<text>(Hacking) Hack their systems and transfer the schematic.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The data transfer goes without problem, but you've also alerted the Lanius of your presence, and they aren't happy.</text>
					<ship load="SHIP_LANIUS_STOLEN_DRONE_HACK" hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="ADV_SCANNERS">
				<text>(Long-Ranged Scanners) Transfer the schematic over to your computer.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The data transfer goes without problem, and the Lanius remain oblivious to your presence.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Contact the Engi.</text>
						<event load="DISTRESS_ABANDONED_STOLEN_TECH_WIN"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true" req="sensors" lvl="3">
				<text>(Adv. Sensors) Transfer the schematic over to your computer.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The data transfer goes without problem, and the Lanius remain oblivious to your presence.</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Contact the Engi.</text>
						<event load="DISTRESS_ABANDONED_STOLEN_TECH_WIN"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Run while you still can.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You power up the engines and fly far away until your computer can no longer detect the signal.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="DISTRESS_ABANDONED_STOLEN_TECH_WIN">
	<text>The Engi are not pleased that their drone was destroyed, but they still offer solid payment for the schematic.</text> 
	<choice>
		<text>Accept the payment.</text>
		<event>
			<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice req="drones">
		<text>(Drone Control) Construct the drone yourself and give it to the Engi.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You briefly construct the drone tech before transferring it over to the Engi ship.</text>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="drones" min="-1" max="-1"/>
			</item_modify>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event>
					<text>The Engi are baffled, confused as to why you felt it necessary to build the drone yourself when they too could construct the drone. They let you keep it and simply take the schematic instead, and transfer over regular payment.</text>
					<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
					<drone name="RANDOM"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<!--
		QUEST!!!
	Events that have distress beacons
-->
<eventList name="QUEST_ABANDONED">
	<event load="QUEST_ABANDONED_RAID"/>
</eventList>

<event name="QUEST_ABANDONED_RAID" unique="true">
	<text>At first this system looks rather ordinary, but a blip on your computer shows a new hail from a ship you cannot see.</text>
	<img planet="PLANET_UNPOPULATED"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Respond.</text>
		<event>
			<text>As soon as you open up the communications interface you spot a pirate ship slinking out of the shadows of a nearby planet. "Psssst, hey Feddy boy, ova' here! I gotta job offer for you. Me and my gang was heading to this ratha fine lookin' colony hopin' to find a large score of supplies when a buncha' spikey metal dudes come busin' outta nowhere! Nowhere, I tell ya'! Why don't yah do us one big favor and clear that place outta the Lanius ships? We gots pay, if that's what you lookin' for..."</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Agree to kill the Lanius.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The pirates give you the coordinates to the colony.</text>
					<quest event="QUEST_ABANDONED_RAID_COLONY"/>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Decline their offer.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You explain you aren't in the mercenary line of work and cut communications.</text>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Run while you still can.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You power up the engines and fly far away until your computer can no longer detect the signal.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="QUEST_ABANDONED_RAID_COLONY">
	<text>You've arrived at the abandoned colony. It seems that it's much better protected than you thought, with a group of Lanius ships, albeit small, in the dozens laying dormant nearby.</text> 
	<img planet="PLANET_POPULATED"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Attack the leader of the Lanius to drive away the others.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You single out the strongest of the ships, a dangerous Elite Lanius. If you can kill it, the other smaller ships likely won't be interested in sticking around.</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_LANIUS_RAID_ELITE" hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Pick off one of the smaller ships.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You single out one of the smaller Lanius ships and engage.</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_LANIUS_RAID" hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>This is a bad idea. Slip away while they still haven't noticed you.</text>
		<event>
			<text>This isn't what you expected. The pirates will have to find someone else to do the job.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="QUEST_ABANDONED_RAID_WIN">
	<text>Now that the colony is no longer protected by the Lanius, you have a choice to make.</text> 
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Contact the pirates and tell them the colony is free from the Lanius threat.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Not too long after the pirates jump in and thank you for the help. They pay you some supplies and a brand new weapon.</text>
			<autoReward level="MED">weapon</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Forget the pirates, scrap the colony yourself.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You quickly scrap all that you can from the colony before the pirates arrive.</text>
			<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

</FTL>