<metadata>
  <title><![CDATA[ FTL: MULTIVERSE ]]></title>
  <threadUrl><![CDATA[https://subsetgames.com/forum/viewtopic.php?f=11&t=35332]]></threadUrl>
  <author><![CDATA[ Kix, Laythe, AgentTHeKat, PDTM, MoreOrLesser, Felipemello, SquishyBoi, Jersee, Maddie Doktor]]></author>
  <version><![CDATA[ 5.3.1 ]]></version>
  <description>
<![CDATA[ 
YOU DO NOT NEED TO USE HYPERSPACE.FTL WITH THIS.
It is also recommended you do NOT patch Multiverse alongside any mods that are not made specifically for it.

FTL Multiverse (MV) is an extensive overhaul mod for the roguelike FTL: Faster Than Light that also uses the hard-coded modding API Hyperspace to accomplish things never before possible in FTL mods.

---**Over 200 brand new playable cruisers!**---

-Unlock ships through brand new questlines to play as any of the dozens of new factions and experience a wide range of playstyles
-Discover secret bonus ships through additional quests or achievements
-Unlock powerful Elite vessels with notable strengths and weaknesses as rewards for unlocking other ships

---**Dozens of new crew types**---

-Find entirely brand new alien species such as the Orchids, Shells, Leeches, as well as other secret species to discover in your travels
-Play with many different subtypes of crew like Human Medics, Engi Separatists, Zoltan Monks, and more
-Recruit powerful Elite Crew and Unique Characters from special events, who are much stronger than ordinary crew

---**New Sectors, Factions, and Lore**---

FTL Multiverse introduces an entirely new storyline, which while similar to FTL's, takes place after the original events of the Federation Civil War. It also introduces dozens of new factions, many of which are based on type B and C variants of player ships from the vanilla game!
These factions all have their own sectors, ships, crew, and often times special questlines as well where you'll meet some notable characters, even a few you might recognize from vanilla like Slocknog and Kazaaakplethkilik. While far more extensive than the vanilla lore, everything new to MV builds on top of it.

---**Brand New Challenges and Endings**---

-Fight new minibosses bosses along the way for unlocks and special loot items you can't get anywhere else
-Homeworld sectors are now completely revamped, with their own unique events and encounters, including extra deadly elite enemies similar to the Rebel ships you'll find at fleet controlled beacons
-Achieve various alternative endings through secret questlines. Your adventure doesn't always have to end with the Flagship!

---**Many, many more features**---

-Completely reworked stores that now function as additional events and are owned by different factions. Different store owners are more likely to sell different things, and some might not be so keen on selling to you at all unless you have something to convince them
-Sylvan the Traveling Merchant can be found all around the galaxy, selling many items (usually at a discount) as well as providing additional quests in certain sectors. Don't try and provoke him however, as only the strongest and most powerful ships could ever hope to take on his mighty vessel
-Battle over 800 new enemies, including stations that can't evade shots but have stronger defenses, battleships that can wield up to 6 weapons, motherships that wield massive arrays of drones, and more
-Use combat augments to disable your enemies's systems, and install internal upgrades to improve your ship in many different ways without using augment slots
-Upgrade your own crew using the Crew Lab, to specialize them towards certain niches that work better with your playstyles
-All of this and more awaits you in the completely overhauled experience that Multiverse brings to FTL: Faster Than Light

]]>
  </description>
</metadata>